sl0wp0ke_lu: <3
leDryPotato: PogChamp
sl0wp0ke_lu: Whats up?
tex01: Hi
capjackm: Yo
Bitcoin__: Bitcoin__ subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 14 months!
Sylfine_Unreal: hi
Santiago_LHC: YO
K0enich: good morning
eldac_kno: wasssup
mikaeeeeel: Heyhey
Mig1939: hey George!
DaMiniBeast: hiii
malana_cream: yo!
就很棒: :)
calebsuhy: hai george
Ne0Zer0: HeyGuys
furure_jedi: are you buying bitcoins ?
Deno_____: George I have a book recommendation for you: kalam cosmological arguments by mohammed hijab
ricardosmf: suuuup
TheSkapegoat: hi from Australia
sl0wp0ke_lu: Yooo
boosteraftermath: Hello
Santiago_LHC: Morning George
unluckychickenn: squadL
jonathan_haeberle: Hey!
boosteraftermath: Hello from India
soldierheadsmite: morning
InfiniteReddit: hi from aus
tex01: hello
DaMiniBeast: hi George
nasko0op: hi
anthonykwan: Night ! from Hong Kong ~~
mikaeeeeel: Do we hack the servers of the who today? 😄
adam_xxd: hi
siriusblack189: hello from india
axlebear: HeyGuys HeyGuys
ogrockefeller: Dad!
Santiago_LHC: I saw it
easysleeep: hey George. Where in SD did you move? I grew up in North County, Del Mar.
ogrockefeller: Father Hotz!
Santiago_LHC: I might submit one
danilosh45: Hi doc
aayaanamir: hello from Pakistan
joseanavarrom: What are we doing today??
c0sm3s: hey yoo
dawae_shw: hey cheers from Spain
detroitwiller: Germany wie gehts
Mig1939: george what do you think of YOLO?
ogrockefeller: Hacking session in full effect
tex01: hello
generated_human: Hi from Russia
mikaeeeeel: Gut gut
balloonpopa: Hi, I caught a live stream
Santiago_LHC: Nooooo, we love this apartment
kornez: PogChamp
henri2777: recht gut
boosteraftermath: but we love this apartment
krefsan: Hi from Peru !
aar0npham: aiyah
boosteraftermath: but we love it
pzuko7: hello from bermuda triangle
ogrockefeller: You should try to hack a Fleshlight Launch
jib1337: PepeHands
vovko_codes: @georgehotz what car would you recommend to run by commaai?
hichm19956: hi i'm from morocco 🇲🇦
furure_jedi: how can I donate you in bitcoins?
siriusblack189: I am writing nn for Tetris
capjackm: Are you staying in San Diego ?
aaddrr: ?????
markov010: hey !
th3_maj0r: yoyo
duzy: yea mic is good
Jehhred: Moving to San Fransisco?
ogrockefeller: Daddy Hotz
grahamstephan420: yo
ionelaipatioaei: how much is the rent?
mikaeeeeel: What is it actually about?
ogrockefeller: SF is cancer lol
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz what we doing today
meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeenz: george, changing the subject quickly, could you tell me the different between linear regression and logistic regression?
Santiago_LHC: So many memories in this apartment. We cooked together
grahamstephan420: comma.bio
jonathan_haeberle: What net are you training in the background?
DaMiniBeast: what we hacking today george??
balloonpopa: What ever happened with the protein folding?
furure_jedi: how can I donate you in bitcoins ?
anthonykwan: where u move then ?
boosteraftermath: How's it feel being an overachiever?
zooooodiac: what computer u use?
mikaeeeeel: Your thoughts on corona?
s4j0k5: saw you were looking for an app developer will some fucntions of openpilot be converted into an app?
axlebear: shots fired
pzuko7: !ide
Santiago_LHC: Don't start with the dumb questions, guys
vrv_exe: SD > SF
pzuko7: !commands
aaddrr: are there good taxes in SD?
krefsan: Any proposal for autonomous delivery robots with comma tech
theonlymonkas: Hi
Fatmetheny: Nice travel and outdoor stream. (I'm a non-sub please don't ban me for this criticism)
aaddrr: I would subscribe if I understood half of the shit he does
Santiago_LHC: "crap papers", I smell a new song
joeleonard212: joeleonard212 subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
sampleaccount123: Papers are from Arxiv Sanity?
dmfj_io: dmfj_io subscribed with Twitch Prime.
gal40: What's MuZero?
eduardoadf1: have you ever worked with verilog
meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeenz: george, changing the subject quickly, could you tell me the different between linear regression and logistic regression?
DelusionalDreams: DelusionalDreams subscribed with Twitch Prime.
luspr: luspr subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
aptgetmark: yo man whats up
kiwikili: kiwikili subscribed with Twitch Prime.
gal40: By dynamics you mean physics, or something else?
C4TFive: gotta publish to get funding!
Santiago_LHC: LOL
aaddrr: LULW
luspr: loved your prediction episode!
rkxbz: @georgehotz is fortnite going to be first step to move into simulation?
InfiniteReddit: where do you go to browse papers?
aaddrr: i would also like to know
Santiago_LHC: "Do parachutes matter", deep question
vrv_exe: Do you constantly review ML papers or do you read them according to what you are trying to solve?
Newlax: if you want to live
jib1337: Free paper Pog
yoyo_brobro: yoyo_brobro subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 12 months!
aaddrr: how do you test that lul
kornez: how many ppl without parachute did they drop off the plane? LUL
michaelkawwa: I'd imagine lmao
TheStudentDoctor: This was a tongue in cheek paper to illustrate the debate between RCTs and observational research to guide medical decision making
Newlax: test if parachutes work George
gorodinskiy: https://youtu.be/6qF_fzEI4wU
Santiago_LHC: QUANTUM PARACHUTES, they both exist and they don't at the same time
C4TFive: sound like more fun than russian roulette
AThousandHours: um.....
yogi_1010: hmm...
jib1337: I see...
dr_set: !uptime
Cutter1998: Gravitational challenge XD
Newlax: free skydiving
jib1337: Only 23?!
harmanthebest1: @georgehotz plz change the category right now it is travel & outdoors
buddhm: am i tripping?
OutsideGuidance: Heya, company that i work in is going to medicine in next year or two, making IoT devices that would be affordable to many of us and Im thinking to switch my current position to some programming, maybe some AI would be useful and i could jump ahead of time for now. What do you guys think? Even tho i got no programming experience
AThousandHours: 0 mph
yogi_1010: WaitWhat
hue88: they basically killed people ?
aar0npham: lo
leDryPotato: LUL
wholesome_pepe: how do u even placebo this?
siriusblack189: learned pytorch watching twitchchess
ViktorTV: @hue88 a total of 0 people died
jib1337: How many seriously injured
Kertoip007: PyTorch or TensorFlow, what's your opinion?
eldac_kno: what do you think about Yandex self driving car? sorry if a bit offtopic
Ne0Zer0: LUL
bichid69: why are we not folding proteins?
TheStudentDoctor: @outsideguidance start with the basics in a language that'll be useful for that field e.g. Python
matthewmirman: Seems pretty analogous to the situation in RL
hue88: that doesnt make sense, they said that parachuted didnt reduce death, does that mean that they woudl survive when jumping without a parachute ?
roussillon: LUL nice troll paper
chillguy269: LUL
Newlax: don't take drugs before skydiving boys
funwayz: so next time don't take parachute, save some money Kappa
yungtoad1: JonCarnage
garydsmith1: wtf what is that?
michaelkawwa: im so confused
ViktorTV: @hue88 your iq is to low to understand
OutsideGuidance: @TheStudentDoctor thanks! :)
michaelkawwa: did i just get r/woooshed
robotboy987: what the fuck
C4TFive: she didnt even try to pull her parachute, shes a goner
aar0npham: i guess they have to do it now 9000 m high
grahamstephan420: Why is your search engine google and not Yandex?
hue88: @ViktorTV Must be too much of an peasant to understand your jokes
DaMiniBeast: oof
chillguy269: But I want them to work, so I am going to slant my paper
god_damn: when will he be playing fortnite
yungtoad1: PunchTrees
PhosphoricAcid: LUL
kornez: LUL
yungtoad1: MrDestructoid
garydsmith1: duckduckgo?
DaMiniBeast: george, ily no homo
YouPowerRush: wot
bichid69: what's that green shit you're drinking?
Den_dp: lirikLUL
niclasrst: SirSword
Prinz_Sissi: LUL
hanycodes: why do you use jupyter ?
Newlax: prove it
yungtoad1: TheIlluminati
akotirous: The russian bot is getting really advanced
MrGwopz: @georgehotz yoo how did u jailbreak the ps3?
C4TFive: you can tell its real because its in a jupyter notebook
gal40: What do you mean by "dynamics"? The Physics branch?
yungtoad1: TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati
Tekrific: Yandex is only good for image searches, for other stuff it's crap
pedroriseo: are there some paper for drinking chlorine?
gorodinskiy: was the alpha go written in go?
Cutter1998: wait you're not a Russian bot? unsubbed
mattdougherty22: do you know Alex Guzey and his sleep studies contrary to Matthew walker?
tarunaditya: :p
nvmem2: @cutter1998 you’re not subbed to begin with lol
siriusblack189: like tetris ?
PhosphoricAcid: are you instagram famous yet ?
StapoTV: why is it so rare to see recurrent nets being used in RL?
garydsmith1: hey george whats your daily rotine?
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: George on Egirls Kreygasm id pay for that
wholesome_pepe: LUL
DelusionalDreams: we got u pal
norsesage6934: norsesage6934 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
ekalsuwaidi: squadW
gamester2665: youza cutie
WickedSidereaI: i want to lick your feet
robotboy987: you should sell bath water
nvmem2: I’ll sub to your only fans George
MrGwopz: how did you jailbreak the ps3 ive been a huge fan of u since 2011 i am just very curios on how you done that
fleischfleisch: heyhey
DaMiniBeast: George, I wanna learn to code, any tips??
InfiniteReddit: where do you go to browse papers?
sircuss: Your category is still Travel and Outdoors
Deno_____: george I wanna hack instagram any tips?
ogrockefeller: Father Hotz
isalhi: When openai was good? Doesn’t that imply they’re not anymore :)
DaMiniBeast: @deno_____ lol
calcmath: !uptime
CaptCalifornia: Ah yes, a premium Travel and Outdoors stream
ogrockefeller: Are you a Corona fan?
h6m9d: bleedPurple
CaptCalifornia: KEKW
DelusionalDreams: Whatś your opinion about RL applied in self driving cars?
CaptCalifornia: BloodTrail
Avelansh: Yo George Go or Rust?
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz what about transition states in a game like Dota 2? such complex environments?
phrixus_bro: Fitness and Literature
markydothh: Hey George!
funwayz: basic programming :)
DaMiniBeast: hEy GuYs, BuY mY oNlY fAnS
eldac_kno: What do you think about Winograd Schemas
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz what about transition states in a game like Dota 2? such complex environments? OpenAI did manage to give pros a run
axlebear: indoors
yungtoad1: SuperVinlin
symbiiote: @DelusionalDreams what is RL?
majorawpsome: dota 2 more like starcraft 2
grahamstephan420: You should make a brainfuck compiler in brainfuck?
bjorkthedog: Do you have a reading list? A list of some of your favourite books? @georgehotz
hanycodes: do you use perf ?
Newlax: you should make your own crypto for comma
ogrockefeller: Dad
urhentom: what's the scar on the face?
CaptCalifornia: CaptCalifornia subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 7 months! gang shit 📡
DaMiniBeast: George is underrated
CaptCalifornia: when we gonna get a cool sub icon 😔
mhammad123: ay man wasap
bichid69: BRO why don't we use AI to invent AI
xenozork: hi george
eldac_kno: have you read Art of Programming
Deno_____: @georgehotz Do you believe in the possibility of there being a god?
DaMiniBeast: hey George, I wanna learn to code, any tips??
eldac_kno: read art of programming
axlebear: axlebear subscribed with Twitch Prime.
b1nk: just code lol
Newlax: is this a cult if I need to pay?
arakis_djall: Didn't realize... watched your old rap video about a large gaming corporation. Wow.
sceptix1337: did the villin fold?
grahamstephan420: That was t0mcr00ze not George
bichid69: @DaMiniBeast buy a dildo
moshiko777: what are we doing today ?
harmanthebest1: @georgehotz series idea write chess like you did but using muzero
l1ttlemtman: did you watch the documentary ?
siriusblack189: tetris would be nice
leander_ms: Hello George
moshiko777: you gonna do a machine learning course in some point in the feautre ? you're really good at it
Deno_____: lolita express safest form of flight
toninoblack: go tetris
mrgh0st0: Snake ?
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: LUL
leander_ms: why did he switch to chromium?
Santiago_LHC: Tetris is not atari, except maybe a port
michelfugain69: hi do you think we have to be goot at maths to do machine learning ?
eldac_kno: have you read Art of Programming
le111an: Hi George, awesome channel
Digital_donger: yeah tetris was stolen from the soviets
natz42_: would be fun to reverse
Santiago_LHC: The story of the creation of Tetris is fascinating
sentoprak: @georgehotz hi, ım from turkey
PhosphoricAcid: their own mk ultra
siriusblack189: already i wrote nn for it
le111an: Pajetnikov was an author
fleischfleisch: alexy never earned a penny afaik
Avelansh: Beat by the Russians again
le111an: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_fQtxKmgJC8&t=1861s
Newlax: do a media share stream
elmixy: Privet vsem :)
sheveeee: what documentary? @harmanthebest1
vrv_exe: There’s a pretty good documentary on yt for Tetris. Lot of BS took place w that game
le111an: Privet :)
Deno_____: @georgehotz do you think believing in matrix is a more rational belief than atheism?
PhosphoricAcid: polybius*
eldac_kno: Джордж Хотц русский хакер, подтверждено
le111an: Ti tak dumaesh ?
vrv_exe: Russian government stole it from Russian indie developer
le111an: Я не уверен :)
eldac_kno: интересно он умеет читать по русски?
Digital_donger: tetris side effects WutFace
jakeglenn: my first time on stream
anuj_: what's up with the starlink satellites. why is USA put 9000 satellites in space
jrrbls: Google polybius
Santiago_LHC: There are hundreds of Tetris variants
le111an: Ну на крайний случай скопирует в транслейтор
mhammad123: george da fuq we doin today
majorawpsome: a computer might be able to beat the world champion of chess but there's no way they will able to beat a human at tetris
niclasrst: niclasrst subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! you're the best!!
eldac_kno: Джордж Хотц не умеет программировать
le111an: А что он хочет сделать ?
Avelansh: dev.to is new medium
le111an: Я поздно подключился
buddhm: Has anyone ever suggested for you to set up an eyetracker so its easier to follow your pathway?
Newlax: do a typing test stream
michelfugain69: That's deep
michelfugain69: Kappa
funwayz: some 5Head shit
hoffs: very deep
leander_ms: Deep bro
eldac_kno: не знаю, он читает бумаги про нейронки
PhosphoricAcid: so woke at such a young age, so brave
le111an: Да но последние все стрпимы он читает эти бумани по нейронке и что ?
Newlax: abstract art
le111an: Тензорфлоу заметил
le111an: А задача то какая ?
gyne: jargon PogChamp
eldac_kno: научит машины ездить
ralphielaurence: дисрапшн
Santiago_LHC: Disruption has become a product in of itself
Deno_____: @georgehotz can you do a stream ranting about religion and atheism and all that stuff
Ne0Zer0: rumsfeld was ahead of his time LUL
majorawpsome: or the boondocks
michelfugain69: wtf
eldac_kno: What do you think about Winograd Schemas?
michelfugain69: I don't understand I'm stupid
mritzing: wmds
mariusmafius: Clayton Christensen
RexRothx: Plato's statement on ignorance
ak0ya_: разобраться в мюзеро
raisedbyphantom: some bioshit
arakis_djall: but for 98% of companies disruption was having a website in 2005. It can be relative; if the definition has been taken over by those 98%
eldac_kno: он опять забросит это на полпути как всегда
fleischfleisch: biology is nice BibleThump
lambdaman0f: lambdaman0f subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! how is it going with backspace.ai?
Digital_donger: but a curved tv Kappa
le111an: Да ? Я особо за ним не слежу
grekler3: !uptime
le111an: помню его по Ultrasn0w
buddhm: corona virus known unkown?
fleischfleisch: do you do any sports georgehotz?
leander_ms: What is medium? Never heard of it LUL
mistertenko: What's the most disruptive thing since you were born?
twinkiee: hi, my main lang is not english and i do not fully understand your speech. For this, can you implement subtitle with python? Kappa
Santiago_LHC: It's precisely because it has become so overused of a notion, that if so many things are "disruptive", then nothing is.
roussillon: so only time tells us what ideas were disruptive ?
arakis_djall: today having "AI" for companies is disruption, even though it's just a bad linear regression implementation for their marketing data.
l1ttlemtman: l1ttlemtman subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 4 months, currently on a 2 month streak! Hello, have you seen this https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WXuK6gekU1Y about AlphaGo ?
eldac_kno: thoughts on Winograd Schemas?
TheKoreanZombi: What does this have to do with Manifest Destiny?
l1ttlemtman: it is really good
PhosphoricAcid: bean bag chairs
mgstrein: what do you mean when you say 'it is not zero to one' I think I missed the reference
l1ttlemtman: I enjoyed it a lot
Newlax: pog
be9ns: any haskell projects besides building a compiler?
hanycodes: are disruptive ideas important ?
Deno_____: @georgehotz what created the universe
Sycto: its a pretty good watch
l1ttlemtman: haha.
allrz: just do it
grekler3: D:
Avelansh: watch it with us
ArcherCreatlol: watch it on stream PogChamp
omarmiranda: is pretty good actually
allrz: come back later
YouPowerRush: h e h e
leander_ms: haha fine
PhosphoricAcid: ez content
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: DansGame i came here for some code
calcmath: he gave up go because of the AI
chillguy269: @l1ttlemtman way to go you made him leave
Newlax: on stream
arakis_djall: @mgstrein was a book by Peter Theil (sp), Zero to One.
darthbearjew666: Do you ever use Wolfram Language ?
funwayz: alphago — when we beat outdate stockfish on cpu :)
Digital_donger: okay later haha LUL
omarmiranda: hahaha ok !
Deno_____: @georgehotz DONT DO IT
aar0npham: lol
hoffs: lmao
emel_ryan: he's sabotaged us with the sub lol
aar0npham: later
maddyakhil: we can watch it together
omarmiranda: see ya later then
be9ns: fucking goat
TheKoreanZombi: Later!
aPosterior: that smirk tho
Santiago_LHC: GUYS, this is your fault!
allrz: do it
sinisa_koscec: do it, its nice
Newlax: :(
jsnfly: damn
zooooodiac: looooooool
allrz: DO IT
sobol55: please no
leander_ms: That is one of the best things ever LUL
mrhdr: Jebaited
kornez: Jebaited
mrgh0st0: yeyy
Den_dp: so how was it
maddyakhil: back LUL
Santiago_LHC: Was it GOOD?
Ne0Zer0: LUL\
Ne0Zer0: LUL
kornez: HOW IT WAS PogChamp
maddyakhil: was the movie good LUL
Digital_donger: Jebaited
a_ato: zoraoCOFFEE
Digital_donger: maybe he watched it at 50x speed
johnwill86: yoyoyo!
hurzg: was alphastar also done with muzero?
le111an: What was the result of the coronavirus stream? I didn't watch it fully
LiveCustoms: yooo. geoooo
l1ttlemtman: yo
luspr: Using Tensorflow instead of PyTorch ? DansGame
l1ttlemtman: what was wrong with the movie
l1ttlemtman: i dont remember it being so short
le111an: THX !
Santiago_LHC: Flu is pretty scary
norB88: Whats ur paper reading methodology? Are you usually searching for something? Or what parts are you especially paying. attention to etc?
THX1342: hi @le111an
sceptix1337: what about the villin?
le111an: hi thx1342
Den_dp: F
Den_dp: reiraF
luspr: The lockdowns are terrible. Fortunately, the discours changes towards opening. Here in Europe many countries are already opening uo
god_damn: need shkreli bro
l1ttlemtman: germany keeps making wrong decisions
asaalgk: flu has an IFR of 0.04%, covid has it between 0.2-1%.. how is that a a 3x? the 0.1% flu statistic that has been circulating is the CFR which is a meaningless stat
l1ttlemtman: and opening up
sircuss: what happened to watching the Alphago movie?
mhammad123: here in the uae they are opening up malls again
mrgh0st0: we can inject some disinfectant into people
osuiw: is that a broom
Penguino138: @georgehotz whats the meditation app you used in previous vids?
Lizardan: Tensor Flow KEKW
raystriker98: he's back!
YouPowerRush: wot
5punnr1ng: Hi Gehot I want a child from u😍
re1mond: hi, mr.robot!
re1mond: !uptime
Lizardan: he doesn't sell children
garydsmith1: !uptime
THX1342: i haven't taken a deep dive but as far as I went there have been studies during this and previous pandemics showing the effectiveness of lockdowns.. don't know where the controversy is
Ne0Zer0: Lizardan LUL
osuiw: @5punnr1ng i am selling some around the corner
calcmath: can you increase font size of code?
5punnr1ng: How much
5punnr1ng: For one?
hayewood: sup george
osuiw: @5punnr1ng 10$/kg
ralphielaurence: what's he doing?
Penguino138: @ralphielaurence looks like some physics programming
osuiw: @ralphielaurence some stuff here and there
ralphielaurence: what's this nn?
5punnr1ng: @osuiw i‘ll take your youngest one!
Penguino138: @georgehotz what is the meditation app you use?
osuiw: @5punnr1ng no
l1ttlemtman: i dont understand why deepmind puts so much effort into reinforcement learning. google learned from nlp that too much compute breaks research, deepmind is close to doing so
OttoCavalry: What is he doin?
JAKWAI: could u do a chaos pendulum with this?
5punnr1ng: Why?
Santiago_LHC: @Penguino138 Headspace
osuiw: the one with the orange lad @Santiago_LHC ?
AThousandHours: got bored of movie? LUL
dontbeameme: Pablos Holman your idol?
tinkerzwhothe_t: hey teach me html
Relic69: hi george, do you have a recommend way to get into hacking and stuff?
Penguino138: It's now a great day that George is back streaming
ancientchineseelder: @Relic69 read hacking: the art of exploitation
l1ttlemtman: show all your papers
samosasauce8: What's your favorite text editor?
THX1342: watch Hackers
Santiago_LHC: People, enough with the off topic questions
Relic69: @ancientchineseelder ty, will check it out
Kyoto_o: stop telling me what to do @Santiago_LHC
Santiago_LHC: Make me
god_damn: @Santiago_LHC stop telling Kyoto_o what to do
dontbeameme: From someone like you I would expect more amazon free trial primes
Santiago_LHC: Okay, I will listen to you
Kyoto_o: @god_damn: @Santiago_LHC stop telling Kyoto_o what to do
phrixus_bro: balanced ez
amaranthion1991: Pog
SurfCat: Ey, Goerge online on this lovely day. Very nice, glad you are online hope all is well FeelsGoodMan 👍
JAKWAI: can someone explain me what MuZero is?
Santiago_LHC: Google it?
ShredderSherlock: is that animation of the progress bar part of the jupyter notebook or the code?
l1ttlemtman: how can this be so fast on a cpu ?
calcmath: its from the code
ShredderSherlock: ty @calcmath
JAKWAI: ok got it somehow ty :D
Beraton: !uptime
nitrixen: @shreddersherlock Trivial to do with \r to bring the cursor at the start of the line and write over it.
Ne0Zer0: LUL
ShredderSherlock: what?
god_damn: FeelsGoodMan neat
BetaMalePaypig: <3
11plus4thinking: PogChamp HES STREAMING
nitrixen: @shreddersherlock When you print the \r character, you get to overwrite your current line.
ido_nvidia: do you use dqn?
cktreon: When are u going to da a hacking stream?
calcmath: look up tqdm python package to mae your own progress bars in code
Penguino138: Penguino138 is continuing the Gift Sub they got from aar0npham!
vlsbrd: what happened to alphago?
amaranthion1991: "whitecap hacking"
Penguino138: @georgehotz thanks for all you do! Your streams are great and I always play them in the background while working
garydsmith1: can we get another python tut?
chairman_Z: @georgehotz do u ever drink hot tea...
DiiCE3: weve seen some bug bounties in our day
dontbeameme: Lolool
sceptix1337: black hoodie hacking
ralphielaurence: that's a way to look at it..
OttoCavalry: kevin mitnick xd
dontbeameme: All marketing is hacking/manipulation
THX1342: the latest infosec twitter hashtag is #whatrealhackerlooklike or some shot.
amaranthion1991: @georgehotz Did you ever hear about Dan DeFelipe hacker dude ?
THX1342: pathetic
11plus4thinking: LUL
Farafire: Have you learned AI on your own?
Penguino138: @georgehotz I look forward to continuing being a loyal subscriber! Keep up the great streams!
Greaser_1: :-)
chairman_Z: what does rm mean?
Den_dp: remove
garydsmith1: re name?
garydsmith1: oh
THX1342: only real "famous" hacker right now is phinneas phisher
chairman_Z: @Den_dp thank you friend
emel_ryan: it's how you delete in command line
calcmath: does rm 0 out every bit on the HD, is that why it makes so much noise?
famousdex: 5Head
wssheldo: did u end up folding the protein?
calcmath: i thought it just deallocated the files
fillmyvoid: wow lmao
god_damn: we do not forgive B)
dontbeameme: When views are botted, downloads botted, what is real?
Penguino138: What kind of tea you drinking on @georgehotz
calcmath: then why does it make noise?
Avelansh: thats how i feel when i listen to todays rap/hip-hop
THX1342: vulnerabilities now are named with emoji....
mistertenko: It's funny, and I'm tired of pretending it's not
hayewood: an nymnO n nymnO my nymnO us
Bazingaka: alias rm='stealthrm'
garydsmith1: can we get a python tutorial? merge sort this time?
THX1342: ArgieB8 🔫
bill1929: trust me cuz
nitrixen: This is why we made SSDs.
nitrixen: Rebalancing the forces.
s4j0k5: is comma planning to port some features to an app
sceptix1337: inb4 george is an ancap
calcmath: government has monopoly on violence
DelusionalDreams: Whereś a good place to get started with comma?
Penguino138: So true, govt just changes teh name of their mafia-esque activities
Tekrific: both play on trust too
dontbeameme: Lolollolol
fillmyvoid: I don't know if I'm *that* anti government
THX1342: https://unicornriot.ninja/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/hackback-announce-text.txt
funwayz: libertarian hotz monkaS
dontbeameme: MK ultra
gamester2665: There was a network error. Please try again. (Error #2000)
Kreunt: eviscerate the proletariat
dontbeameme: People need balance of fair and unfair
Penguino138: Roooon Pauul
OttoCavalry: Ancap memes are the best
ShredderSherlock: oh lord
Tekrific: changes should be selected for actual changes we want to keep in the future
MrGwopz: do you think freecodecamp is a good site to learn coding?
hayewood: gold KKona
zrman331: In any way, civilzation needs a pyramidical structure of power
phrixus_bro: going up baybeee
Snowlav: what would you call genuine good people, and do you think there's many left of those?
boxofninjas: wonder if the price of track pants have gone up
dontbeameme: Government keeps gold prices stable like BTC
anguscupcake: what if u write a government AI
THX1342: that's called HFT @anguscupcake
Penguino138: I'm glad we're all finally moving past COVID news and moving onto new topics
phrixus_bro: karenocracy
THX1342: and it is deployed
calcmath: the economy is the first artificial intelligence humans created, its decentralized and out of our control
dontbeameme: Everyone has agenda
Iliftmymousealot: wow i am late to the party
Tekrific: boomers are a meat mountain that needs to be decomposed
hiredguns: !uptime
Iliftmymousealot: george give us that cure
Iliftmymousealot: we need the cure
Iliftmymousealot: !!!
numinousloop: excluding the self-driving car space, who doing the coolest work to build the infrastructure of the future
dontbeameme: what is this carona virus situation? More people die from car accidents?
Penguino138: @georgehotz do you ever plan trying to fold proteins again or other biochem programming?
numinousloop: who do you think is doing*
shiftpgdn: shiftpgdn subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months!
norB88: https://www.amazon.com/Way-Men-Jack-Donovan/dp/0985452307
hiredguns: scarry part is even asymptotic ppl have lasting lung damages
Iliftmymousealot: recommenders are cool aswell
MrGwopz: what are you coding right now?
hiredguns: there are couple of divers had covid19 asymptotic and won't be able to dive again
shipteri: poulChat poulChat
anguscupcake: there's probably some lung herb in ancient chinese medicine that fixes it
sceptix1337: who names their variables v_0k
zrman331: @hiredguns you got any info on that? Im genuinely interested since i havent found good info on stuff like this
mariusmafius: @sceptix1337 mathematicians
Penguino138: @anguscupcake Ask Qin Shi Huang, he was an old Chinese Emperor that drank mercury to live forever :p
sceptix1337: they eat tiger dicks for potency in chinese medicine
norB88: @Iliftmymousealot reccomenders are cool!
Iliftmymousealot: these biohackers
anguscupcake: maybe the ones that survived past 210 BC ;)
prostate_v: just got here, what're we doing?
enton29: geo say porco dio
imshaez: imshaez subscribed with Twitch Prime.
DelusionalDreams: What about End to End models for self driving cars?
Penguino138: His tomb is protected by the terracotta statues and is theorised to contain rivers of mercury
gorgoleon89: Can you code a hack for me to get a girlfriend?
shiftpgdn: all of my variable names are the letter a in various lengths, like a aa aaa aaaa
Joselinis: True
reformed_human: u just have to search harder
shipteri: @gorgoleon89 come on,finding girls is easier that to write hello world in c
Penguino138: More info makes it harder to search, but when all you find is BS it makes it real easy
01_pollux: @georgehotz did you read wolframs blog?
fillmyvoid: when did MuZero come out?
calcmath: can you increase font size of paper as wel, so we can read along
dontbeameme: But they learning how to make people believe the lies, like a BETA
Avelansh: you just have to develop the ability to think critically and not take everything you hear at face value
01_pollux: new model coupling quantum mechanics and theory of relativity. I love it @georgehotz
ferric: !school
CaptCalifornia: wait did you watch the alphago movie
gorgoleon89: @shipteri teach me master.
Iliftmymousealot: getting really philosophical here, oof
ferric: Did you study Computer Science at college/uni or self-taught?
garydsmith1: can we get a python tuts? merge sort this time?
norB88: https://theportal.news - Trying to make a new way to consume news. Separate facts from opinion and emotional manipulation.
pelegogrosso: How intelligent is geo? and what he is doing?
dontbeameme: They made skinny jeans popular
dontbeameme: Mind control
shipteri: @gorgoleon89 just speak to every girl you like.There is no way that at least one wont like you
dontbeameme: True true
Iliftmymousealot: @pelegogrosso geohot has 400 iq. I read it on the internet.
Snowlav: what's the mistake? veiThinking
mistertenko: What do you think about Sweden strategy?
anguscupcake: the mistake of not being taiwan
Penguino138: That's gonna be a lot of apologising if anyone ever decided to for COVID
gorgoleon89: @shipteri thank you for these wise words sensei.
garydsmith1: can we get python tut? merge sort this timr?
Ne0Zer0: oil? what oil? bxtch you cooking?
Rekkeno: "I take no responsibility"
YouPowerRush: yee
calcmath: dont they say that if we acted ontime for coronavirus its going to look like we made a mistake and overreacted
mhammad123: Do u think that corona virus is man made?
anguscupcake: no because you would see underdeveloped countries get swarmed
pelegogrosso: why we ask for him to do a iq test?
shipteri: @gorgoleon89 body language is very useful too.
pelegogrosso: dont
fizziblytwitching: I'd rather look like a mistake and people not die than people die because someone is worried about how it will look
Santiago_LHC: He argues that the lockdowns are a mistake. But without them, you get completely saturated health care systems, lack of essential supplies, and people dying that shouldn't be dying. So I don't understand the logic.
gorgoleon89: @shipteri touching an shit right?
bottonresult: @anguscupcake like equador?
r00tkey: !uptime
gorgoleon89: @georgehotz gaming stream when?
garydsmith1: 30mins
b2kemann: Still not using Jupiter lab George?
MrGwopz: what is he coding?
r00tkey: What am in missing?
janpoonthong: Can you zoom in I can't see your code
bottonresult: he could zoom in
calcmath: I dont understand his logic either
garydsmith1: :(
calcmath: he is coding an RL agent to balance a stick
r00tkey: hmm
akrwp: Connection lost?
gorgoleon89: anyone here in chat that can actually code? :D
bottonresult: me
calcmath: i can ..
r00tkey: yep
ferric: i can but im very new, I know java and learning python rn
mariusmafius: o_0
djguslim1337swe: we solvning P vs NP?
anguscupcake: been coding for a decade
gorgoleon89: @anguscupcake ok boomer
StapoTV: wait, isnt RL what commaai would use for driving?
Iliftmymousealot: @gorgeleon89 what do you mean by "know how to code?" What qualifies someone to know how to code? A diploma?
anguscupcake: dunno math though
god_damn: @anguscupcake same bro i can code but im closer to braindead than not
shipteri: @gorgoleon89 you can touch but only at specific body parts like elbow waist.It depends on you well you know the girl.
calcmath: yes startover plz
bottonresult: ZOOM IN
gorgoleon89: @shipteri i struggle at openers though
calcmath: also zoom plz
gorgoleon89: not goot at small talk
fillmyvoid: yep
choppingitoff: Explain the imports please
SofiaLouise: what happend with the movie?
skut1212: hey george! What resources would you recommend to programmers on learning AI?
sceptix1337: write tf from scratch
DelusionalDreams: where can i get started with comma?
MrGwopz: what are you coding?
garydsmith1: geo writes tf from scrath in one night
gorgoleon89: @georgehotz please code an AGI on stream and take over the world
alexlucas__: alexlucas__ subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
calcmath: coding an RL agent to balance a stick
shipteri: @gorgoleon89 yee i feel you , you can go at a place that dont know you and speak free so you can train it.But you must not fall whatever they tell you.Some bitches are hard
bottonresult: i
OutsideGuidance: How do you develop this level of understanding in everything? I seem to forget a lot of things with time :(
Penguino138: Does anyone know the alt code for mu off the top of their head?
kayoeyumisaolegais: !uptime
gorgoleon89: @georgehotz who is your favorite waifu?
Santiago_LHC: @OutsideGuidance motivation, genuine interest
kayoeyumisaolegais: how long is george streaming?
z00fle: @georgehotz is advertising a scam?
garydsmith1: 30 mins
Izimoney92100: !uptime
lovewave_: do you think quantum computing is any useful for current algorithms as of right now? @georgehotz
rkxbz: can someone explain geohotz's workflow (vim + tmux) that he talked about in Lex Fridman podcast?
calcmath: tiny neural netowrk
Penguino138: Yessir neural nets
Iliftmymousealot: not really to be honest
numinousloop: for sure, this is great
calcmath: i am following
garydsmith1: no one following
toninoblack: following
routerkicker: Simple stuff
lanyxqt2: i just got here
chaprio1: no, but it looks cool man
god_damn: nah i dont know shit
shipteri: @gorgoleon89 you can find some ready crosstalk just for fun.After that you have to tell whatever you feel.If he has super ass,tell her something funny about it. Some will like it,other will not xD
c0lemak: idk what's going on
garydsmith1: we need python tuts merge sort
DelusionalDreams: how can i get started with comma?
Santiago_LHC: I'm reading the MuZero paper while I hear you
hiredguns: trying to keep stick upright?
routerkicker: stop assuming everyone's an idiot george
michaelkawwa: for real
pyentropy: @georgehotz opinion on life homochirality? (L aminoacids, R sugars)
z00fle: yay
rkxbz: i cant understand nothing, but it is very interesting
Penguino138: dont worry @georgehotz many of us here follow and find it very stimulating
bichid69: oh ur back!
gorgoleon89: @shipteri training makes a master
r00tkey: @gorgoleon89 Man don't compare yourself with others, George is doing it for several years and you might have just started.
DelusionalDreams: this isn rocket science bruh
Iliftmymousealot: yeah but how do you filter all these people out through all the noise, the people which actually contribute something valuable to the stream
bichid69: you seen the whole movie?
Iliftmymousealot: i dont
plazmacsgo: you slit it in the middle
symbiiote: roses are red, violets are blue, George Hotz better than Elon Musk.
shipteri: @gorgoleon89 yeah thats why if you are very shy,just go to a place that you will not ever go again and speak free xd
bufferovrflw: @georgehotz long time no see, what happened to the corona stream?
hiredguns: was it splitting random or half?
Ne0Zer0: lip lol
ogsixaxis: good morning <3
gorgoleon89: @r00tkey i am learning python this shit is too advanced for me to understand
Pitzthistlewits: 😬
ogsixaxis: bruh this is basic python
DelusionalDreams: i would rather do a quicksort haha
plazmacsgo: @ogsixaxis but merge sort is not that basic
plazmacsgo: you know..
elmixy: PogChamp
gorgoleon89: i am 2 months in my dude
guccibruf: PogChamp
Iliftmymousealot: the great coof
gal40: Merge sort is absolutely basic...
funwayz: from monte carlo tree search to mergesort real quick Kappa
garydsmith1: how are you atually doing it?
iifiryth5429: Can you not just do it with recursion? its much easier too
Digital_donger: PogChamp
z00fle: beauty
tommy_clash: Don't cough
Izimoney92100: PogChamp PogChamp
dinxpoy: my internet isn't even good enough for 1080p60 so I can't read shit Kappa 🔫
plazmacsgo: @gal40 for beginners its not
bottonresult: zoom in the screen
anguscupcake: just get a 5k monitor broo
plazmacsgo: you got to understand that for ppl who started learning a week ago merge sort is not basic
gal40: @plazmacsgo What do you define as beginner? You learn mergesort in intro to compsci course...
m0etaz: what are we implementing today
Izimoney92100: @m0etaz we solving N NP
plazmacsgo: @gal40 like someone who started learning a week ago
Iliftmymousealot: literally cant decipher any letter from that paper. it's all blurry. Oof #Resolution=bad
m0etaz: cool, thanks
ibizi77: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1911.08265.pdf
plazmacsgo: and tbh I didn't even know any sorts for my first year of programming
plazmacsgo: I focused on making games and learning object oriented and doing some basic machine learning projects
calcmath: zoom the paper
Iliftmymousealot: thanks @ibizi77
gal40: @plazmacsgo That's not beginner, that's someone who heard about programming lol.
garydsmith1: mechine learning without sorts?
anguscupcake: you can go your entire career without knowing algorithms. just depends on what u fo
bufferovrflw: What happened to the Corona stream? @georgehotz
m0etaz: @ibizi77 @izimoney92100 thanks !
plazmacsgo: @gal40 than whats a beginner in your defenition
ibizi77: you're welcome!!
calcmath: he doesnt have enough compute for protein folding
Iliftmymousealot: @bufferovrflw the protein didn't fold
chuck_person: the logos are cool in that shot
hiredguns: amricanized brit pop
ogsixaxis: george folded on the coronavirus stream instead of the protein ;/
Iliftmymousealot: proteinfolding = numerical expensive
hiredguns: oasis for east coast
bichid69: =(
DelusionalDreams: Why arent you using LISP the real ai language? lmao
gal40: @plazmacsgo I would argue that a beginner is someone who has a grasp on basic concepts, such as sorts.
dinxpoy: did he develop the corona vaccine? is it on github? jk dont ban me pls
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: BBoomer music LULW
plazmacsgo: @gal40 I see
Atlas03: quarantine haircut SeemsGood
god_damn: @dinxpoy if it gets any worse he'll intervene, its on his backburner for now
11plus4thinking: WutFace
dinxpoy: @god_damn hope he saves us all 🙏
michaelkawwa: he really jus vibin
sceptix1337: naive_search(o_O)
Avelansh: quite the interesting music taste
WillGreen98: heyo :)
michaelkawwa: very intresring indeed
IIrLiChT: he vibin tho
gal40: @plazmacsgo Maybe it's about baseline. If you look at it from a purely "coding" perspective, maybe someone who knows how to code could not know sorting, but I think a programmer is also about knowing compsci concepts.
JjohnConstantine: Kappa
dinxpoy: song recorded with the mic of a nokia 3310 5Head
mistertenko: What kind of protomusic is this
cybergenik: George, have you heard of gamozo? hes a streamer thats building a Hypervisor in Rust from scratch. He's gonna use it for fuzzing, its supposed to be able to spin up VMs and kill them 3million times a second per core. its crazy he's crazy good.
Vistor1001: i wouldnt be able to concentrate with this music
Transferer: very interesting personalities
dgkng0d: hello everyone how are you today
bichid69: this stream sucks bro
JigglyGirls: bakedONE / hullo
bichid69: pls entertain us
wafflesan: cool idea
calcmath: ZOOM plz
plazmacsgo: @gal40 definitely! I agree that knowing theory is really important. That what I have been focusing on for the past couple month. But its kinda hard to know which concepts are important when self studing
b2kemann: there are 100 of courses online
Iliftmymousealot: imo the real metaskill a programmer needs is that he can read and knows how to use a search engine, like google, really efficiently. this is how you get good
gal40: @georgehotz Could you explain what difference exploring multiple steps makes if you only take the first action?
michaelkawwa: could someone explain to me what he's doing.
IIrLiChT: ai i think
plazmacsgo: @Iliftmymousealot ye LOL
fabriziobertoglio: please link to the document
calcmath: balancing an inverted pendulum
calcmath: RL agent for doing that
michaelkawwa: ohh cartpole
plazmacsgo: @michaelkawwa I think he is doing a RL agent
zenderbeg: isn't this a game?
AThousandHours: is the notebook on the same computer as you stream?
apetiss: Hi, late to the party. What is he doing with the MuZero algorithm?
Waldoqq: Waldoqq subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 4 months, currently on a 2 month streak! Wheres the covid streams
plazmacsgo: @apetiss cartpole
calcmath: is h the value function?
chrisinajar: hey george o/
Iliftmymousealot: @plazmacsgo I am not trolling btw... it sounds obvious but many people thin´k they know those things but really they don't including me I am really bad at it
jagger_rsw: jagger_rsw subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months!
bichid69: @apetiss your mama
plazmacsgo: ye ik
mero_1181: Hey George, what’s the name of the book you are referencing?
symbiiote: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1911.08265.pdf
luggy_b0i: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1911.08265.pdf
mero_1181: Thanks!
fatpanda168: spooky links
plazmacsgo: its really important to know how to google and comprehend what ppl write on the internet
davidgames68: @Transferer resttOk
fatpanda168: dont click those links bois
Transferer: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
gal40: @fatpanda168 It's the link to the paper george is referencing.
jagger_rsw: are we taking over the world with python again?
b2kemann: don't you think it's pain to implement papers with python, when it's so slow... I think swift will take over in the future, when s4tf gets popular
JigglyGirls: click all the links baked2head
ogsixaxis: best way to learn python is to start making project and look up stuff u get stuck on
luggy_b0i: @fatpanda168 google arxiv.org and see what it's about.
bichid69: @fatpanda168 why not bro
plazmacsgo: @b2kemann that might happen
cengea: sup
gal40: Could you explain what difference exploring multiple steps makes if you only take the first action?
bichid69: im blind bro, cant see difference
fatpanda168: looked kind of fishy but ok
erichtp: how was the movie
fatpanda168: have you ever thought about creating some sort of anti-cheat?
luggy_b0i: It's a scholarly article distribution site.
bichid69: bro im blind bro
jagger_rsw: what's the percentage of your team that willingly relocated to san diego? (that's where comma.ai currently is?)
mero_1181: @gal40 You know the path of the future states
Santiago_LHC: Chess tactics
SparksCx: i would say so. why not.
bichid69: yeah but im blind bro
p4r4774x: hii
SparksCx: anti game cheat
SparksCx: like aimbot
calcmath: can you explain the output of your search fn so i can follow
sceptix1337: eat the ice
funwayz: python fast LUL
b2kemann: that may happen, but wift is fast and hackable
Bazingaka: numba ftw
fatpanda168: yeah but you can sell it for a lot of money
JVictorVO: What about creating cheats?
m0etaz: cython ResidentSleeper
Skurt2k: true KEKW
bichid69: numba sucks bro
fatpanda168: creating cheats WeirdChamp
jagger_rsw: mens rea (re comma.ai), put rules in the stream title :)
robby0313: The vanguard ant-cheat needs ring 0 privs
JVictorVO: @fatpanda168 its funny actually lol
sceptix1337: ring -2 is where its at fam
iiiiiiillllliiiill: has he cured corona yet
fatpanda168: honestly whoever makes a good anticheat system will make an ungodly amount of money
Imuhnent: @georgehotz do you remember any CTF challenges from your past?
bichid69: @iiiiiiillllliiiill nah he too dumb
robby0313: Ring -3 is where the government is watching my camera
Waldoqq: Does anyone remember that funny song from one of George's covid streams that was talking about consumerism?
Waldoqq: it was on youtube and it was super old
Iliftmymousealot: george I don't mind being abused as some thinking agent to help you to be more productive. But what does grind my gears is that our communication mechanism is critically broken. There has to be a way to filter out the comments which are relevant so you can actually see them. Unless you do these streams for pure enjoyment and that case ignore what I just typed for 2 minutes.
Tuhafadam: hey you are back I was miss u.
god_damn: @Waldoqq 50cent - window shopper
robonhansonem: What is he building?
foti_kasparov: We need a quantum computers stream
Digital_donger: wicked PogChamp
Waldoqq: lmao @god_damn def not him
chairman_Z: wtaf i've been binging on the Wicked soundtrack the past few days lmao
Waldoqq: it was some white guys no one had ever heard of
hiredguns: squarepusher - terminal slam
fatpanda168: will you dab for 500 bits
bichid69: @iliftmymousealot lol he ain't gonna read that shit
sceptix1337: george out here listening to frozen soundtrack
Iliftmymousealot: ye and thats the whole point
FargioFarmani: Whats the square root of log 2 ?
fatpanda168: tldr pls
GoTo3: @fatpanda168, its 2020 dude knock it off
bichid69: @fatpanda168 y u such a n00b
fatpanda168: D:
Ne0Zer0: LUL
csrf_player: song name pls
fatpanda168: the front bottoms - more than
sceptix1337: the wizard and i
fatpanda168: idk that should be enough to find it
DrRobotvinnik: I’ve waited months for the RL & Wizard strim cbrahGood @georgehotz
fatpanda168: oh im dumb lol
csrf_player: @sceptix1337 tnx
norB88: wizard and i has weird sexual overtones
norB88: :D
b2kemann: notebooks are addicting
FargioFarmani: Yasser
aloexai: gg
DrRobotvinnik: @fargiofarmani SeemsGod
foti_kasparov: @FargioFarmani Wrong stream go on Chessbrah
SiNNER_ontwitch: This music is a slow punch in the face
SiNNER_ontwitch: why do you hate me
cheesemanuchiha: is george still working on the virus or is this something different
DrRobotvinnik: cbrahGiraffe
fizziblytwitching: So wat's the point of MuZero?
aloexai: George whats up
fatpanda168: ok bois what is the best language to learn that will not be obsolete in a couple of years
aloexai: George sup
sceptix1337: rust
b2kemann: we need some lorde george
airinspiration_: python
b2kemann: or lana del ray
DrRobotvinnik: Jazz hands from George SeemsGood
inDOObitablee: English
WillGreen98: @fatpanda168 go?
aloexai: geohot sup
norB88: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TVcLIfSC4OE
fatpanda168: i have read that python is slow tho
robonhansonem: Something to do with MuZero. Not sure what exactly. Got here late.
aloexai: George wassap
alphagainzzz: guys, i just got admitted to ucsd!
DrRobotvinnik: Cartpole @robonhansonem
fatpanda168: @alphagainzzz noice
airinspiration_: @alphagainzzz gratzzz
sceptix1337: the env.state and i
cheesemanuchiha: thanks robon
dontbeameme: What’s your warzone k.d
alphagainzzz: thanks :)
logi6000: yo how are you all doing today
FargioFarmani: George, a new chessbrah?
airinspiration_: @alphagainzzz which major?
sceptix1337: whats george's lichess elo
logi6000: what are we doin today
fatpanda168: who needs debug tools when you can just print
alphagainzzz: mathematics-computer science @airinspiration_
Iliftmymousealot: incase there is someone who is remotely affiliated with george in the chat and reading this, Even if you are the commaaiarchive guy, can you just tell george to improve the way his audience can communicate with us. That would be cool. No hate I respect you commaaiarchive guy.
forkdb: Yalooo
airinspiration_: nicee
DrRobotvinnik: who needs a warzone k.d. If you have an AlphaZero ArgieB8
norB88: norB88 is gifting 3 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 13 in the channel!
norB88: norB88 gifted a Tier 1 sub to b2kemann!
norB88: norB88 gifted a Tier 1 sub to nizero!
norB88: norB88 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Tuhafadam!
dontbeameme: I am alpha zero
fatpanda168: PogChamp
b2kemann: @norB88 Thanks for the gift sub!
DelusionalDreams: how ca i gte started with comma?
DrRobotvinnik: buy a car @delusionaldreams
jesusthenew: hi
forkdb: How can you learn so much... still cannot understand
SiNNER_ontwitch: We dont actually do anything on this stream. Its about problem solving and learning strategies. Which is awesome.
b2kemann: omg am i a sub now
grekler3: wtf is muzero
byte_baron: @SiNNER_ontwitch really?
logi6000: how am i a sub
anguscupcake: it's a lot easier to learn stuff if u don't work 9-5
DrRobotvinnik: reinforcement learning @grekler3
b2kemann: i have finally become something in my life
Iliftmymousealot: commaiarchive guy where are you at?
alphagainzzz: @SiNNER_ontwitch literally the best part
Iliftmymousealot: manifest yourself
DelusionalDreams: OK @DrRobotvinnik such a great advice
logi6000: whats he doin
dontbeameme: On scale 1-10 how Italian is George
hiredguns: trying to keep his stick upright
byte_baron: @dontbeameme pasta/10
fatpanda168: Cheer1000
DrRobotvinnik: SeemsGood @delusionaldreams
hiredguns: muzero doesnt cooperate tho
mrhdr: 1000 bitcoins PogChamp
fizziblytwitching: What does it mean by policy?
fatpanda168: lol wtf
byte_baron: is this fun?
fizziblytwitching: Is that the set of rules is it learning?
calcmath: policy tells oyu what action to take given the state
byte_baron: are you actually having fun right now, im curious
fatpanda168: someone posted the paper before not sure if they are still here
calcmath: policy is what you want to learn
DelusionalDreams: @fizziblytwitching https://stackoverflow.com/questions/46260775/what-is-a-policy-in-reinforcement-learning
SiNNER_ontwitch: @byte_baron I like to watch how he researches and attacks a subject he does not know about. It makes me feel less crazy.
sceptix1337: do 1/state
mero_1181: He’s learning for sure! Some may find it fun
fizziblytwitching: Thanks @DelusionalDreams
ceo_of_anxiety: hey
ceo_of_anxiety: print hello world
hiredguns: value should increase with minimum action
anguscupcake: learning is more fun that most video games
fizziblytwitching: Ok so a set of actions to acheive a result
byte_baron: @anguscupcake you think?
jontowtruck: surprised he doesn't use the vim keymaps in jupyter nb
airinspiration_: @anguscupcake not funnier than battlefield 4
calcmath: policy is function from state space to action space
ceo_of_anxiety: @anguscupcake you're not good at them
gal40: @fizziblytwitching More like a way to map a state to an action
airinspiration_: LUL
anguscupcake: bf4 is too much like cod tbh
hiredguns: +1 stop -1
byte_baron: i feel like the end product of the learning process is a way better feeling than anything you'll get from gaming but for me the learning process can be quite dry (depending on what im learning)
airinspiration_: i cant handle what you said, im out
byte_baron: and im generally a procrastinator
anguscupcake: it is. when you finish a project you've actually done something. when you finish playing video games you just wasted 4 hours
fizziblytwitching: @byte_baron but you could class gaming as learning
Iliftmymousealot: the thing about gaming is that it is designed to be fun. Where as aquiring a skills is not.
Iliftmymousealot: dopamine detox inc.
eldac_kno: is it ok to ask him slightly offtopic questions?
fizziblytwitching: Just that you're not going to really grow intellectually form gaming
fizziblytwitching: from*
byte_baron: @fizziblytwitching right but i think we all know we're going to get way more from learning stuff like programming/maths/ML than playing runescape or something
byte_baron: i think it's about moderation
norB88: @SiNNER_ontwitch yeah learning how to learn type of thing.
byte_baron: do something hard (learning) > reward self with a game
Santiago_LHC: @eldac_kno no
calcmath: gamin simulates an ideal form of learning and exploring
robonhansonem: Gaming provides all the feelings associated with accomplishment without the accomplishment. Considered dangerous.
byte_baron: ^
anguscupcake: @robonhansonem exactly
Paw_4: gaming is like working out, you don't learn anything but you gains skills and capabilities
cheesemanuchiha: is this inverted pendulum
calcmath: yes it is
anguscupcake: lol
grekler3: some of this chat = Pepega
cheesemanuchiha: thanks calc
mackinonit: you gain skill...??
DelusionalDreams: watching someone doing might achive the same result @robonhansonem
SiNNER_ontwitch: @byte_baron Im also a procrastinator. I try to follow what im passionate about and keep many irons in the fire. I bore easily. If I create multiple irons in the fire, an opportunity or breakthrough is much more likely.
eldac_kno: only delusional people think gaming helps you grow intellectually
sceptix1337: you learn to farm lol
mackinonit: what are the valuable skills you gain from basketball?
Ne0Zer0: starcraft 2 might teach you valuable skills
Santiago_LHC: So.... I'm not a farmer by playing Farmville?
anguscupcake: basketball is good cardio at least
logi6000: says this while im playing madden
grekler3: you just coping and wasting time LUL
dr_set: you learn resource allocation and managment?
xeeton: do you gain an intuition about newtonian physics playing KSP?
WEEEEEEEELL_ITS_KNOCC_OUT: WutFace
forkdb: How do you learn so fast?
Penguino138: @georgehotz what kind of tea?
foti_kasparov: I can learn how farming works so I can build my own weed farm
fizziblytwitching: No it's not, you do have to learn to play a game, so by definition you're learning.
mackinonit: they did that with formula 1
eldac_kno: i know it's slightly offtopic, but what do you think abot Winograd Schemas?
ogsixaxis: i learned to be a gangster from gta
sceptix1337: ksp is dope
anguscupcake: VR is the ultimate for learning to play paintball
vybster: There's an argument to be made for fun though
Ne0Zer0: racing games make it easier to practice driving
gal40: @fizziblytwitching Arguing about semantics is a waste of time.
Imuhnent: What's fun?
Iliftmymousealot: fun is a fake concept
byte_baron: @vybster right, i don't think all fun should be eradicated from your life, i think it's about a healthy balance
bravetraveller: The Witness was actually fun figuring out various patterns, recommended as a puzzle game anyway
fizziblytwitching: Except in the context
vybster: Games can be fun, even though there's no "valuable skills" to be learned
THX1342: deus ex teaches you to be woke
eldac_kno: any arguing is arguing about semantics
fizziblytwitching: Given we're training AI
anguscupcake: lol deus ex was great tho
fizziblytwitching: To play a game
fizziblytwitching: In order to test it out safely
b2kemann: everyone should play outer wilds, awesome game
robonhansonem: The tea is his secret. Never will be revealed lest we all become as him.
fizziblytwitching: To prove it's usefulness to apply to other problems
Checkmate624: Checkmate624 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Ne0Zer0: TRUE LUL
CozyDinoKigu: It's more easy to launch a game than to think what useful skill you have to improve, and to find the best ressources to develop your skills.
Santiago_LHC: I got good at playing whatever Need for Speed game came out in 2013 or so. I didn't acquire any skills, I learned the mechanics of that one game. I didn't get better at anything else.
robonhansonem: Yes. But in general, we probably have too much fun.
anguscupcake: the best video game is where you buy a whiteboard from aliexpress and write a todo list every morning
byte_baron: @robonhansonem society as a whole?
robonhansonem: Yes.
grekler3: this chat coping so hard LUL gaming = wasting time
Paw_4: @Santiago_LHC you probably did without noticing nor knowing
Santiago_LHC: Nope
eldac_kno: do you guys think Winograd Schemas are good test for AI?
Fatmetheny: @grekler3 This
CozyDinoKigu: And video-games is epidemic, when your only friend play video games, it's hard to not play with them
Checkmate624: doing something you enjoy is never a waste of time
leftyytwo: this discussion is giving me autism
anguscupcake: u already had it bro
Klemen1337: hello
robonhansonem: Worst video games are ones like WoW. You don't even learn useless skills. Instead, they simulate skill acquisition itself with their level system. Skinner box.
eldac_kno: no game teaches you useful skills
Iliftmymousealot: gaming = bad, learning = good can I get some credit for having the opinions
fizziblytwitching: Hah, WoW got me back into programming
koreais: @CozyDinoKigu it is not i used to play sorry waste time a lot but i deciced to stop this shit and now my friends play video games and i prefer to learn sth or read good book
byte_baron: they need to condense education into an mmorpg.
robonhansonem: Most teach you useless skills. Some teach you nothing.
DragonXPolymath: 1000 of games teach you usefull skills
byte_baron: education with all those addictive mmorpg merchanics.
calcmath: value is expected reward from that state
eldac_kno: no
Santiago_LHC: There are countless different types of games. I've learned many things by playing games, mostly the same kinds of things you would learn by reading fiction.
parasite_is_a_snakee: ETH mooning ;D
Checkmate624: yeah there's a big gap between educational games and games that are fun, a gap that should be filled
anguscupcake: VR could be used to gamify learning real world skills
sorin_chebac: wtf
eldac_kno: games are not education lol
CozyDinoKigu: @koreais With whom can you share your learning progress to get a bit of motivation ?
Santiago_LHC: But getting good at a game, generally doesn't get you any useful skills
DragonXPolymath: if u learn nothing usefull, ur mindset isnt usefull
byte_baron: @Checkmate624 the thing is though, it's kind of hard to stick education into a game and keep it fun
fizziblytwitching: I started writing a WoW emu because WoW was boring
calcmath: you should sample based on past visits or elese you wont explore
eldac_kno: it like putting education in movies
alexdenewb: Hey everyone, I'm new here, this community seems pretty interesting!
eldac_kno: stupid
parasite_is_a_snakee: just hack the pentagon bro 4Head
mero_1181: Shouldn’t the policy being function of the expected value of the future states?
vybster: I'm thinking of kids developing a very visual and intuitive understanding of mechanics(physics) by playing video games
Checkmate624: @byte_baron that's very true, but compare learning in schoo. You basically never feel like you're having fun, but when you learn by yourself it can actually be enjoyable
koreais: @CozyDinoKigu yeah thats the problem I have one friends who is into programming but on the other hand you have the community on the internet
Checkmate624: it's not impossible to make learning fun
eldac_kno: why dont they just play with phyisics irl
vybster: Or anyone else developing problem solving skills by playing puzzle games - like portal etc
mero_1181: Bellman equation
DrRobotvinnik: I like this new post-COVID focused George SeemsGood
eldac_kno: there is no such thing as problem solving skills
vybster: @eldac_kno Coz that can be boring. You gotta lure them in with fun stuff first
mero_1181: That’s what you solve to find the policy at time t
Newlax: !uptime
Fatmetheny: @DrRobotvinnik Post-covid??
5GToren: whats up mate have you touched a van de graaff generator?
marckkhoury: Which paper is he reading?
CozyDinoKigu: @koreais Okey. Personnaly i only have my uni. But even my mates in uni are not very serious about getting better in programming etc . . So i feel so fcking alone
swagettiyolonaise69: no more hairdresser
robonhansonem: There is use to visualizing mathematics. Making it into a game is unlikely to do much. Tricking people into acquiring skills generally doesn't work. People generally have to want to learn to get good at something. If they want to learn, you don't need to trick them with a game. Desire to write a useful script is far better than something snazzy like Code Academy.
mero_1181: Need to solve the equation backward
sorin_chebac: Hello mr George.Can you create a texas holdem bot? :D
Iliftmymousealot: i taught myself the navier stokes equations by playing minecraft.
foti_kasparov: Cooking music
calcmath: inst policy just chose action with maximum value?
cheesemanuchiha: LUL
leDryPotato: oof D:
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
parasite_is_a_snakee: TriHard
fizziblytwitching: Soothing voice
hiredguns: aah jennie, old horse
boss_ev: hola
robonhansonem: Play The Pirates of Penzance
Newlax: angelic
eldac_kno: so this is how he hacked ps3
koreais: @CozyDinoKigu yeah it's sucks. i also start learning programming as self-taught and i find it hard sometime to talk to someone who is on the same level as me
parasite_is_a_snakee: woow u emo's man .. LUL do u think bill gates felt the same as u
eldac_kno: it's slightly offtopic but what do you think about Winograd Schemas, is it a good test for AI?
Major_Spicy: @georgehotz what is happening here? I know very little about programming :)
parasite_is_a_snakee: @Major_Spicy trying to hack the pentagon.. to confirm is kim jung un is indeed dead
eldac_kno: he is reading papers while listening to pop muzak
sceptix1337: shoutouts to the people on youtube who cant hear shit reading the subtitles
Major_Spicy: @parasite_is_a_snakee thank you :)
Newlax: SingsNote SingsNote
robonhansonem: Was very supervised at Winograd progress. Problem with all these tests is once they are passed I start thinking they are less significant.
I2btw: show feet kaceyHEH
eldac_kno: why george always looks pissed off
Major_Spicy: Kacey subs DansGame
parasite_is_a_snakee: wooow a kacey sub 4Head
foti_kasparov: @eldac_kno Because of you
I2btw: kaceyTron hide the memes
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Kreygasm
fabriziobertoglio: Waitress is good
leDryPotato: Kreygasm
parasite_is_a_snakee: i will not even escape kacy subs even in the depths of hell
fizziblytwitching: (y)
NoLimitFitness: whyyyyMocked whyyyyMocked2 whyyyyBanned3
logi6000: its nice
norB88: meh
NoLimitFitness: whyyyyBanned1 whyyyyBanned2 whyyyyBanned3
Newlax: no
eldac_kno: если писать на русском Джордж ничего не поймет
St47ik: yo PogChamp
anguscupcake: хахахахааа
foti_kasparov: VoteNay
byte_baron: @robonhansonem are you 'the' robin hanson?
logi6000: why the russians here
norB88: Джордж of the jungle
tvorog9: о, а нас тут много?
robonhansonem: No. His em. Degraded copy. Much dimmer.
eldac_kno: Потому что у Джорджа русские корни
byte_baron: @robonhansonem oh
mero_1181: It’s the present value of the future states
logi6000: we are being invadrd by russians
eldac_kno: Джордж наш, русский
smurfd0: hmm didnt get a notification when you got back. was the movie good?
foti_kasparov: Останови эту игру, ты, блядь, шлюха
eldac_kno: с нами Бог
pinkcichlid: eldac_kno почему
grekler3: why do i understand russian little LUL
Newlax: you should make a crypto for comma
skut1212: hey george! What resources would you recommend to programmers on learning AI?
sceptix1337: rush b
I2btw: ENGLASCH!
alionthealien: test hi youtube person watching from the subtitles
leDryPotato: D:
airinspiration_: LUL
SiNNER_ontwitch: English only
alexanderrrrr: rush b
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: monkaH
okeeeeeee: PogChamp
sureom: cykla blat
foti_kasparov: @sceptix1337 I watch tunnels
oscar_my_cat: cyka blyat
DragonXPolymath: DragonXPolymath subscribed with Twitch Prime.
iiiiiiillllliiiill: cyka blyat
anguscupcake: lol
Newlax: what about british
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaW ONLY ENGLISH monkaW ONLY ENGLISH
Santiago_LHC: Mod me, I'll time them all out
numinousloop: do you play poker george?
pinkcichlid: sorri gorge my england is bed
WEEEEEEEELL_ITS_KNOCC_OUT: Speak American KKona
eldac_kno: it was ukranian
adamcernycz: KKona
alexanderrrrr: englad is my city
I2btw: su- or nord british?
pwnbutt: @georgehotz did you find a way to beat the corona? :)
sceptix1337: and if it werent for team 10
mr_stochastic: Is he trying to implement MuZero?
sorin_chebac: england is in france
foti_kasparov: france is in london
calcmath: yes he is trying to implement muzero for inverted penduulum
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: I thought englang was in Uganda
robonhansonem: @pwnbutt don't be older than 60.
eldac_kno: George is insecure about russian hackers mocking him on twitch
iiiiiiillllliiiill: i wish he would go back to coding the vaccine
sorin_chebac: can u create a texas holdem bot mr george?
eldac_kno: he wasnt coding the vaccjne
pinkcichlid: georgehotz sorri my england is bed
calcmath: protein folding took too much compute
I2btw: I'm happy he move on the the next task. After fix corna with AI.
calahat: What's up? What's happening,
Newlax: I only speak in twitch terms SwiftRage
iiiiiiillllliiiill: @eldac_kno he was and he was going to upload it to github
ez_clappers_: @georgehotz can we get an anti-govt rant
I2btw: gretCreep
eldac_kno: no, he was just learning about corona
I2btw: ohhh
St47ik: MuZero finds corona vaccine PogChamp
robonhansonem: Muzero learning CartPole.
be9ns: thoughts on the alphaGo doc?
NV17: Dynamics? ELI5?
eldac_kno: MuZero learning to hack
omniilismo: whats that pdf viewer?
fa7c0n: !today
robonhansonem: @be9ns Nothing you have not read before. Kinda interesting to watch anyway.
logi6000: remember when george played mibecraft
sceptix1337: minecraft lets play pls
I2btw: The only use case for PDFs is to extract official document layouts and logos. Just saying.
wasphy: hello; What do you know about gwern?
sceptix1337: oh no number go up
NV17: geohotz made by iPod touch better during my childhood
Newlax: fold protein pls
calcmath: widen your neural nwtowrk
fa7c0n: what are we doing today?
St47ik: NUMBER BRO GO DOWN PogChamp
sceptix1337: local minimum go brr
grekler3: PogChamp ?
eldac_kno: the only use for PDF is export of your LaTeX for normies
xeeton: yo, what's an appropriate timestep value when you apply this in cartpole?
St47ik: PogChamp PowerUpR
fabriziobertoglio: somebody understand this?
CozyDinoKigu: Put number - 1 Kappa
sceptix1337: 1000q
St47ik: Number goes BRrrrr
gamerguy009: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Mertkulek: Why you are using chromium
I2btw: LaTeX have a total visual brain.
calcmath: numner is is his neuralnetworks loss function
robonhansonem: Once I get some tea I will.
sceptix1337: rainbow ball go brr
logi6000: @mertkulek its ungoogled. jts really nice j use it too
fabriziobertoglio: adding an action to hidden state sk-1?
Newlax: rant about government pls
pinkcichlid: what chair is that?
I2btw: Can i get pass Myth+ 28 in WoW with this tool?
Joooooooooonas: how long is he streaming guys ?
gamerguy009: Trump2021?/?/? LOL
Joooooooooonas: or since when
pinkcichlid: MAGA
sceptix1337: rand paul 2020
eldac_kno: stop politics plz
grekler3: yo its going down PogChamp
robonhansonem: Governmental decay is inevitable. Ranting is only a palliative measure.
swagettiyolonaise69: drink bleach pls
CozyDinoKigu: the number so down we cannot see it on the screen
xeeton: @pinkcichlid Herman Miller Sayl
danrod43: i accumulated a batch earlier u get me
sceptix1337: number go way down
I2btw: geishaaKappaLisa
Newlax: George for prez?
logi6000: anyone else see the chargers fire new unis
NV17: how did he learn to jailbreak?
pinkcichlid: xeeton looks confy but if it herman must be exzpensive (
RazielSaysNice: a fellow The Front Bottoms listener, never would've expected it from you lol
fabriziobertoglio: is the output number the reward?
duckofdoom12: it do go down
sceptix1337: hell yeah cooking stream
eldac_kno: thoughts on Winograd Schemas?
robonhansonem: @swagettiyolonaise69 We should put bleach in our water supply to prevent pathogen growth.
beastars_is_best_anime: moon2BRAIN smart things
fearofcode: closing the renderer doesn't work on his machine either LUL
FargioFarmani: Can you turn on TTS?
sceptix1337: sudo killall
goochofanubis: oG af.
robonhansonem: @eldac_kno Saw this take on Winograd last week: https://deponysum.com/2020/01/16/recent-advances-in-natural-language-processing-some-woolly-speculations/
Broodfinger: Broodfinger subscribed with Twitch Prime.
eldac_kno: thanks man
duckofdoom12: them some good numbers
sceptix1337: learning rate too big
Streetmaniac: what is he working on
logi6000: ha geos computer go brrr
masters8: Read the title bro
swagettiyolonaise69: he's asking as if anyone understand wtf hes doing
FlySeddy: FlySeddy subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Streetmaniac: lmao
Newlax: pogchamp
74c55639: @georgehotz do you understand the fundamentals of reinforcement learning?
robonhansonem: @Streetmaniac MuZero CartPole.
FlySeddy: PogChamp PogChamp
Streetmaniac: ok so hes trying to get an AI to balance the stick
Streetmaniac: yes?
CozyDinoKigu: that it
robonhansonem: @Streetmaniac You got it.
robonhansonem: CartPole is considered AI complete.
calahat: !uptime
RexRothx: SourPls
N3wl34f: SeemsGood
lucianoxo: yo in middle school you were the reason i got all these girls, i had that jailbroken ipod touch
masters8: y'all viewers are retarded, peace
calcmath: u is reward
fabriziobertoglio: a model u
god_damn: @masters8 its true, i'm straight up braindead
rafplicz: nice κeyboard, what is it?
grekler3: u = Ligma i think
eldac_kno: Yu is a guy's name
eldac_kno: remember Rush Hour 3? Who is you, me is Yu
logi6000: we got scammed on our winter in philly. no snow at all
ak0ya_: u is a reward
ak0ya_: it says in the caption if the figure
anguscupcake: consoom
god_damn: LMAOOOOO
danrod43: TRUE
marcosneeroo: LUL
whichtom: reddit is wild
okeeeeeee: LUL
Caje_Vi: are u the new north korea dictator?
FlySeddy: LUL LUL
eldac_kno: favoruite Rush Hour movie?
fabriziobertoglio: :D
god_damn: thankyou kind stranger, upvoted
danrod43: reddit is such a cesspool
anguscupcake: huge echo chamber
hiredguns: god bleaa postmodernism, everything facist
Ne0Zer0: LUL
RexRothx: CONSOOM
I2btw: nice sub
Ne0Zer0: thats arguably the best sub
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaW
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaStare
danrod43: 4chan 29% lol
vloood: reddit is cringe dude
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
byte_baron: oh my god lol
god_damn: something something based something
byte_baron: that tara reade one is brutal
grekler3: Content finally PogChamp
exaccord: carful TOS
Ne0Zer0: LUL
Keyeh: monkaTOS
robonhansonem: Best Reddit is https://www.reddit.com/r/SubSimulatorGPT2/
danrod43: this isn't bannable
danrod43: plus no one's watching LUL
I2btw: kaceyHEH
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Believe all woman except when they come after top democrats LUL
parasite_is_a_snakee: 4Head 4Head 4Head
eldac_kno: fav Jackie Chan movie?
ez_clappers_: @georgehotz can we get n anti-govt rant
Keyeh: the m16 are ready
5GToren: he has that exploit sniper
Penguino138: George Hotz: "Just like you don't talk about having sniper rifles in your closet"
r00tkey: Of course corona lock-down is stupid. NotLikeThis
foti_kasparov: Reddit have some big losers and douchebags in there
radino321: kim jong un died according to tmz
suav12: TRUE
grekler3: TRUE
scenic9: Internet superman
danrod43: ANY PREPPERS? KKona
robonhansonem: Any sufficiently advanced crime is indistinguishable from sovereignty.
suav12: blockchain Pog
scarbromangler: so i come on here expecting bioinformatics and get
RexRothx: Woke take, bro
scarbromangler: this
PhosphoricAcid: same
fabriziobertoglio: Government will fight Blockchain
scarbromangler: ok here we go
Penguino138: The Ice
byte_baron: make an ML gubbermint, the algorithm will tell us what to do
whichtom: werent you meant to stop eating ice
5GToren: u didnt want the iceblock?
foti_kasparov: blockchainianism
byte_baron: just ML it
fabriziobertoglio: Blockchain can not scale right now .. Bitcoin can not replace Mastercard ... Unluckily
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: LUL
bsx1123: Omg he is chewing ice again
foti_kasparov: LUL
Mariosavitch: hello mr hotz
grekler3: LUL
okeeeeeee: XD
whichtom: thats going to be excellent to clean out
alionthealien: whats that
radino321: yes me
foti_kasparov: Those drone shots
Oligomineral3: awesome
Mariosavitch: no
marcosneeroo: LUL
ido_nvidia: that's fucking stupid
duckofdoom12: haha bulldozer go wrrrrrrrr
smurfd0: ge's litterarly playing in the sand box
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: quarantine... CarlSmile
rustduck: KKona hell ye
sobol55: hell no
r00tkey: fuckin stupid
jakuhor: best thing is it attracted bikers :DD
bubthefi5h: Lolol
PhosphoricAcid: Their take on gun control is just as hilarious
ido_nvidia: like the 2 kids still using the skate park are a real threat
anguscupcake: looks like a nice park
airinspiration_: LUL
I2btw: kaceyHEH
fabioitout: where are those parks?+
suav12: POOLS CLOSED
PhosphoricAcid: pools closed
dr_set: how do we keep the dummies in check without the goverment?
ido_nvidia: lmao
Mariosavitch: lol
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: SHOW US
iswoqqe: LUL
fireposeidoncx: leaked
Sycto: Swimming in your bathtub is the new thing
SparksCx: LEAKED
foti_kasparov: Neighbor peeping
SparksCx: I KNOW WHERE YOU LIVE
I2btw: GPS JPG kaceyHEH
purpaleslushiii: @georgehotz bruh u want corona
DasMastah: High tech solution
Penguino138: Quality content i love it
SparksCx: True
fireposeidoncx: leaked...
whichtom: liability bs
joaosena1: FailFish
SparksCx: @fireposeidoncx nice name
Palmatoro_vg: Top recommended books? @georgehotz
5GToren: move to the app on the other side xD
PhosphoricAcid: george karen
anguscupcake: just consoom
5GToren: wave wave
suav12: mizkifW yo
powerofpickle: karen hotz
alionthealien: lmao revealing government darkest secrets on twitch
Quad___lol: @Palmatoro_vg bible
Penguino138: @georgehotz Are you gonna get an apartment where you can smoke weed?
foti_kasparov: Edward Snowden tryharders
robonhansonem: How do we make govt not a joke?
duckofdoom12: putting police in place < haha bulldozer go wrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
eldac_kno: thoughts on Winograd Schemas?
arhamkaiser: steve jobs or elon musk
Penguino138: Phagophagia
grekler3: no government ? LUL
whichtom: make the majority of people not morons
RexRothx: Is he in Cali?
Tekrific: at this point it feels like a bad simulation where the programmer is fucking with us
Penguino138: *Pagophagia
ralphielaurence: open source data driven govt
whichtom: democracy is working as intended, its just most people are idiots
SparksCx: lol
rustduck: true
powerofpickle: Do you do low level stuff anymore?
gamerguy009: Are we a simulation?
Penguino138: Why is Idaho the most interested in Corona? We have less than 2k cases here lol
jakuhor: why there are 2 political parties in US Kappa
fabriziobertoglio: I agree on coronavirus.
rene7551: which hip hop is the best vs corona?
suav12: nash equilibrium monkaW
powerofpickle: Will we reach herd immunity before a vaccine?
jakuhor: yin yang
gamerguy009: I dont want this to end
yo_zayden: Bro I'm a big fan and a follower but non sub am i allowed here brother.
jakuhor: :DD
Mariosavitch: true
suav12: kill monkW
foti_kasparov: @yo_zayden Get out
robonhansonem: Median voter theorem
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Two parties LUL it's just one party
SparksCx: yin and yang
fizziblytwitching: the point is that you have two parties that are so similar that when the people want to give the government a kick you cna elect the other to do the same thing in a different suit
suav12: @yo_zayden plebs unite
JakeWoodruff20: a technocracy is coming soon!!
scarbromangler: how often do you masturbate
airinspiration_: :(
dr_set: what about the green and the libertarians parties? There's more than 2 parties, but nobody votes for them
crabby_clink: riopYolo
ky0jinjaeger: @rene7551 nas is fitting, especially ny state of mind
5GToren: do you watch pron
jasondesante: some have bigger dicks
freshsoclean: lul
okeeeeeee: nice try LUL
SparksCx: I AM NEVER GIVING YOU MY SUB :)
qubitmanipulator: because I'm smarter with my money
leDryPotato: ok im not falling for thiss LUL
anguscupcake: that makes a lot of sense
yo_zayden: @foti_kasparov did i asked you P****
danrod43: have you seen invadievie's take on subscribers?
logi6000: @jasondesante yes
airinspiration_: Im gonna sub rn
foti_kasparov: Meritocracy
alxhotel: :(
I2btw: mcretPAB mcretPAB mcretPAB
fabriziobertoglio: I agree. Subscribers are better
SiNNER_ontwitch: lol
axlebear: PogChamp
eldac_kno: subscriber chad
fabriziobertoglio: Just Subscribe
r00tkey: Better in what sort of way?
SlowDeluxe: so are we gonna invade north korea ? looks promising
CozyDinoKigu: i dont know why but i feel a sudent desire to click the subscribe button
PhosphoricAcid: never subbed, never donated, adblock on, stolen laptop, neighbors wifi
Akandesh: time to get my moms credit card
ar2zee: What is the best move in your opinion Goverment should takes now ?
Penguino138: That was the best Aside of any stream
jasondesante: thank you george for subscribing to my channel
arhamkaiser: whats the religion that makes the most sense
jasondesante: jasond711 jasond711 jasond711 jasond711
alxhotel: Better in the sense of richness
fabioitout: just do it
fizziblytwitching: Better for george
robonhansonem: Have to get to work. PM me when Hotz triggers the intelligence explosion.
gamerguy009: Gift me a sub
fabriziobertoglio: I m poor, can't subscribe... literally corona virus killing everything
logi6000: @phosphoricacid the free life
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: RIP kim jong un LUL
PhosphoricAcid: @logi6000 some call me a free spirit
gamerguy009: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
fabioitout: So, you think society is meritocracy driven, and not by luck?
Bentipe: lamans1Fogo
freshsoclean: mat ops research
anguscupcake: your ability to succeed in a meritocracy is largely affected by genetics
whichtom: RL is a super interesting field, but the research is mostly lame
gamerguy009: Society is fat and disgusting
robonhansonem: Merit is mostly genetics. Genetics is luck.
ky0jinjaeger: imagine being so fat that you unintentionally kill yourself in your mid 30s
SlowDeluxe: anybody knows why he is using degoogled chromium ?
freshsoclean: .... up to
SparksCx: its easy its ....
whichtom: 'we achieved new SOTA on x atari games' and deepmind lying saying they solved SC2
fabriziobertoglio: @georgehotz ... I believe they just mean a range
fabriziobertoglio: @georgehotz a1, a2, a3, ..., an
fabioitout: Yes, i think so it is all about luck
axlebear: fricken dot dot dots
Mariosavitch: ... means "did you just really say that?"
fireposeidoncx: what are you trying to do?
PhosphoricAcid: @ky0jinjaeger I'm bulking bro
Joooooooooonas: @SlowDeluxe maybe cause chrome is good and google is bad
anguscupcake: permabulk
blueberryguac: blueberryguac subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak! I am better than all of you.
gamerguy009: Duck duck go
moizai: how's life going
rustduck: i prefer firefox
anguscupcake: firefox f12 is so slow tho
whichtom: wait muzero cant even perform for games with highly sparse rewards
SlowDeluxe: @Joooooooooonas sure but i read that its only one guy patching it so i was just wondering about the security level of the browser
SlowDeluxe: privacy > security ?
gamerguy009: Write some ransom ware
moizai: is comma still working right now.
74c55639: i prefer firefox, because it was written in Rust. Just wanted to join the idiotic conversation ...
ky0jinjaeger: damn, kimmy boy would've been ripped if he had the time to lose weight BibleThump
fizziblytwitching: Fix values?
fizziblytwitching: Lame comment
fireposeidoncx: rip kim jong un
zennydmt: he died?
Musashhhi: comma10k, you can work with comma too
kektobiologist: link to thr paper?
parasite_is_a_snakee: r.i,p joe rogan BibleThump
fireposeidoncx: @zennydmt apparently
arhamkaiser: rip kim jong
whichtom: ya ive submitted PR to comma10k already
arhamkaiser: bong
zennydmt: @fireposeidoncx i dont see it on cnn
SlowDeluxe: @zennydmt apparently he is in a vegitable state after a botched heart surgery
SparksCx: is gonna explode
fabriziobertoglio: E[ut+k+1...].. do you guys understand this?
kektobiologist: nvm got it
nsielicki: Hey George, can you talk a bit about the state of Qira and what needs to be done to get it working on python3? Willing to do the work just don't know where it's at. Thanks.
arhamkaiser: rip kim
gamerguy009: Rip tom hanks
whichtom: I just wish gym documentation was good
fireposeidoncx: rip kim
arhamkaiser: rip kim jong long tong
SparksCx: what happened to kim
arhamkaiser: ded
arhamkaiser: reportedly
swagettiyolonaise69: is he dead ?
arhamkaiser: tmz
SparksCx: its confirmed?
fireposeidoncx: kims death is a huge loss for society
gamerguy009: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
74c55639: "Other unconfirmed reports, attributed to senior party sources in Beijing, said an operation to insert a stent went wrong because the surgeon’s hands were shaking so badly."
arc12__: he is in a vegatative states
swagettiyolonaise69: i dont think he does vegetables
gamerguy009: Celery state lol
fabriziobertoglio: i is time ... why not call it t like in the book
arhamkaiser: apparently his heart surgery was botched
kektobiologist: 0 to 100 real quick
St47ik: PogChamp
Lathendros: @georgehotz thoughts on transhumanism
gamerguy009: SeemsGood
St47ik: Decentralized governance PogChamp
Mariosavitch: have you read john lock?
swagettiyolonaise69: AI government overlord
gamerguy009: Pacemakers
fabriziobertoglio: i don't understand why he is multiplying i*3 because as my understanding i is the t for time .. each next step is t+1
parasite_is_a_snakee: @georgehotz ppl dont care who is controlling the strings as long as they can consooooooooooooom Kreygasm
WhispyHerc: george can you explain what your'e working on? sorry im a noob not sure what this is
dr_set: I want a benevolent AI tyrant
YellowSnowman_23: YellowSnowman_23 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months!
grimers: why is chat talking about kim
whichtom: whats your reward function though?
arhamkaiser: cause he died
SparksCx: @grimers they say he is dead
arc12__: kim kardashian
St47ik: Kim possible
oversum: jupyter notebook is nice
fabriziobertoglio: what is gamma?
fireposeidoncx: kim is dead
SparksCx: no
arhamkaiser: no
DzyaN_: Rip kanye
Penguino138: I was the first sub today :D
gamerguy009: Dont touch your face
SparksCx: D:
gadean: gadean subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Penguino138: Welcome new subscribers
rustduck: D: ☝️
Den_dp: I'll subscribe if you start hacking Kappa
grekler3: i hacked this Pog
SparksCx: I AM STILL HERE :)
PhosphoricAcid: you have no power here
DzyaN_: Ez
Hypheus_: dead chat PepeLaugh
SxRS2: LUL
routerkicker: routerkicker subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 5 months, currently on a 2 month streak!
HopZe: HACKERMAN PogChamp
YellowSnowman_23: YellowSnowman_23 is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
garydsmith1: yo i am a sub!!!!
YellowSnowman_23: YellowSnowman_23 gifted a Tier 1 sub to bsx1123!
YellowSnowman_23: YellowSnowman_23 gifted a Tier 1 sub to eeXecute!
YellowSnowman_23: YellowSnowman_23 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Mint2bSpiced!
YellowSnowman_23: YellowSnowman_23 gifted a Tier 1 sub to apolybus!
YellowSnowman_23: YellowSnowman_23 gifted a Tier 1 sub to eldac_kno!
Checkmate624: yo nice
garydsmith1: yo man gift me a sub?
grimers: hboxA hboxB hboxB hboxB hboxC
sectionmp: sectionmp subscribed with Twitch Prime.
dorkmo: ShowLove1
lanyxqt2: Lol
Checkmate624: you can buy a message in sub only mode with bits
buddhm: Dodged
Penguino138: @georgehotz has the divine right to ban
garydsmith1: you can redeem a sub only message
Mobius5: WHICH K3YB01RD do you have????
swagettiyolonaise69: kim is ded
okeeeeeee: subing to a millionaire Kappa
localcanofdutchgold: never subbed, never donated, stolen laptop, neighbors wifi, gifted sub, ez clap
mmi18: i can type in sub mode !
Hypheus_: :crab: kim is gone :crab:
Checkmate624: I just want the train to go further
Penguino138: You spend 430 twitch points and it lets you message if it is in sub only mode
abedbawsxx: Sub mode LUL
parasite_is_a_snakee: LOOOL IM NOT A SUB AND IM SPEAKING CXXX TriHard
garydsmith1: why did this happen tho? sub only mode?
fireposeidoncx: stop this dictatorship
Mariosavitch: no
SparksCx: NO YOU DON'T GET ANYTHING :)
Talgathy: Free the peasants
cheesemanuchiha: im in the gulag
mritzing: twitch gets money for twitch points, ads are worth more when they can prove the viewer is there
Checkmate624: Why would he turn off high quality chat mode lol
mmi18: i think 1 twitch point is equivalent to a bucked of oil
grenaderaven: whats a sub
garydsmith1: we just need to watch your videos and we get points
Joooooooooonas: you get them by watch time
abedbawsxx: Not only i'm going to type in a sub mode, but im also going to ask for the k3yb4ard LUL
numinousloop: who are your favorite engineers to collab with
Penguino138: I think the chat may be higher quality in subs only mode
norB88: norB88 is gifting 3 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 16 in the channel!
norB88: norB88 gifted a Tier 1 sub to powerofpickle!
norB88: norB88 gifted a Tier 1 sub to forklifting1!
norB88: norB88 gifted a Tier 1 sub to T3chHS!
Penguino138: ayoooo hype
garydsmith1: gift me a extra month of subs?
lanyxqt2: have you ever played videogames? or is it something you've never been interested in?
Waldoqq: imagine not being a sub
Waldoqq: imagine being so poor to not be a sub LUL
St47ik: i was a sub and now i'm broke :(
garydsmith1: imagine not having a credit card to pay for subs
garydsmith1: thats me tho
bigie: what is mu zero? (model based/free, TD or monte carlo)
Checkmate624: Can we get level 5 train?
0xnan: just use my points
garydsmith1: yesssss
cheesemanuchiha: monte
ricardosmf: suuup
ak0ya_: why only sub mode??
garydsmith1: higher qulity chat
Lost_x_Echo: Lost_x_Echo subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Avelansh: You can't silence us all :)
Checkmate624: It's reverse taxation without representation
cactusvacuum: income, sales, capital gains, or what?
abedbawsxx: Remove sub mode you semite Kappa
Mariosavitch: you just straight up assumed federal income taxes is ok?
St47ik: Blockchain proof of tax voting PogChamp
Checkmate624: De-centralized voting? Weird
Den_dp: so poor people will never get a chance to pick his/her candidate and change situation
RexRothx: Why not just make it landowners-only voting, while you're at it
SparksCx: i am back :)
bigie: bigie subscribed at Tier 1.
Checkmate624: @Den_dp poor people still pay taxes though, right?
grimers: cool
Ne0Zer0: PogChamp
engineererik: Danke
marcosneeroo: o
St47ik: pls don't be low quality chat NotLikeThis
arc12__: could some one gift me a sub please
bigie: come on i just subbed dude.
BootsForCats: so people on wellfare can't vote?
SlowDeluxe: Pog?
norB88: Choo Chooo HypeRacer
SparksCx: @bigie LUL
cheesemanuchiha: liberate me daddy
DzyaN_: freedommm
mero_1181: Voting is not enough incentive to have people paying taxes
Penguino138: We can only discriminate towards non-subs :p
neilsweb: Only people with cherry brown keys should be able to vote.
parasite_is_a_snakee: @bigie rekt 4Head
Ne0Zer0: the bar is private tho
fireposeidoncx: welcome back plebls
Lost_x_Echo: Choo Chooo HypeRacer
Den_dp: @Checkmate624 yes, but I can imagine some situation where they are broke and can't do that
bigie: I would like a refund please LUL
cheesemanuchiha: @bigie LUL
St47ik: proof of steak voting Kappa
filipeoliveiraa: :)
anguscupcake: only people with HHKB can vote
nsielicki: I mean this country was founded on the principle of one vote per tax-paying family, enforced through the notion that land ownership represented that.
swagettiyolonaise69: worst idea ever
garydsmith1: George whats the most illegal thing you have done? pirate a movie?
nsielicki: It's really what the country was founded on.
bigie: is that basic cartpole?
henistein: How worth is learning assembly nowadays?
arc12__: we shouldnt look to the past to find out whats right
St47ik: @arc12__ why not?
arc12__: black people coulnt vote
whichtom: abolish the federal govt so states are independent and act more like the EU
mmi18: so then rich people have the power?
grekler3: D: Wtf
St47ik: droogz Kreygasm
Checkmate624: @arc12__ so we look to the past and learn not to do that
Waldoqq: god I love this stream
grimers: dude weed lmao
beltez: yoooo george !
fabioitout: You are not forcede enter Apple, you are forced enter this fucking planet
nsielicki: It's a great idea but it's politically untenable. Less than 50% of the population is tax positive -- that's a fact -- it's what Mitt Romney got in shit for in 2012 but he was 100% right when he said it.
arc12__: yeah thats fine
xeeton: keep it up george we believe in you
arc12__: i meant look to what the founders said whats right
nsielicki: We're already far off the cliff of unsustainability when it comes to tax granting representation.
RexRothx: What's his job/main source of income?
Leleckoo: !uptime
whichtom: the world the founders lived in was far different to today
okeeeeeee: true
St47ik: Skin in the game PogChamp
ayy420stillnotbanned: brain draining india fuck yeah
Avelansh: Why would you want to go to America in the first place
highflyer_nl: pay to play?
SparksCx: but they think, that will displace US citizen workers @georgehotz
parasite_is_a_snakee: @georgehotz what about asylum seekers?
nsielicki: > imagine not thinking America is the best place to live in the entire world.
parasite_is_a_snakee: @georgehotz fuk em 4Herad ?
arc12__: if the education system gets fixed, so does our democracy
St47ik: @highflyer_nl contribute to play
Mariosavitch: Hotz 2020. Break the simulator. Vote Today
ayy420stillnotbanned: @Avelansh lol yeah stay in india pajeet, sure that's your own choice and not that your visa got rejected
numinousloop: how good of a proxy do you think money is for value add? sounds like you think it approaches 1:1
parasite_is_a_snakee: @georgehotz what about refugees
whichtom: some american industry is the best in the world by a huge margin
mmi18: but what if we only let non tax payers vote?
grekler3: @parasite_is_a_snakee same principle
okeeeeeee: ye ok the brain draining of other countries is also a valid counter argument 󠀀
parasite_is_a_snakee: @grekler3 how do u know if a kid from syria going to add value
Avelansh: @ayy420stillnotbanned good story
St47ik: @georgehotz how about tax havens/evasion NotLikeThis
fireposeidoncx: america is literally the last country one would like to live in
aaddrr: why @fireposeidoncx
whichtom: thats like, your opinion man
ak0ya_: @georgehotz
bigie: @fireposeidoncx categorically false but ok
whichtom: american aerospace industry is the best in the world bar none
phennessey: Did the protein ever fold?
ayy420stillnotbanned: @fireposeidoncx back to /r/chapotraphouse tr4nn y
mero_1181: Democrats pay more takes
okeeeeeee: whats the deal with brain draining weak countries ? @georgehotz
neilsweb: Are you going to invest in a better quality bed? You need to take care of your back.
mero_1181: By definition
Checkmate624: @parasite_is_a_snakee I think one solution could be that immagrants seeking asylum have a waiting period after immigration where they don't have to pay taxes, so they can find a job initially
nsielicki: The rate of expatriation in the united states is evidence that Americans don't want to live anywhere else.
aaddrr: fuck sleeping bruh
whichtom: its such a huge country with such variety
m3m333: what do you think about corporations that avoid paying taxes
St47ik: ^
Checkmate624: ^^
arc12__: value added tax
fireposeidoncx: @aaddrr trashy health care, cities are dirty, education is bad...
robonhansonem: Land value tax is the best tax.
numinousloop: democrats dont think money is a good proxy for value
parasite_is_a_snakee: @Checkmate624 why do they need to find a job when they can get food stamps TriHard
RexRothx: Why would the voting population then vote in the interests of the poor, then?
arc12__: VAT + UBI
MABunglawala: anyone know what's his upcoming project?
mero_1181: What if you don\’t
cactusvacuum: i don't understand why all the libertarian tech folks don't all move to some place like idaho and setup the kind of utopia that a rich, educated, and forward thinking community would create
mero_1181: Have a job?
mero_1181: What if you don’t have a job?
ak0ya_: You can just suggest UBI to people to buy their voting rights
Major_Spicy: 69% of political parties funding from... TheThing
Checkmate624: @parasite_is_a_snakee that's true, if they're living off government support, do they pay taxes on that government support which is funded by taxes? seems like a weird loop
anguscupcake: utopia is a myth
MABunglawala: @cactusvacuum that be dope asf
St47ik: from MuZero to taxes 4Head
mero_1181: Are you going to vote or not?
ayy420stillnotbanned: myths are utopic
aaddrr: @fireposeidoncx i am actually trying to get a green card im from spain
anguscupcake: lol they are
maxschneider96: maxschneider96 subscribed at Tier 1.
ayy420stillnotbanned: @aaddrr chaco rubio no te ballas
robonhansonem: There exists utopias that don't violate physical law. Navigating to them is the hard part.
ayy420stillnotbanned: *chacho
whichtom: ya I want to move to the US also but I need a PhD first
Vistor1001: wtf is up with this kim jong un shit is he really sick
robonhansonem: What policy is he talking about?
nsielicki: @georgehotz it depends on the federal money that each state takes
St47ik: @Vistor1001 very sick
beltez: is dead
fireposeidoncx: @aaddrr stay in the EU! It is way better here
Junki4: jinni1 jinni1
nouryqt: heya
smurfd0: it dumbs it down for people
mhammad123: hi gro how is u
okeeeeeee: they mostly do it in USA
Jake_Miller_: @fireposeidoncx wut, are you kidding man
Mariosavitch: go read john lock for your answers
niko174_: Здравствуйте
jacolack: wdym skin in the game?
joaosena1: tadeBOMB tadeTACO
Jake_Miller_: @fireposeidoncx from italy, damn this place
aaddrr: @fireposeidoncx business oportunity is shit in EU i think though
ayy420stillnotbanned: @Jake_Miller_ he's some moron from some commie discord
mero_1181: It’s not democratic
St47ik: @jacolack look it up
Checkmate624: blue states on average are richer, but I would guess republicans have more giant coporations that bring in a lot of revenue
Killeraing: thanks fo reminding me why i want to code
Killeraing: gnite
Muaaath: what is he doing? data science?
whichtom: some reinforcement learning stuff
arc12__: most fortune 500 ceos are dems
Jake_Miller_: @ayy420stillnotbanned ohhhh, ok ty man
yevenesh: @georgehotz are u livin in silicon valley?
fireposeidoncx: @Jake_Miller_ free colleges, good healthcare, financial support from the government, less crackheads for all those reasons the EU is a much better place to live in
SparksCx: its la
whichtom: he's in SD iirc
ayy420stillnotbanned: @yevenesh san diego
Checkmate624: oh nvm, I assumed median
radu3521: What is he working on?
parasite_is_a_snakee: @georgehotz has anyone ever told u .. u walk like a penguin PogChamp
robonhansonem: @radu3521 Muzero PoleCart
fillmyvoid: I disagree with that, because the spirit that should be echoed involves the idea that everyone ought to have skin in the game, and can have skin in the game. If we lose that then we lose more than just how voting works
ayy420stillnotbanned: @fireposeidoncx financial support in the form of 40-50% taxation top kek
Checkmate624: @radu3521 looks like a chess bot? but I've been watching 20 minutes and I still don't know
xeeton: @radu3521 muzero implementation for cartpole
parasite_is_a_snakee: hee walks like a penguin 4Head
aaddrr: @fireposeidoncx financial support from the goverment? am i missing that?
nouryqt: no FeelsBadMan
okeeeeeee: at under 18 over 99% are still net negative LUL
Jake_Miller_: @fireposeidoncx I see you like pay taxes for politician, wow
radu3521: @xeeton i dont understand what that is :))
radu3521: is the first time i tune in
xeeton: an AI thing that balances a pole
maxschneider96: Just subscribed! Hope u´´ ll make another bioinformatics video soon - from a drug discovery student.
robonhansonem: Children a public goods. Give parents a cut of their future kids income tax.
nsielicki: can you talk about what needs to be done to fully get qira off python2? Willing to work on it just don't know what's the hold up
ky0jinjaeger: I think I kinda get what u mean, it's a problem in the Balkans, huge public sector which consistently votes for party which will keep those jobs alive
arc12__: ubi
mikey9988: the rona vote monkaW
ayy420stillnotbanned: anyone can vote in america they aint asking for ID...
fireposeidoncx: @ayy420stillnotbanned you wont pay 50% taxes unless you are a millionaire
Checkmate624: but when you're under 18, you still have to pay income tax, even though you can't vote, which is wack
robonhansonem: Select leaders with random sampling and standardized testing.
bigie: technically not radical but it will be labeled as one
phennessey: All I want to know is if the protein folded.
okeeeeeee: so your discriminating towards dumb people ? Kappa @georgehotz
ayy420stillnotbanned: @fireposeidoncx nope you're paying 46% on average, not saying only income but all taxes
Checkmate624: @okeeeeeee real life discriminates against dumb people
bsx1123: you vote anonymously
ayy420stillnotbanned: ppl making $45k a year are paying that
robonhansonem: Sortition applied to top 1% SAT scores.
Jake_Miller_: @okeeeeeee i think it's called evolution
arc12__: how would value that a person generates be measured
ayy420stillnotbanned: 45k pretax
okeeeeeee: ye it should be like that, it was a joke
jakuhor: @arc12__ money, free market can value everything
fireposeidoncx: @ayy420stillnotbanned where do you live? It varies quite a bit between the countries
AleXander1022: what's up dude? how are you ?
aaddrr: @fireposeidoncx where do you live
Xanor: bailout the bars'
ayy420stillnotbanned: @fireposeidoncx spain, it's below the average tho, around 38%
teerv: rich people use less goverment founded resources
fireposeidoncx: @aaddrr germany
bobsmash: geohot for president PogChamp
whichtom: a big change would probably be mandatory voting so turnout is >55.7% which is a joke
AleXander1022: Geohotz will be a good president yeah !!!
Checkmate624: and most of the missing voters are the young population
engineererik: In germany, people who earn more than 54,000€ have to pay 42%
arc12__: voting should be online
St47ik: @arc12__ nah too risky
whichtom: mandatory voting else fine, that'll give people motivation
Checkmate624: young people not voting is one reason people attribute to bernie doing so poorly
arc12__: when we have the technology
teerv: @engineererik yeah put if you have a company and pay it out like a dividend what is the tax then
Den_dp: that's like a derivative of a people opinions
fireposeidoncx: @engineererik are you from germany?
St47ik: LUL
Jake_Miller_: @engineererik yep, italy 41%, also over 75k 43%
engineererik: @fireposeidoncx yeah
SparksCx: lol
ayy420stillnotbanned: @engineererik and that's only income, plenty more taxes around definitely place em over 50%
fireposeidoncx: @engineererik ehrenmann
bigie: have you seen the covid-19 tracing from google and apple?
Xanor: vote yourself
whichtom: why? you have skin in the game? its in your best interest to vote
Penguino138: george looking comfy af
zyrax222: im voting george then
arc12__: the electoral college is pointless
eeXecute: Thank you for the gifted sub yellowsnowman
engineererik: @fireposeidoncx zumindest bin ich hier nicht alleine aus Deutschland^^
maxschneider96: @fireposeidoncx where abouts in germany? I used to live in munich...
rinaldo1818: @engineererik richtig
logi6000: im back
fireposeidoncx: so viele deutsche hier :D
maxschneider96: österreich...
aaddrr: is frankfurt good to start a business?
engineererik: @rinaldo1818 noch so einer :D
okeeeeeee: was los
maxschneider96: österreich-UK
logi6000: should i play madden or should i work on something
fireposeidoncx: @maxschneider96 bin aus münchen
rinaldo1818: Germany-BLN
engineererik: @fireposeidoncx ich aus Frankfurt
vruthlessv: RIP
Penguino138: germans invading
Ne0Zer0: monkaS
maxschneider96: @fireposeidoncx nice, hab in schwabing und in garching gewohnt und bin zur TUM gegangen
jakuhor: to si jenom myslíš :*
okeeeeeee: german is a germanic leanguage, just like english :)
Leleckoo: RIP
sureom: baguette
abedbawsxx: تبا للانقلش
porteus: KKona
zyrax222: nederlanders?
mikey9988: KKona Clap
MrStereoX: i missed you where have you been ? @georgehotz
bigie: i don't know mu-0. does it have a replay buffer ?
beltez: no puedo hablar español Jorge ?
teerv: SKÅL
Muaaath: اتفق
Nedeljko99: yo yo
rshelat97: george xenophobic?
radu3521: da mai dute in pizda matii
arc12__: konichiwa
iiiiiiillllliiiill: @georgehotz did u hack kim jong un?
frehdo: english is not germanic?
soldierheadsmite: that's too bad :c
logi6000: @abedbawsxx you boutta get fucked
Penguino138: @okeeeeeee english is a hybrid of many older languages
eldac_kno: you can speak english using characters from other alphabets
cylon007: lol
Adictos: ye
g0nzl: hahahaa
Checkmate624: surprising amount of german speakers in this chat
beltez: Gracias amigo
arisnotle: Ik praat gewoon Nederlands wat zeg jij
bigie: why would you do anything in tensorflow man? pytorch is way better
arc12__: the printer industry is worse than healthcare industry
whichtom: tf is a nightmare
aaddrr: its crazy how in twitch you can reach out to such important people so easly
whichtom: I'm losing my mind using it
ky0jinjaeger: Is spanish hard to learn?
aaddrr: @ky0jinjaeger yeah
arc12__: how is pytorch better
Checkmate624: @ky0jinjaeger I've heard spanish is one of the easiest languages to learn from english
Tsoding: 160 raiders from Tsoding have joined!
mikey9988: un poco KEKW @ky0jinjaeger
cactusvacuum: @georgehotz why haven't you bought land?
Ne0Zer0: 160 PogChamp
whichtom: yoo dude hello
Jannnik: tsoding Pog
engineererik: @ky0jinjaeger try out german :D
bigie: could you talk about mu0 a bit? if it doesn't have a replay buffer it takes a while to converge. it looks continuous right ? that's even harder
ravenmaster: tsodinJS RAID tsodinJS
mikey9988: German is difficult to learn
mikey9988: imo
red_plex: working on twitch chess ?
whichtom: imo pytorch is just way easier to work with than tf, way easier to read and docs are better
Penguino138: We got a raid!
Penguino138: Shield wall up!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 2 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 17 in the channel!
whichtom: and i don't have to import tf.compat.v2.python.ops.something
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to lexxy23!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to roberto_in!
eldac_kno: do you think people fundemantally good or evil
whichtom: wow nice link
bigie: the only way tf is gonna beat pytorch is if this swift thing takes off. i hope it doesn't. i hate tf and swift LUL
robonhansonem: Make your own sauce.
Penguino138: You can make creamy pasta sauce with milk
PristineBanana: butter works
robonhansonem: Olive oil. Canned tomatoes. Garlic.
whichtom: isn't pytorch more popular amongst researchers tho
maxschneider96: He needs some milk
Penguino138: I mean I make mine with soymilk, any kind will work
bigie: yes but pytorch is in python and python is slow as fuck
whichtom: tf might still be used more in industry idk
jontowtruck: as someone who's contributed to tf swift.... it's not looking too great.
whichtom: ya true
smurfd0: ketchup=almost pasta sause
xeeton: also, just make sure the eggs sink in water
fireposeidoncx: @smurfd0 true
mashafique: What up everyone
robonhansonem: @smirfd0 Heresy
soldierheadsmite: r u trying to solve a bug?
mltsd: !uptime
whichtom: contributing to anything tf sounds unenjoyable
alabamaman02: george can you give me a virtual high five?
spoofyboy: !uptime
cj1m: imma give you a virtual smack alabamaman
bigie: tf is broken in python at least. they break APIs with each release too. they were the first, definitely not the best
alabamaman02: that's better @cj1m
fireposeidoncx: do you guys think george is viewbotting?
LJRewiind: hey chat whats he doing today
whichtom: they were not the first surely
jefft13: i think if he coded the viewbot on stream its fair game
norB88: What did you guys think of Wolframs "Fundamental theory"?
bigie: first one to offer a "solid" framework
mashafique: I didn't really look into it but from discussions I've seen from other physicists it's nothing that profound
whichtom: what about caffe/theano?
thejuror8: @norB88 Didn't see it, what's it about ?
whichtom: wolfram is an interesting man
bigie: tensorflow is easier to work with than caffe. the other frameworks just fell behind and no one uses them anymore
whichtom: gotcha
bigie: @norB88 i couldn't understand it past the relativity theory. i hope he's onto something
takkat14: guys, what is the article at the background?
mltsd: george do you work on low level stuff at all anymore or do you focus on machine learning
qow_: !uptime
whichtom: @takkat14 muzero paper
thejuror8: Lmao what kind of pants is he wearing
takkat14: @whichtom thanks
bigie: if it's 5 in basic cartpole it means it's basically falling down right? maybe your actions aren't going through for some reason
eksdee_1_2_3: ur not fasting D:
maxschneider96: What do you think of Donald Trump´ s suggestion to inject disinfectants?
thejuror8: @maxschneider96 What do you thin khe things about it
axlebear: Not fasting FeelsWeirdMan
thejuror8: *What do you think he thinks about it, what kind of question is that lmao
fireposeidoncx: @maxschneider96 it is a good idea Trump knows best #Trump2020
mltsd: i finna inject vodka to kill coronavirus
engineererik: @maxschneider96 never heard something that stupid
julianus_mh: is this corona stream?
eldac_kno: what s better for newbie tensorflow or theano
FargioFarmani: pytorch
whichtom: pytorch or keras
kektobiologist: this guy has lost his damn mind
HHqZz: tensorflow
fireposeidoncx: @maxschneider96 rip :d
eldac_kno: why pytorch better than tensorflow
RedguardWithAids: tf
JOPEAR: Hello
axlebear: True
jefft13: if youre new new id say sklearn honestly
whichtom: documentation isn't a mess
majorawpsome: does america have a 2 party system?
whichtom: true actually, start off with sklearn
maxschneider96: Well that escalated quickly
eldac_kno: so theano sucks?
whichtom: theano is ancient
whichtom: no one uses it anymore
bigie: basic cartpole starts at the upright position. if you don't input any controls it falls down. but your loss wasn't going down too idk. i have to read up on mu0
thejuror8: Keras is a great way to start
smurfd0: the values that f_l_loss is based on, do they seem to align with what they should be or !?
thejuror8: Hard to beat
mangoxavier: Have you heard the short story called “the egg”?
majorawpsome: isn't it weird that you can still be alive with a somewhat dead brain?
costcospizza: yup
jefft13: keras is good for nets no?
okeeeeeee: lag
inDOObitablee: F
eldac_kno: brain dead chicken is alive for few seconds
robonhansonem: Vote Trump, the lesser of two demented old men!
lexxy23: droping frames?
Den_dp: F
Penguino138: lagggg
ky0jinjaeger: F
thejuror8: Next slide PogChamp
Den_dp: reiraF
sheveeee: f
whichtom: yea keras is good
mangoxavier: Rip
thejuror8: @jefft13 Yeah
fireposeidoncx: f
mashafique: FeelsBadMan
whichtom: keras is actually really easy to use
eldac_kno: f
Penguino138: F
jefft13: @whichtom i only see keras for NNs no?
finnur: F
trenusss: F
Penguino138: The fight for CPU usage
soldierheadsmite: f
thejuror8: @georgehotz Did you try Colab for this kind of stuff ? everytime I have something to run that is on the heavy side I used it, it's very practical
JohnnyWangPepega: f
tauzN: F
whichtom: @jefft13 deep learning yea
superluminal86: apple's fault
maxschneider96: @thejuror8 It was meant to be a provocative question, worked I guess
whichtom: General machine learning is ofc sklearn
tauzN: SAVED PogChamp
mangoxavier: Coming back later
mashafique: we back Pog
Penguino138: Back again
Ne0Zer0: AngelThump
alexlucas__: ayyy
bigie: sure it can. doing deep learning without cuda fucks the CPU up
maxschneider96: back again nice
gamester2665: HELLO MR HOTZ
Mariosavitch: lol
bigie: LUL
Ne0Zer0: LUL
whichtom: LUL
saintmthw: LULW
mashafique: LUL
ky0jinjaeger: LUL LUL
Mariosavitch: Kappa
Jpdd: OMEGALUL
abk467: sayanoHype LUL
Penguino138: Joe biden shut down the stream ;)
danny95djb: LUL
logi6000: we back
gamester2665: lol
gamester2665: <3
fireposeidoncx: lol
Ne0Zer0: all powerful joe
powerofpickle: However, he is a rapist
logi6000: lmfao😅🤣🤣🤣🤣
mangoxavier: Lmao
maxschneider96: mate, why so serious?
bigie: thanks man i haven't laughed like that in a while
ky0jinjaeger: lmao
mangoxavier: Hahahaha
Penguino138: This is MALARKEY!
mashafique: You didn't fake cry Geo
mangoxavier: Invest in tinfoil
maxschneider96: lol
abk467: you were just being sarcastic
powerofpickle: WHY WHY WHY WHY WHY
Mariosavitch: ???
anguscupcake: led street lights are military weapons bro
mashafique: POG
whichtom: ??
inDOObitablee: wut
Mariosavitch: random
GiGnX12: ??
teerv: PogChamp
anguscupcake: good form
Digital_donger: disruptive PogChamp
Mariosavitch: tuck your elbows in
DzyaN_: cmonBruh
mangoxavier: One punch Man U can do it
anguscupcake: burpees are where it's at
Ne0Zer0: mmm Kreygasm
maxschneider96: @anguscupcake burpees ftw yeah
logi6000: apples got you on there botnet. they did it
powerofpickle: Training to fight corn pop
FargioFarmani: When will you start recording Tiktok videos?
bigie: visualize one episode. maybe you'll see a bug or smth
maxschneider96: @FargioFarmani Pls don´t
mangoxavier: George did you watch Devs?
fireposeidoncx: @georgehotz still a logan paul fan?
FargioFarmani: Tiktok is the future
flickapotamus: i did not get notification for this
anguscupcake: WHAT ARE THOSE
maxschneider96: @FargioFarmani dunno, a bit cringey, init?
whichtom: Devs looks like a cool TV show but I cant find anywhere to watch it, which sucks
premell: what do you think of teslas progress towards full autonomy?
Ne0Zer0: LUL
mangoxavier: What server to use for project like this?
whichtom: big fan of alex garland
Talgathy: broken computer unlucky
bigie: the fuck
maxschneider96: @FargioFarmani I mean I like some videos, but most of them are still cringe
ky0jinjaeger: rip apple music
fizziblytwitching: stephen - your life
loouai: geo I know you hate nonsubs but my country is out of money and i use cash only lately
mangoxavier: Whichtom hell yes
Penguino138: Don't forget the pasta
loouai: https://pythondata.com/jupyter-vagrant/
Nelzex: what keeb?
Nelzex: haHAA
Penguino138: Oh the pasta is done already
bigie: why would the GPU be slower ?
Den_dp: apple EleGiggle
bigie: this guyyy
razmastaflex: Are you still in lockdown?
whichtom: still lagging?
neilsweb: I use fastai , so I use pytorch but don't know how to use it at the same time lol
Ne0Zer0: his macbook is literally imploding
Ne0Zer0: LUL
whichtom: is the fan dead again?
Digital_donger: TheIlluminati ...
smurfd0: do you have an update on obs,i saw some other mac guy who had issues until he upgraded obs
Ne0Zer0: Max Powers LUL
Joooooooooonas: why doe sit say 0 dropped frames thou
xeeton: forget the gov, OBS is the one with all the power
Crowz4K: !streamup
Crowz4K: !uptime
whichtom: about to take off
bigie: you need a new PC. possibly one with an nvidia card
Penguino138: Mac fans spinnin
mangoxavier: console log
Mariosavitch: i upgraded obs and shit stopped working too
maxschneider96: Anyone from london wanna sesh tonight?
routerkicker: lag is better now he's turned up the fans
Den_dp: new OBS can stream via GPU btw, That's called NVENC (new)
Joooooooooonas: msi afterburner is decent programm to log
ky0jinjaeger: F-16 taking off in your room?
demonshalo: Thank god I dont have to deal with this MAC shit XD
mangoxavier: activity monitor and press CMD+2
anguscupcake: macs have the best displays tho
yoloswag360noscope: ANELE
GS540: get a pc LUL
mashafique: Just download more RAM
mangoxavier: or Click the app name and go to services and do app leakage or system trace
sceptix1337: tfw geohot realizes apple sucks
whichtom: could use google colab?
bigie: 20 what exactly ?
whichtom: oh huh
whichtom: 20 speed
whichtom: LUL
Ne0Zer0: lmfaooooooooooooooo
Ne0Zer0: LUL
mashafique: LUL
bobsmash: lMAO
sceptix1337: lmaoo
saintmthw: LMFAO
maxschneider96: hahaha
whichtom: wow
anguscupcake: lol
Ne0Zer0: omg that is actually hilarious LUL
FargioFarmani: See this about the MacBook:
Jannnik: LUL
mariusmafius: charge on the right
bigie: LUL i didn't know it was a macbook
FargioFarmani: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=22957573
mangoxavier: ohhhh battery
Penguino138: Joe Biden's leg hair is the mystery
smurfd0: whut, computer needs powerz?
Skyshifter: u looking cute today georgie
funwayz: plug it to the right!
Mantelis0429: LULW
whichtom: oh I saw this on HN
Ne0Zer0: LUL wow
smurfd0: https://i-tweak.blogspot.com/2015/03/disable-cpu-throttling-in-mac-osx.html
anguscupcake: damn
PeinlicherAffe: left or right side? why two sides?
mangoxavier: wow left side isn't thunderbolt capable usbc?
bigie: what the fuck? this is a thing ?
OttoCavalry: LUL
mangoxavier: Battery monitor
Penguino138: hahaha
mariusmafius: not me :)
triple__m: mod me and I can Kappa
OttoCavalry: me :)
bobsmash: you need a power moderator
mangoxavier: you can set up an alert in system preferences
Giammanaco: Hi George from Italy! You are a genius!
Ne0Zer0: your fancy laptop should be telling you that LUL
mangoxavier: when you get down it will tell you
mangoxavier: it's a check box
bigie: I don't have disposable income to buy a macbook george. my laptops have to work LUL
Santiago_LHC: Make a twitch bot that relays your power to chat.
funwayz: power authority
teerv: hotz you are loaded just buy the mac pro 4Head
Digital_donger: someone make a chat bot that OCRs his battery Kappa
whichtom: mac is pretty good otherwise imo
wifestealer_99: Hello George!!!!!
wifestealer_99: where have yo been man...
gaocaandra: so the new approach
gaocaandra: is
mangoxavier: @georgehotz you need to check out the app "Spaces" You are dragging your windows when you can just do cmd+ arrow
gaocaandra: treat molecular dynamics
gaocaandra: like chess?
PeinlicherAffe: @gaocaandra ?
powerofpickle: Tiling wm gang!
maxschneider96: @gaocaandra wdy mean?
PeinlicherAffe: way faster
norB88: going down!!
el_Razor: Hermann Miller chair ?
sceptix1337: number go down
parasite_is_a_snakee: bitcoin mooning PogChamp
gaocaandra: i mean not like chess
xeeton: yay
sceptix1337: hell yeah replay buffer
gaocaandra: but to apply that methodology to choose the best config?
mangoxavier: oh, lmao my bad
eldac_kno: imagine ironic video tutorials where geohot teaches python
Theguywhobea: 👉 📈 PogChamp
miloeu: hi
maxschneider96: @gaocaandra ah gotcha
miloeu: !uptime
PeinlicherAffe: @gaocaandra this has nothing to do with molecular dynamics
gaocaandra: or what is the use of muzero in md?
miloeu: how long has he been online?
gaocaandra: ahhh
sceptix1337: number go down
gaocaandra: he is not with comma bio?
PeinlicherAffe: @gaocaandra commai stuff
Joooooooooonas: Why dont you buy a decent workstation ?
gsgera: so what's going on here?
bigie: so it's off policy monte carlo? what's the difference with e.g. DDPG ?
maxschneider96: I really hope he´ s gonna work with molecular dynamics again
sceptix1337: whats the blue stuff and whats the orange stuff?
miloeu: can you use vim inside jupyter
miloeu: notebook
gaocaandra: i'm guessing the protein didn't fold
Skyshifter: what is he working on with muzero?
sceptix1337: number go up
maxschneider96: @gaocaandra hahaha
miloeu: is this a prerecorded stream
whichtom: polecart
PeinlicherAffe: you need to fold the protein BRO
maxschneider96: @PeinlicherAffe yh
Theguywhobea: NaM
eeXecute: NaM
sceptix1337: you just got nand bro
gaocaandra: NAM
perrierking: what language is this
Ne0Zer0: first he got biden'd now he got nan'd
eeXecute: python
Joooooooooonas: the stream is still lagging thou
parasite_is_a_snakee: how can u not know its python... is it amateur hour over here?
I2btw: pll pay to make pyhton code?
I2btw: is funny
sceptix1337: whats the blue and whats the orange??
bigie: i like model based stuff. i have to check it out
eldac_kno: georgie boi is so cute, dont tell him
sheveeee: O_o
Penguino138: @Joooooooooonas might be your internet, stream seems smooth for me in 1080
sceptix1337: just write the replay buffer man
maxschneider96: @eldac_kno hope u don´ t bust a nut on your monitor rn bro
Joooooooooonas: @Penguino138 oh lol okay, hmm
mangoxavier: I'm just starting to learn python so this shit is blowing my mind right now
diaryofamadmonkey: You're hero George!
bigie: i think that'll fuck things up. as far as i remember basic cartpole also ends if you balance it for 10 frames or smth. not sure though
sceptix1337: number go moon
ozychhicodes: yo can you show us your key board please mr hot?
ozychhicodes: I'm just kidding
PeinlicherAffe: xD
superuserg: where I can find news on algorithms research and the like?
maxschneider96: @PeinlicherAffe R u german?
PeinlicherAffe: klärchen GunRun 7
Famousix: !commands
maxschneider96: I´ m austria, but I´ m living in london
maxschneider96: austrian
bigie: shit this also does monte carlo tree search?
whichtom: r/machinelearning is good for ml research
PeinlicherAffe: @maxschneider96 cool cool :)
sceptix1337: why do you need monte carlo for balancing a stick
superuserg: @whichtom thanks, I will take a look into that
I2btw: Is this Cobol programming?
maxschneider96: @PeinlicherAffe I sometimes wish I was in austria or germany again, they´ re dealing so much better w the current situation than the UK and the US
PeinlicherAffe: @maxschneider96 overall not easy :/
ELEMENTiQ1337: ELEMENTiQ1337 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 2 month streak! oh hi there, I finally catched your stream
sceptix1337: the next episode
maxschneider96: @PeinlicherAffe besonders mit Boris und Donald
whichtom: its not super bad in the UK
PeinlicherAffe: @maxschneider96 yo :D
Santiago_LHC: Have you guys seen the show Devs? It's about determinism and the simulation.
whichtom: just want quarantine to be over man, it sucks
parasite_is_a_snakee: @whichtom only 20k dead not that bad BloodTrail
I2btw: Imaging having a german sound name
whichtom: could be worse
I2btw: muha
ELEMENTiQ1337: @I2btw i do bruh
PeinlicherAffe: GunRun
maxschneider96: @whichtom yeah, but I´ ll at least have a private sesh today in london
whichtom: private sesh? @maxschneider96
I2btw: schneider
vexedkiller0071: wtf I left my computer on
parasite_is_a_snakee: he means a gay orgy
sceptix1337: replay buffer is love, replay buffer is life
maxschneider96: @whichtom yeah w people from my student accomodation
vexedkiller0071: who raided you?
Santiago_LHC: Don't touch your face, George
whichtom: ahh
Legardovia: hi
maxschneider96: @whichtom wanna join haha
whichtom: nah lol thanks
maxschneider96: haha
parasite_is_a_snakee: sesh aka gay orgy 4Head
PeinlicherAffe: @maxschneider96 what are you talking about?
PeinlicherAffe: @parasite_is_a_snakee lel
maxschneider96: @parasite_is_a_snakee my backdoor´ s only designed for exit
maxschneider96: @PeinlicherAffe small party...
PeinlicherAffe: k
Skyshifter: sounds like me
truemorpheuz: @PeinlicherAffe wtf
PeinlicherAffe: Jebaited
bigie: i don't know about the tree search part but that definitely happens without replay buffer. it doesn't revisit the good states without one
PeinlicherAffe: @진정한모피어스 kene lust mehr auf fedor? LUL
truemorpheuz: @PeinlicherAffe stalkst du mich ? WutFace
PeinlicherAffe: du mich cmonBruh
truemorpheuz: @PeinlicherAffe ne
sceptix1337: replay buffer is love, replay buffer is life
PeinlicherAffe: @진정한모피어스 cool that we share same interests :)
truemorpheuz: @PeinlicherAffe yes :)
PeinlicherAffe: @진정한모피어스 kiss now? :)
truemorpheuz: @PeinlicherAffe sure :)
PeinlicherAffe: @진정한모피어스 cool :)
sceptix1337: this just got real
truemorpheuz: @PeinlicherAffe yes :)
PeinlicherAffe: @진정한모피어스 very yes :)
alfantasticdd: I just understand the half of it but I thank you for streaming this stuff. 100% better than wasting time while watching games!
PeinlicherAffe: true
abedbawsxx: I don't understand a thing, also what's nine plus ten
samuriia: !uptime
gaocaandra: only english in chat bro
SVANI70: rayintKawaii rayintKawaii
PeinlicherAffe: @gaocaandra sorry bro
abedbawsxx: only english in chat please Kappa
samuriia: What’s the command to see how long he been stream for
JysonJeh3: hi
maxschneider96: What are the best machine - & deep learning courses out there? I am a biochemist, but I wanna get into artificial intelligence for drug discovery.
gaocaandra: andrew ng course
ozychhicodes: @georgehotz can you name variables a bit more meaningfully pleas,e it'll be much easier to follow
gaocaandra: is a good intro
DasMastah: What's with the double "if done"?
parasite_is_a_snakee: looking for a course u already fucked up
gaocaandra: you learn by doing
minichota: @ozychhicodes he never does lmao
gaocaandra: you see what george is doing
maxschneider96: @gaocaandra I have created some machine learning models already, maybe something more advanced
bigie: it's meaningful in reeinforcement learning. v= value, s = state, a = action, p = probability
gaocaandra: that is how you learn
parasite_is_a_snakee: @maxschneider96 why dont u google it
maxschneider96: @gaocaandra That´ s why I´ m watching bro
gaocaandra: me too
gaocaandra: learning how to learn
gaocaandra: also good asmr
maxschneider96: @parasite_is_a_snakee wanted to have some opinions
graszewek: !uptime
gaocaandra: to work
gaocaandra: on the fucking weekend
whichtom: look at what people have already done, look at open source code
alfantasticdd: @bigie thanks for the explaination
whichtom: just search for keywords
maxschneider96: @whichtom thanks
eldac_kno: sorry if this was asked, thoughts on Yandex Cars?
sceptix1337: no never
whichtom: courses and stuff really aren't that useful imo
socialnotsocial: @georgehotz what is your sleeping schedule like? you seem to have high energy. Do you avoid stimulants also?
gaocaandra: he does coke and ritalin
whichtom: paid stuff at least. There is so much free content/tutorials/open source code/papers
brisingr1031: @georgehotz semicolon on get_training_epsiode
I2btw: SHow feet kaceyFist
PeinlicherAffe: @gaocaandra LUL
gaocaandra: for breakfast
ozychhicodes: @socialnotsocial adderall is a hell of a drug
sceptix1337: crippling ketamine addiction
brisingr1031: colon*
samuriia: @socialnotsocial adderal
whichtom: eating ice is his drug
sceptix1337: true
gaocaandra: why does everyone assume he is high
PeinlicherAffe: and limes
truemorpheuz: think its cocaine, code, sleep repeat
gaocaandra: all the time
maxschneider96: @sceptix1337 ketamine ftw
PeinlicherAffe: @gaocaandra lel you did
gaocaandra: if he were high he wouldn't reason sol well
ozychhicodes: How's ketamine even relevant here
PeinlicherAffe: highs are different @gaocaandra
Featen: someone tldr what is he doing?
gaocaandra: i work on weed
gaocaandra: for example
truemorpheuz: i too
gaocaandra: but the guy isn't on coke
samuriia: @gaocaandra have u ever been high lmao
PeinlicherAffe: horse anesthetic 4Head
gaocaandra: just because he types fast
maxschneider96: @ozychhicodes It´ s being tested for psychiatric disorders
elmixy: LUL
I2btw: This text editor is very responsive
ozychhicodes: time for stress eating
truemorpheuz: fentanyl
sceptix1337: recreational heroine
norB88: krokodil
Mariosavitch: ice cream... love being an adult
bigie: wait is the action part right? your network outputs the probability of choosing the action "1" ?
grahamstephan420: desomorphine
PeinlicherAffe: 🐊
ozychhicodes: why is he chewing with his front teeth
swftdev: asmr
PeinlicherAffe: @ozychhicodes he is addict
I2btw: desomorphine is this not more in a negavice way
gaocaandra: for more pleasure
I2btw: t
Vrookems: codeine squad
gaocaandra: the coke makes you feel flavor on the teeth
lexxy23: small amount, already 3 tablespoons full of ice cream
bSnatch: What programming language is this?
PeinlicherAffe: 🐍
eldac_kno: what do you think gonna be the core of AGI
grahamstephan420: Desomorphine is chemically pure krokodil
whichtom: we are so far from AGI, who knows
I2btw: i love phyton for UI. This is all i have to say about this fuck up
maxschneider96: @bSnatch python
whichtom: the current big research labs have little idea of how to get there
maxschneider96: the best
v0sn: wow george you are looking so good today!
bigie: does search return the probability of choosing "right" ?
parasite_is_a_snakee: @v0sn its the hair
buicy_jooty: !uptime
parasite_is_a_snakee: dont cut the hair george u look sexy
v0sn: indeed
liesai: yo bro
eldac_kno: i think its gonna be machine fo math proofs
I2btw: emilyccIRSS emilyccIRSS emilyccIRSS
emmbeezy: could you do a comprehensive tutorial how to follow scientific papers for coding?
brisingr1031: !commands
PeinlicherAffe: @emmbeezy turnup
eldac_kno: agi gonna crack the riehmann hypothesis
PythonNoob: is openpilot write in python ?
whichtom: AGI is a really weird topic for discussion anyway. who even knows if the singularity will come about even with AGI/ASI
PeinlicherAffe: @PythonNoob yes
emmbeezy: @PeinlicherAffe ?
grahamstephan420: Ops pilot is written in perl
tessier_ashp00l: anyone got the link to the paper he has up on screen?
sceptix1337: openpilot is written in asm
whichtom: its all guessing based on science fiction
eldac_kno: openpilot is written in Pascal
whichtom: afaik no one is _actually_ researching it
crawcraw66: what's up with that syntax? for _ in range?
norB88: https://arxiv.org/abs/1911.08265
PeinlicherAffe: @emmbeezy thought you were german and knew money boy, nvm
maxschneider96: @PeinlicherAffe money boy is austrian
sceptix1337: wer moneyboy nicht mag, liegt bald im sarg
whichtom: _ is like a blank variable
v0sn: skrt
emmbeezy: scurr?
PeinlicherAffe: sceptix1337 hat verstanden
sceptix1337: skrr skrr
ido_nvidia: @crawcraw66 where he doesnt care for the item just wanna iterate for the number of items
maxschneider96: @sceptix1337 hahaha
PeinlicherAffe: germans take over monkaS
crawcraw66: @ido_nvidia ohh ok thx
Keyeh: number going down Pog
TasosTheLord: TasosTheLord subscribed at Tier 1.
v0sn: deutsche an die macht
pelegogrosso: what is he doing?
TasosTheLord: PrideHi
PeinlicherAffe: 🇩🇪 7
sceptix1337: hes balancing a stick lol
whichtom: yea no point assigning an actual variable if it wont be used, so use _
grahamstephan420: subscribed at Tier 0
dontbeameme: Gg
bigie: @whichtom the main goal of openai is to find AGI
sceptix1337: using some overengineered ai stuff
ido_nvidia: yep
tessier_ashp00l: TY
whichtom: @bigie i have yet to see any good work towards it
whichtom: apart from overhyped press releases with little new work
whichtom: also renamed to 'closedai'
whichtom: openai is such a scam
bigie: their language model is pretty good. their dota thing was amazing. i don't know how it's a scam
Maw3rick: monkaS
doganigooo2: helloo
kerediax: not a scam but pretty overhyped imo
doganigooo2: what happen to covid research
gaocaandra: it died
crawcraw66: so what is the algorithm meant to do? balance that stick/
whichtom: the dota thing was kinda disingenuous b/c of how many limitations were placed on the system
gaocaandra: we are now a tree search cooperative
sceptix1337: battery number go up
whichtom: GPT-2 is interesting yea, but how they went about it leaves a bad taste in my mouth
bigie: yes but if you don't force the agent's hand in a big state space like that it won't work. same with starcraft and deepmind
god_damn: PogChamp 📈
eldac_kno: gpt 2 is defintely not future
whichtom: which is fine, just don't advertise it as solved
eldac_kno: it doesnt understand text
TasosTheLord: just fold the stick man
whichtom: Deepmind's SC2 agents are pretty bad still
sceptix1337: lmao
whichtom: when it was playing in the ladder, a lot of people found it was shit
gaocaandra: all of "machine learning" is sortof snake oil
itsPhlu: hey george
whichtom: but they still went around saying they solved it
gaocaandra: it does work
gaocaandra: but its very limited
gaocaandra: and overhyped
mangoxavier: What can I do to prevent models being built for me in order to manipulate me (IoT). Other than just blocking ads
whichtom: yea
ido_nvidia: some of it works really well tho
whichtom: incredibly overhyped
ido_nvidia: what about alpha go tho?
bigie: no one claimed they solved it. openai failed vs. pro teams. it's just the big leap from atari games
gaocaandra: but thats the context
whichtom: yea true
gaocaandra: at this point in history
god_damn: i'm not really understanding, why would he turn himslef into a pickle
whichtom: even w/ atari games, most algorithms published struggle with sparse rewards
gaocaandra: we are headed towards another winter
itsPhlu: lmfao
bigie: the people around it who didn't understand what was going on overhyped it. AI is in general overhyped bcs of it
whichtom: even this one, muzero, struggles with most which is why most algorithms don't count all of the atari games
maxschneider96: @gaocaandra I wish there were sometimes better sources to figure out which model to use
itsPhlu: lol
gaocaandra: which will go unnoticed beacus these tools altough overhyped can have a great impact in accesibility
itsPhlu: hi george
whichtom: struggles with a few sorry*
itsPhlu: hi mr hotz
itsPhlu: u kinda cute
whichtom: like montezumas revenge and pitfall
sceptix1337: is this reinforcement learning
eldac_kno: GPT 2 doesnt "understand" text
itsPhlu: just use a bypass 3+
gaocaandra: because
ido_nvidia: yes
whichtom: alphago is cool ye I'll admit
PythonNoob: what is hes leyboard ?
gaocaandra: these algorithms are learning a function thet describes the statiscal distribution of a LIMITED dataset
itsPhlu: !
gaocaandra: thats inherently limited
cybergenik: @georgehotz what kb do you use?
itsPhlu: !kb
itsPhlu: !keyboarddd
itsPhlu: dont work
tensorspac3: why?
gaocaandra: you are't learning t speack
itsPhlu: help
raisedbyphantom: what is he doing
whichtom: the media keeps overhyping/misunderstanding openai's work but openai doesn't really do anything to correct them
itsPhlu: helpll
bigie: the games are usually pretty complex compared to what people use it for. DDPG is used for robot arm control but might suck ass at dota
Mariosavitch: nothing @raisedbyphantom
orami: i believe he has an hhkb
PeinlicherAffe: @whichtom not his problem if he gets free promo
whichtom: yea generalization is obviously the biggest requirement for AGI that hasnt been met
gaocaandra: altough it beats kasparov in chess it doesn't know to 'play' chess
gaocaandra: that diference is subtle
bigie: AGI is not gonna happen without a big push from neuroscience but people are working on it.
whichtom: thats kinda philosophical
gaocaandra: that difference is the diference between AGI and ML
miloeu: is someone familiar with JS in .pdf files?
whichtom: do _we_ really know how to play chess, other than respond to inputs with some output
sceptix1337: you just need more compute for agi
whichtom: if we act instinctually, do we understand what we did
bigie: @georgehotz what does search() do in run_episode()? seems like you expect it to return the probability of tatking the action "1"
whichtom: @bigie ya I agree, need way more work in neuroscience
gaocaandra: I mean
bigie: ah ok makes sense now
sceptix1337: try leaning the stick and make some test cases if search() distribution makes sense
gaocaandra: the idea that a neuron firing in the brain is somehow equivalent to a linear function encased in a nonlinear functiom
gaocaandra: is ignorant of all the nuances
whichtom: oh yeah its not 1-to-1
CoachMeech: GOAT SHIT
gaocaandra: and processes that take place
bigie: @whichtom listel to lex friedman's podcast. there's a lot of work being put into AGI but mostly in neuroscience. it'll take a long long time
gaocaandra: on a human brain
maxschneider96: Hoping for deep reasoning to properly happen in 2020
metis_zver: Hi, what's your monitor?
emmbeezy: @georgehotz do you have a git where you publish these things?
whichtom: oh yeah Ive watched a lot of episodes of the AI podcast @bigie
PeinlicherAffe: funfact: you can't compute the total number of possibilities in chess. there's is an estimate/lower bound of 10^120 states (look shannon number) but probably way more
whichtom: its fantastic
sceptix1337: you just need more compute
whichtom: @emmbeezy geohot on github
gaocaandra: i think that AGI will emerge from a cellular automata
CoachMeech: what is a george hotz?
gaocaandra: and feed us all
gaocaandra: corn
sceptix1337: kb boss
sceptix1337: return loss 0 big brain
whichtom: thats actually how I found geo, through lex
maxschneider96: @whichtom great podcast
bigie: that was a fun episode
I2btw: You sub to e-girls @georgehotz ?
whichtom: yea lol
chaprio1: @georgehotz what do you think about zoom LUL
abhinavneelam: !bet 20
sceptix1337: do you train the network with the stick falling over just one time?
pwnbase: pwnbase subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 2 month streak! primeagenAJasm
I2btw: kandyFinduz
maxschneider96: are u already working on the artificial intelligence brothels u talked about with lex fridman?
I2btw: Pll sponser me my sub
Mrkz_: Hey everyone :) What's the topic of today?
bigie: the network represent an agent. the environment just tells it if it did "good" or "bad" using the reward function. it has to figure out what to do @sceptix1337
I2btw: mcretIQ
miths: miths subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months!
sceptix1337: i get that but if he only trains it once its never gonna learn
sceptix1337: stick has to fall over many times
Muahmli: HEYYYYYY
eyep1e: still using HHKB?
bigie: he runs it more than once but not a lot because it's not learning
sceptix1337: ok
jacekakacz: George what do you think about RaspberyyPi?
eyep1e: lmao
sceptix1337: check if your search returns a good distribution
Bootstraps: is this still part of the corona virus reverse engineering
Ne0Zer0: LUL
bigie: LUL denied
mashafique: LUL
whichtom: @Bootstraps nah
Skyshifter: monkaS
socialnotsocial: @georgehotz what is your sleeping schedule like? you seem to have high energy. Do you avoid stimulants also or not?
eyep1e: 3,2,1 bye
yoloswag360noscope: D:
DiiCE3: pwned
miloeu: f in chat LULW
PythonNoob: i remember goehot from ps3 crack ...
Penguino138: @georgehotz you drinking green tea?
eyep1e: someones next
gaocaandra: it's the fast typing
gaocaandra: they can't imagine
gaocaandra: being able to
sceptix1337: they cant handle 200wpm
ofaas: do you supplement
eyep1e: the energy comes from wearing a black hoodie
mangoxavier: George has already said that drugs only let you explore inside yourself. There's no point to that with what he's doing right now.
bigie: i wanna be on drugs but they're hard to get with the quarantine. bullshit
calcmath: can you somehow visualise the model of the environment that is learnt
gent03: FREE MY BOY QUICKFLOOR
PythonNoob: @bigie thats true ....
sceptix1337: george your search function is bad
Skyshifter: quickfloor was just a memer BibleThump
PythonNoob: @bigie harder to find and more expensive .... way more...
malmeani: malmeani subscribed at Tier 1.
bigie: yep...
raulciuntastefan: is kratom good ?
truemorpheuz: @raulciuntastefan no
mangoxavier: kratom doesn't do much IMO
truemorpheuz: its bad
eyep1e: caffeine is all i need
mangoxavier: can make you angry after taking it and screw with your blood pressure
Skyshifter: yea i just snort coffee powder
eyep1e: im young work out daily and meditate twice a day, im sorted
sceptix1337: moar compute!
calcmath: increase capacity of model?
eyep1e: whats wrong with the search function @sceptix1337
whichtom: what was that biohacking thing before, applying UV to the forehead?
ajnoom: yo
washuash: good morning from estonia
sceptix1337: distribution not normalized
washuash: what are we doing today
ajnoom: !followsince
CoachMeech: GEORGE
ajnoom: !followage
whichtom: you can click your name and see follow age
bigie: 80 seems pretty good to me
sceptix1337: stick go balance
mangoxavier: great
Skyshifter: Pog
whichtom: w o w
norB88: boom
mangoxavier: he knows kung fu
yuptheladsdownthecans: PogChamp
pwnbase: STICKO MODE
ofaas: i was here
Digital_donger: balanced stick PogChamp
sceptix1337: check if it works with gravity increased
Santiago_LHC: GG
mangoxavier: lmao sticko mode haha
god_damn: thats incredible, i guess terminator really is going to happen
Mrkz_: !uptime
PsycopathSurgon: thank you for every Jail Break you made ,you really helped me for the country i used to live in has no app store access :)
sondreal: sondreal subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 9 months! 9 months PogChamp
eyep1e: cha-ching
Skyshifter: AI has now achieved the balance of a child's brain
ky0jinjaeger: why use lot word when few word do trick?
Ne0Zer0: PogChamp
sceptix1337: that was me
mangoxavier: @pwnbase he's got a new single with Kid Cuddi
ez_clappers_: me :)
god_damn: that was @quickfloor may he rest in peace
parasite_is_a_snakee: me :)
sleep_waIk: Hey orbWave
mangoxavier: I am spartacus
Skyshifter: 1 step close to the turing test monkaS
Santiago_LHC: Is there a github repo for today's twitch?
brkydnc: do you upload every stream yo do ?
maxschneider96: When will AI replace barbers? Can´ t get my hair cut during the lockdown...
sceptix1337: what did you even change lol
Penguino138: @brkydnc Comma AI Archive does on YT
brkydnc: thanks!
whichtom: @Santiago_LHC check the geohot github on geohot/ai-notebooks
mangoxavier: Will George be secluded to a compound in Alaska and drink all day and then run some lottery for his company where a guy comes and interacts with the stick but falls in love with the stick?
Dai_Vern0n: why does it stop?
god_damn: @Dai_Vern0n it get bored after 82
mangoxavier: Put a wig on the stick
TasosTheLord: NotLikeThis
Joooooooooonas: So what are we gonna do PogChamp
sceptix1337: make the stick a dick
mangoxavier: dat can be dat
mangoxavier: dis n dat
sceptix1337: can this balance stick in real time
Skyshifter: how many sims till the AI breaks out of its sandbox and beats u with the stick for making it do this menial shit for hours?
mangoxavier: a stick beating someone with a stick is meta af
logi6000: how was the alpha go movie
sceptix1337: wouldnt the cartpool hit him
sceptix1337: that looked smooth af
mangoxavier: alpha go movie is amazing
CoachMeech: NICE
mangoxavier: if you learn to play the game it will blow your mind
erichtp: extend stick length will it understand stick then
sceptix1337: now make it balance stick attached to stick
mangoxavier: it's mind blowing regardless but really useful to get a glimpse into how they layer ai and machine learning
sceptix1337: yeah lets go
sceptix1337: stick on stick
bigie: cartpole episode termination: length is greater than 200 (500 for v1). so your max score is around 200 i guess
sondreal: Remember to subscibe, its a really good investment boiiis! PogChamp
calcmath: can you try for longern than 100?
logi6000: @sondreal subs have bigger dix
Featen: rip
Skyshifter: surely the AI should be able to balance the stick perfectly eventually right? like no movement?
sondreal: logi6000 true
sceptix1337: local minimum go brrr
logi6000: stick balancer go brr
simmy7: simmy7 subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 5 months!
calcmath: maybe neural network got bad initial weights
eldac_kno: are you gonna go on JRE
sun_is_not_yellow: !uptime
logi6000: @eldac_kno he probably won't
Featen: gamma?
eldac_kno: it would awesome tho
god_damn: @eldac_kno yeah cant wait to hear what he thinks about the ferguson fight
logi6000: @god_damn lol
calcmath: reinitialize the neuralnetwork between runs
Featen: go lower
eldac_kno: elk meat
sceptix1337: make an ai that finds the best gammi
sceptix1337: gamma
tessier_ashp00l: forget, JRE, do The Portal
Silodox: oh hey, sup hotz. i had you followed not when your first stream would be
Silodox: i vibe with your energy tho
eldac_kno: eric weinstein is a fraud sorry
tessier_ashp00l: i know
calcmath: you need to recompile the keras model to reinitialize neural networks weights otherwise it will always be stuck in local minima
whichtom: how is eric a fraud?
eldac_kno: he dont want publish paper on his "breaktrough" theory
god_damn: i miss 82
tessier_ashp00l: see if gh calls him on his shit
gigafact: It's nice to finally catch the stream live. We see some disconnects happened during the stream so more work for us to sync chat ect when uploading to youtube...
bigie: LUL what happened
Silodox: that is programming in a nutshell when you want to make edits, "hey yeah remember that time when it worked"
Silodox: lmao
eldac_kno: geohot is not a physiciat lol
Featen: "calcmath: you need to recompile the keras model to reinitialize neural networks weights otherwise it will always be stuck in local minima" ?
mangoxavier: mangoxavier subscribed with Twitch Prime.
tessier_ashp00l: doesnt take a physicist to see he is a crank
mangoxavier: nice
dps910: hi
calcmath: You are just stuck inlocal minima, need to reinitialize weights
sceptix1337: local minimum go brr
eldac_kno: i mean there should be a paper and then physicist gonna make peer review and decide whether it is legit or not
tessier_ashp00l: there will never be a paper, thats the thing
Joselinis: all you need is lofi to make this work
eldac_kno: just publishing youtube video of your lecture is not a legit way to present your theory
Fr0zenOfficial: hello, what are you programming right now?
whichtom: I mean submitting papers for review is kinda a scam in itself but yea
whichtom: given reviewers are sometimes stupid and academia is wack but I get it
mangoxavier: That was easy, is prime sub okay too?
calcmath: please reinitialize ur NN
Featen: " @calcmath : you need to recompile the keras model to reinitialize neural networks weights otherwise it will always be stuck in local minima"
sceptix1337: geohot uses reinitalize! its very effective!
eldac_kno: perelman did paper, why eric is above that
bigie: yeah it shouldn't be that sensitive to hyperparameters.
whichtom: who knows
calcmath: thanks featen
tessier_ashp00l: eric is only looking for followers and fame
Silodox: hey to be fair the atari jaguar WAS kinda swink swank groovy tho
whichtom: a paper is a good idea anyways to formalize/convey ideas better
routerkicker: Peer review is utter shit but he could at least porst his paper on the internet. As long as he doesn't do that he's a scam to me.
whichtom: you don't go into physics/math for followers and fame lol
Waldoqq: HEY EVERYONE LOOK AT ME
mangoxavier: hi
Featen: @georgehotz " @calcmath : you need to recompile the keras model to reinitialize neural networks weights otherwise it will always be stuck in local minima"
calcmath: he will eventually restart kernel and it will reinitilize his model and it will work
gigafact: George did you watch the new Karpathy talk about TeslaAI? it was very interesting...
whichtom: like wolfram published his ideas and people tore him apart
auron018: greetings from albania!
sceptix1337: reinitialize my man
whichtom: 'published' I mean informally
jimbofreak: wouldn't adding one more stick to the system make everything way more complicated due to the fact that two sticks attached to a point show chaotic behavior?
sceptix1337: thats the point
routerkicker: doesn't matter. if the theorie's right people will have to eat their words eventually.
sceptix1337: we want to see if ai can solve advanced physics
mannekchin: HeyGuys
calcmath: keep trying different inits
eldac_kno: it already solves some of it
sceptix1337: this is like the villin, the initial position is bad for folding, you need to pull the stick at both ends
Featen: refit starts in local minimum already
mangoxavier: ohhhhh is this a Joe Baiden ai?
calcmath: NN are finicky like that, need to try many inits
calcmath: or make them wder
calcmath: wider*
mangoxavier: A stick that keeps forgetting
sceptix1337: search is bugged
sceptix1337: im callin it
mannekchin: Kappa
mannekchin: i wonder when he going to read this Kappa
sceptix1337: the cartpool isnt getting enough credit tbh
bigie: cartpole starts at upright so if it's ending at ~20 it's either going out of bounds facing down for 180 steps. probably the first one
bigie: *or facing down
curr1wurst: I wish I could code like him...
supplydemand88: sup
eldac_kno: just practice more
sceptix1337: back to the high numbers bois
supplydemand88: george what do you think is the best way to do (dis)similarity measures in python for ts? DTW, EDR or?
sceptix1337: nvm
mannekchin: for a begginer, what do you see that allows you to say wheter its elarning or not?
calcmath: is learning rate too high?
calcmath: the first number shoudl go down, second number should go up
norB88: https://gist.github.com/crizCraig/ec806f0d606c9e727512dce886bdc966
sceptix1337: number dont go right >:(
sceptix1337: why is there 0.00 and 0.99
sceptix1337: seems extreme
bigie: it should also usually have some random walk
calcmath: its not trained properly, so it wont make sense
pedrosantos867: guys what is this ide name
pedrosantos867: named?
nsielicki: that's jupyter
calcmath: jupyter
whichtom: its in a jupyter notebook
Ipkstef: hello what are weorking on today>?
eldac_kno: jew peter
sceptix1337: make the policy so the cartpool isnt rewarded for small movements
eldac_kno: funny?
bigie: maybe ye should also put a size limit on your replay buffer. they're talking about priority queue though so im not sure
Featen: isnt it just overfitting?
sceptix1337: those numbers look better
calcmath: if loss is decreasing but value is not increasing, yeah it seems like overfit
sceptix1337: restart kernel
THX1342: what framework is he using here? keraws?
THX1342: *keras
sceptix1337: it overfits to the stick being perfectly balanced
fearofcode: "Grrr" - also my experience with evolutionary computation
melahii: what do u think about colab
sceptix1337: it needs more tilt
calcmath: change number of layers/ number of neurons?
sceptix1337: use cuda
phelipe3: yo!
mannekchin: dont bother, he doesnt read chat PepeLaugh
bigie: bad policies can fill the replay buffer with garbage which makes the policy even worse
eldac_kno: he reads only useful comments made by Subscribers
sceptix1337: play with the replay buffer size
Emma_Cakes: Good evening :)
calcmath: bad policies dictate how action space is explored right?
timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be
sceptix1337: ^
timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny
nsielicki: if <...> len(replay_buffer) < 10: replay_buffer = replay_buffer[0:50] ???
sceptix1337: ikr seems like oob access
timeiskey: GO READ MY MESSAGE AAAG
lord_alpaca_666: I am glad this is no longer a subscriber only chat. Thank you, george.
timeiskey: THE TAB ON mu.fit is ONE TO THE LEFT
C4TFive: how that match stick treating you george?
calcmath: i think fit should be outside that loop right
nsielicki: read chat^^^^ indentation bug
eldac_kno: big brain energy right there
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz There is this good book which might help you: "Deep Reinforcement Learning in Action"
sceptix1337: yeah sure hes just gonna read the book now
eldac_kno: is Art of programming worth studying?
calcmath: i think he prefers to learns hthings by doing
FargioFarmani: its new
ortunado: its like March 2020
ortunado: i think
MoProject: ho
sceptix1337: audit the search function
死ね: can u do a rice overview real quick?
fancyslimshady: youtube
sceptix1337: thats what im betting on
justcrash: hotz's stream and my life suddenly stops being miserable
timeiskey: MR HOTZ, you gotta fit the replays INDIVIDUALLY. SEQUENTIALLY. NOT IN A BATCH FIT
timeiskey: AAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHH
nsielicki: george, read timeiskey messages above, you have a simple bug
PeinlicherAffe: BRO SEQUENTIALLY
cankoloz: @timeiskey LUL
knicked: SEQUENTIALLY BRO
Featen: BRO
eldac_kno: read timeiskey message
timeiskey: SEQUENTIALLY
alextodoroki: based retard not reading chat
eldac_kno: TIMEISKEY MESSAGE
sceptix1337: policy is also important guys
h1lfiger: yo geo!
dontbeameme: 200iq
calcmath: lol he is gutting his code now
raystriker98: damn he's still on it?
sceptix1337: still balancing a stick
timeiskey: MSE IS AVERAGING YOUR EXPERIENCES T_T
eldac_kno: lol
nsielicki: wow this is lame read the fucking chat george
Artara_: most interactive twitch chat LUL
sceptix1337: try policy, if that dont work listen to timeiskey
cankoloz: he is changing shit right now, he reads in between
eldac_kno: it's like watching hitchcock movie
7Locrian7: he's focused
32bitrobo: <3 VoHiYo PogChamp CurseLit
Pedi: @7Locrian7 +1
nsielicki: i'm just worried that once he gets around to chat it's gonna be off his screen and he's not going to see it.
ortunado: @7Locrian7 i dont think so, we dont see green tea
calcmath: so what you are saying is you should train on one experience replay at a time?
justcrash: just write the n word and he will be alerted in seconds
timeiskey: lets vote with spam
alextodoroki: LOL
7Locrian7: monkaS
FargioFarmani: naughty
sceptix1337: vote with sperm
ozychhicodes: There's no 3
fearofcode: would it help to compare to possible working implementations like https://github.com/werner-duvaud/muzero-general/blob/master/games/cartpole.py ?
timeiskey: you gotta fit the replays individually sequentially not in a batch fit
eldac_kno: georgi boi is such qt when focused
timeiskey: spam go
norB88: @timeiskey shouldnt you have both? Individual and batched?
sceptix1337: SEQUENTIALLY
cankoloz: @georgehotz someone said you shouldn't fit to batch, should do sequentially
timeiskey: SEQUENTIALLY
eldac_kno: SEQUENTIALLY
justcrash: HAHAHAHAHA
routerkicker: you gotta fit the replays individually sequentially not in a batch fit
nsielicki: lmfao
alextodoroki: SCROLL UP AND READ TIMEISKEY'S CHAT YA DINGUS
knicked: SEQUENTIALLY
erlsek: hahaha
justcrash: oh my god im crying
eldac_kno: rofl
cankoloz: Pepega
eldac_kno: F
nsielicki: F
knicked: F
timeiskey: F
sceptix1337: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny
justcrash: F
Joselinis: F
inDOObitablee: ignored
justcrash: HE WILL LITERALLY WIPE OUT THIS WHOLE CODE
MacoNighto: Yo it's geohot and for those that don't know...
ozychhicodes: Why do you have "mse", "mse" twice?
sceptix1337: im getting sued by sony
justcrash: @MacoNighto LOL
MacoNighto: haha
cankoloz: Just delete the whole code 4Head
死ね: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny
alextodoroki: george hotz i'm simply appalled at the levels of mental handicapped that you have reached on this stream
erlsek: ahahahahanm
justcrash: hahahhaa @alextodoroki
sceptix1337: no dont mse
timeiskey: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny
justcrash: im fucking choking
sceptix1337: youre making god sad
nsielicki: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny
erlsek: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny
MacoNighto: :D
死ね: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny.
sceptix1337: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny
justcrash: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny.
whichtom: chat no
hardtarget4: never gonna break out of the simulation at this rate Kappa
knicked: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny.
eldac_kno: : timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny.
alextodoroki: Cheer1 does cheer1 get text to speech haha anyway sequentially bro
buzzind99: PepeLaugh OH NO NO NO
justcrash: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny..
fearofcode: chat is mean :(
eldac_kno: : timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny. Twitch Primewhichtom:
sceptix1337: legally blind lmao
inDOObitablee: READ CHAT
justcrash: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny.
ozychhicodes: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny. Twitch Primewhichtom:
mejhem: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny..
nsielicki: timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny
whichtom: he'll get there eventually
eldac_kno: : timeiskey: are you doing old fashioned experience replay? if yes, make sure to fit each experience individually, not in a batch, or the errors will be MSE'd and be like 1/K the size they should be sceptix1337: ^ timeiskey: it looks like you are forwarding them all in a batch, so your error will be too tiny.
erlsek: PLEASE READ
erlsek: finally
sceptix1337: finally
WearyBread: hello there
justcrash: HAHAHAHAHA
erlsek: hjmkahja
justcrash: NOOOOOOOOOOOOO
sceptix1337: XDDD
alextodoroki: LOL
ozychhicodes: well, we got that
mejhem: LUL
nsielicki: only took TEN MINUTES
ortunado: @timeiskey get rekt monkaS
alextodoroki: fucking based
cankoloz: Way too dank
timeiskey: you are batching your mu.fit
calcmath: tbh i am nost sure the comment makes sense
eldac_kno: LUL
calcmath: why is batch wrong?
timeiskey: tab mu.fit into the FOR LOOP
justcrash: IT TOOK TEN MINUTES TO MAKE HIM SAY THAT HE DOESNT UNDERSTAND :LUL:
horndeski: What are you programming?
sceptix1337: youre batching your error and you lose all learning that way
hardtarget4: son of a
Joselinis: f
erlsek: oh no
timeiskey: he is essentially only getting one replay per batch
ozychhicodes: @horndeski this is not programming channel, this is modify a random value, comment some code out and try again channel
Featen: add tab to fit
FargioFarmani: please repaste all: tab mu.fit into the FOR LOOP
t00big2fl4il: !uptime
calcmath: oh so the same replay is being used for the entire batch?
eldac_kno: tab mu.fit into the FOR LOOP
calcmath: ahh ok makes sense
Featen: add tab in fit line
ozychhicodes: oh man i cant take this any more
calcmath: but arbitrary scaling doesn not matter right?
ozychhicodes: why is he trying to force fix this without understanding
t00big2fl4il: yo what up?
erlsek: print loss
nsielicki: double dared
ozychhicodes: print loss
calcmath: he is already printing the loss
Pedi: I'm entertained, keep going chat
ortunado: @calcmath i dont think the scammers understand it LUL
calcmath: lol
ROXASBrandon: I understand why he doesn't read chat, you guys are toxic asf
t00big2fl4il: Are you writing a program to calculate the risk of inflation due to the ever expanding national debt?
nsielicki: over iterations he means
lpdon2: deep learning in a nutshell
milcapone: hello from Greece. i dont understand programming but love when you discuss various things in our society!
justcrash: rip
frunkAF: oh shit
Subonik: monkaS
Pedi: LUL
justcrash: he literally banned them
PeinlicherAffe: monkaS
Ne0Zer0: LUL
b2kemann: we are still going!! awsm
whichtom: LUL
I2btw: georgehotz you stop streaming?
Digital_donger: monkaS
andrew_mrballsack: hi was he intersted in coding and mathas a kid
ortunado: roxas got green sword bois!
b2kemann: is geo mad? i just came
Subonik: Wow, that ROXASBrandon guy is really swell. :)
whichtom: yea geo will get there with his method
JeanFrag: WOW GREAT CHAT monkaS
PeinlicherAffe: xD
raystriker98: what's geohot doing today? something obscure? or open pilot stuff?
I2btw: the point is why work
Featen: add tab to mu fit
nsielicki: BASED AND FUCKING REDPILLED
nsielicki: TIMEISKEY MOD WHEN
okeeeeeee: XD
whichtom: bruh
erlsek: AHAJKH,AA
Digital_donger: the madman did it PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: @raystriker98 neither
mejhem: LUL
eldac_kno: F
Pedi: LUL
knicked: F
PeinlicherAffe: timeiskey 4 mod
calcmath: try higher than 100 time steps
PeinlicherAffe: timeiskey 4 mod BRO
raystriker98: @santiago_lhc what's he doing?
I2btw: floats numbers are shit
b2kemann: nice
nsielicki: TIMEISKEY MOD NOW
eldac_kno: it took half an hour to read the chat lol
Pedi: @cankoloz not if he gets mod now :O
bigie: 200 is the max in cartpole. after that the episode ends
shoesman17: mod him SwiftRage
lpdon2: what was the fix
whichtom: pretty cool
randoma1: What is he making? I just tuned in
Ne0Zer0: lmfaoooooooo
hardtarget4: lmao
ortunado: enjoy timeiskey LUL
erlsek: oh no
PeinlicherAffe: not ban D:
ortunado: i love @georgehotz
Ne0Zer0: LUL
Pedi: LUL he acutally got banned
PeinlicherAffe: mod
ozychhicodes: lol
okeeeeeee: ??????
kaboomyoo: banned im so weak
PeinlicherAffe: he helped you
DasMastah: lol
erlsek: hajhkajhkla
treeknifeslug: lol
ozychhicodes: @timeiskey pepehands
Subonik: LUL
eeXecute: BAM
okeeeeeee: ?????? 󠀀
erlsek: f
eldac_kno: EPIC gamer moment
hardtarget4: got him
PeinlicherAffe: FeelsBadMan
mejhem: He died for our sins
ortunado: BEST F IN AWHILE LUL
buzzind99: Banned for helping
knicked: top 10 anime deaths
PeinlicherAffe: xD
Pedi: @ROXASBrandon did you ban him?
Ne0Zer0: the noble sacrifice LUL
FargioFarmani: F
PeinlicherAffe: F
okeeeeeee: help = ban
eldac_kno: top 10 anime betrayals
chai_wala: !uptime
PeinlicherAffe: FeelsBadMan / FeelsBadMan
Ne0Zer0: pole ran away lol
Zepcon7: Is your fan running?
ortunado: @ozychhicodes ps3 jb? LUL
nsielicki: “The tyrant dies and his rule is over, the martyr dies and his rule begins.”
Pedi: @cankoloz FeelsBadMan
eldac_kno: Fs in the chat for timeiskey boiis
funwayz: @georgehotz he was telling you to do that for 15 minutes
Ne0Zer0: LUL
whichtom: LUL
PeinlicherAffe: monkaS
suspence20: LUL
mashafique: monkaS
frunkAF: LUL
mejhem: FeelsBadMan
justcrash: GEORGE DONT KILL ME NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
b2kemann: why the mood? what happened??
erlsek: you can use /user timeiskey
calcmath: can you try 1000 steps?
whichtom: chat just backseating and being rude
bigie: he said you missed a tab on mu fit() so it wasn't doing it more than once or smth but you didn't change that when it worked
calcmath: mu.fit is fine
blazeofglorytv: Where did he stop with covid19 reverse?
milcapone: hello from greece love your stream
Ne0Zer0: this is quality content lol
bigie: i think that's what he was saying and the morons were spamming it
routerkicker: yeah he wanted it in the loop
Pedi: I can mod :)
Santiago_LHC: I can mod
chai_wala: I just wanted to thank george for the bubble sort tutorial in python, Thanks george!! :)
sleep_waIk: sumVac2
Santiago_LHC: I like timeouts
Pedi: @cankoloz as well
hardtarget4: yeah we need to clean this place up
Joooooooooonas: atleast timeouted LUL
kaboomyoo: bubble sort xDD
gent03: yo let me be a mod
andrew_mrballsack: can i ask whats muzero and wat hes doin
CoachMeech: GEORGE
gent03: i’ll take care of these fools
Penguino138: I wish someday to be a mod. Subbed today but been watching for a while
CoachMeech: GEORGE OF THE JUNGLE
whichtom: being mod isn't fun
bigie: @andrew_mrballsack a reinforcement learning algorithm
CoachMeech: Stop simping for mods losers
routerkicker: if you put the fit in the loop and it works unban him
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz Take me as a mod
Penguino138: oh shitt
Penguino138: back to the subs only chat
Penguino138: waste your points
b2kemann: feels good
CoachMeech: FREE THE PLEBS REE
TasosTheLord: DansGame
gaocaandra: yeah boii
eldac_kno: chad subscribers
PeinlicherAffe: FeelsBadMan
bigie: haha plebs get out. my sub finally paid off
Mariosavitch: ive lerked so long i have a billion points
b2kemann: the elites
CoachMeech: NON SUBS, WE MUST FIND THE EXPLOIT IN THESE RULES.
Penguino138: IRON FIST GEORGE
7Locrian7: D:
shoesman17: monkaS
Penguino138: Yeahhhh waste all your points non-subbers
eldac_kno: lol
malmeani: you inspire me
gaocaandra: because we could use the chat to learn shit
qlutoo: whats this math shit? LOL
gaocaandra: not spam
Pedi: I am hiding shhh
b2kemann: why should he read the chat if it's just bs
bigie: i think you can disable the twitch point msg thing
TasosTheLord: Just let them BibleThump
FaustPetrovich: FaustPetrovich subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 6 months, currently on a 6 month streak! whoa 6 mouths already?!
gaocaandra: because sometimes we are helpfull
Penguino138: They're misbehaving we have to have some semblance of control
Mariosavitch: before you do, i want to say i love you
Ne0Zer0: Honestly I think they like getting banned lol
hurzg: chat is fine compared to some other streams btw :D thats freedom of speech (or stupidity) :D
gaocaandra: i guess
bigie: definitely but i don't know how
PeinlicherAffe: see you in next life
gaocaandra: we get entertained he gets help
plazmacsgo: see ya
henistein: How worth is learning assembly nowadays?
gaocaandra: win win
shrekandchill: He dropping more bans than the americans be dropping bombs in the middle east
Joooooooooonas: Yea, you can edit it and shit so you need more points or disable it completely
Mariosavitch: please hotz. we love you.. dont :(
eldac_kno: is art of programmin worth reading?
Santiago_LHC: Are people misbehaving?
whichtom: @henistein only for OS development or reverse engineering probably
bigie: what was k to begin with? is it an algorithm specific thing ?
plazmacsgo: what is he measuring?. loss, accuracy, episode survived?
whichtom: @bigie the muzero paper says K=5 for their results
Mariosavitch: bless you
bigie: ah thanks @whichtom
bigie: they have a prioritized replay buffer. that one's way better than normal experience replay
b2kemann: u need a burger
malmeani: now the value of my sub just went up
numinousloop: they were convinced they knew what the problem with your code was
Mariosavitch: you should train the inputs to your inputs
bigie: i hate that it's only possible in python & slow. i want an ML/DL framework in C++
malmeani: we love you
smurfd0: from the paper, "Predictions are made at each time-stept, for each ofk= 1...Ksteps" for the one asking about what K was
gaocaandra: yo what happened with the protein fold
nsielicki: nsielicki subscribed at Tier 1.
gaocaandra: did it ever work
b2kemann: swift is the answer @bigie
gaocaandra: where us the rant
gaocaandra: ?
nsielicki: longtime watcher, first time subscribing. I literally linked timeiskey to the stream because he knows a lot about this. You're convinced he was wrong, I'm fairly certain he knew what he was talking about.
pwnbase: @bigie the python is just an api, all the heavy lifting is done in c++
nsielicki: subscribed literally just to tell you to fuck yourself.
gaocaandra: beggining of stream
gaocaandra: ?
eldac_kno: lol
bigie: i know google's hardly working on that but i hope it fails because i hate tensorflow and swift @b2kemann
Mariosavitch: @nsielicki lol
eeXecute: alt account LUL
bigie: @pwnbase yes but python itself is slow
b2kemann: @bigie why the hate
plazmacsgo: @nsielicki ????????
PeinlicherAffe: xD
bigie: @b2kemann tensorflow is just badly written & breaks their API with each release. I looked swift up. didn't really like it
b2kemann: you can say fuck you george, but yuou have to be a subscriber
routerkicker: i don't know much about this. what's wrong with the proposal of fitting every episode?
bigie: that's a pretty expensive fuck you LUL
eldac_kno: goverment in the us is basically just a corporation
nsielicki: yeah all four dollars
numinousloop: have you done any poker AI work?
bigie: 4.99. congrats
gaocaandra: do third world countries get discounts on subs?
eldac_kno: I would call Poker Ai Wittgenstein
Ne0Zer0: def feel the frustration with ml
bigie: i pay more because i'm in germany and pay 4.99 euros instead of 4.99 dollars. that's also price discrimination
gaocaandra: have you looked at wolfram lang?
eldac_kno: that's the price for not being a part of the US boi
bigie: is any RL algorithm stable though ?
Penguino138: He learned so well :')
zyrax222: i have no idea what you're doing but im enjoying it
b2kemann: @bigie but you think we should do it in a lowlevel language? sound like a bad solution, maybe haskell or another pure functional language is the solution
gaocaandra: i pay more because the government puts a 30% tax on usd bus
Ne0Zer0: AngelThump
PhosphoricAcid: freedom
cankoloz: free
SHAVEYY_: :( noooooo not the non subs
CoachMeech: TriHard NEVER SUBBED TriHard NEVER DONATED TriHard ADBLOCK ON TriHard STOLEN LAPTOP TriHard NEIGHBORS WIFI TriHard FREE ENTERTAINMENT TriHard
mangoxavier: oh hey
Penguino138: Are you reanabling sub only tomorrow?
plazmacsgo: what so special about muzero?
bigie: @b2kemann wtf my msg got flagged or smth
bigie: @b2kemann not low level necessarily. I'd learn swift if e.g. pytorch did it. using libtorch in C++ is near impossible but could be improved
MrGwopz: How did you jailbreak the ps3? @georgehotz
eldac_kno: what do you think about Yandex self driving car and Yandex in general?
abedbawsxx: TOS
mexeroserisback: @bigie use julia
RaulYTpro: Is it worth it to work for someone ? :c I'm a software engineer @georgehotz
Joooooooooonas: Why dont you turn you table a bit so we have a nice background view @georgehotz :D
whichtom: tf is 60.7% cpp though
calcmath: how is biphasic sleep?
zyrax222: are you in a hotel or something?
saixj: i respect your chat can you keep it open for non subscribers
b2kemann: geo guru session
tex01: hello
abedbawsxx: the loop
CoachMeech: what color keys we using on the mechanical?
cankoloz: i can see myself PogChamp
plazmacsgo: the infinite effect
gaocaandra: when is the cult starting?
fabioitout: For me it is a fair price for the thing he is doing, his opinion we can disagree
konradmad: fastest way to learn programming is to actually program all the time?
whichtom: I imagine if anyone would push for langs other than python for NN itd be for autonomous driving
mangoxavier: how do you prevent models of manipulation being built about you?
bigie: @mexeroserisback if it goes mainstream & its good i will. right now there's nothing better than pytorch
MrGwopz: how did you jailbreak the ps3? @georgehotz
pwnbase: red solo cups for the party
Bootstraps: georgehotz how many hours do you sleep per night usuallky?
SHAVEYY_: Hi mom PogChamp
WilliamMu6: hello
nsielicki: thanks for the stream today, interesting stuff.
plazmacsgo: what so special about muzero?
b2kemann: can we do it in haskell??
mexeroserisback: @bigie true that... I played around with FluxML in Julia and it works fine but is still in its early stages
numinousloop: when will v2 be??
ROXASBrandon: ROXASBrandon subscribed at Tier 1.
skut1212: heyy What resources would you recommend to programmers on learning AI?
funwayz: finally pytorch
lolix_idontknow: when a collaboration with others hackers to shut down the Chinese system?
gaocaandra: whats the end goal?
bigie: nice and i will clone it and pretend i wrote it
calcmath: what wil try after cartpole?
Bootstraps: wtf is mu_0
eldac_kno: thoughts on yandex self driving cars?
victorzarzu: pytorch vs tf
mariopedreiro: !uptime
numinousloop: your screen is a strange loop
MrGwopz: @georgehotz plz explain the parts that you can on how you jailbroke the ps3 im very curious
bigie: @mexeroserisback money & research should be behind it to go mainstream. or at least one of them heavily.
PhosphoricAcid: LUL
santi_264: kim jong un is dead?
Ne0Zer0: LUL
Ne0Zer0: lmao
zyrax222: sellout
Ne0Zer0: o/
fabioitout: thanks for the iphone jailbreak, lot of fun
bigie: no
calcmath: what is the parachute paper?
whichtom: thanks for the stream geo
plazmacsgo: what concepts would I miss if I dont go to colledge?
Penguino138: Peace! Thanks for the great streams!
Bootstraps: george whats your insta
SparksCx: you put it in submode...
Joooooooooonas: When can we expect you ?
mangoxavier: Thanks George.
bigie: talk a bit about apple and google's covid 19 tracing shit before heading out
murkythunder: selling out for$2.5 cut from twitch
SHAVEYY_: Do you have kim jong un's phone number?
eldac_kno: art of programming worth reading today?
zyrax222: selling out for $5 LUL
victorzarzu: pytorch vs tensorflow
b2kemann: love your streams!:)
SparksCx: 4Head
cankoloz: Dictatorship is the best! monkaS
whichtom: brrr
numinousloop: thanks for the stream, man! love the live coding AI papers <3
zyrax222: 4Head
SHAVEYY_: pay pigging the government?
mangoxavier: Taxation without representation is what we're in right now
gaocaandra: inflation?
whichtom: money is pretty arbitrary
info303: thats how inflation happens lol
saixj: but that causes inflation
gaocaandra: money machine goes brrrr
MrGwopz: fair enough if you cant talk about how you jailbroke the ps3 but thats a very interesting topic in my opinion @georgehotz
santi_264: doesnt printing a lot generate inflation
mangoxavier: State tax taxes your fed tax refund. that's double taxed
ROXASBrandon: LUL
saixj: money is a social construct
info303: and you get 100 billion zimbabwean dollars for a loaf of bread
gaocaandra: boi
gaocaandra: come live in argentina
lambdaman0f: its to ensure demand for dollar currency
michaelkawwa: true
calcmath: not it also creates GDP growth
gaocaandra: see what printig and peronism is
konradmad: i dont pay taxes....im sneaky xD
plazmacsgo: are you planning to support more cars with openpilot?
zyrax222: so how do you see the national debt then?
hurzg: taxes kinda balance wealth..
eldac_kno: it's like chris tucker quote in rush hour, i am the president, i am the emperor, im the king
corpus_cule: are actually saying taxes are not needed? lol
murkythunder: ppl have said this printing doesn't cause inflation but i nvr understand :(
chemicalflash: but don't they have to sell bonds in order to print
eeXecute: Look at that loop FeelsGoodMan
Kalland: the difference is who you tax. if you print you tax people who have money. not who earn money.
saixj: we should just sell a state to canada or mexico to get rid of debt
bigie: so you're saying i should buy bitcoin?
MrGwopz: @georgehotz yo im out bro take care!
slevinxd: How we win against the system, sir George?
b2kemann: printing is inflation, by defenition
mangoxavier: Which bitcoins will stand the test of time?
lambdaman0f: look into Modern Money Theory
saixj: lol
whichtom: LUL
calcmath: its people bidding up pricess with extra money that causes inflation
sudoaptgetupgrade: it just works because most countries trade with USD. If countries start to pay with their own currency the USD will fall
pelegogrosso: @georgehotz can you be my teacher? hahaua
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: @georgehotz sir have you ever taken an iq test?
b2kemann: by gold ;)
plazmacsgo: you should stream more!
fedexkinkos: U ever play poker
ocandoja: hi!
pepelaugh0: HeyGuys how you been geohot?
asheritis: hi George
DecayingSkullz: Hello George
TheSkapegoat: hi from Australia
Jehhred: Two in one day? What is this sorcery?
terrarosa: hey
masters8: Charmin ad, nice
JaeGeeTee: Whaaaaaatuuuuuuuuup
enlightenedgambino: hiiiiiiiiii
ad5k: Fzero
leonardssh22: hi man, how's going?
ck1956: not able to sleep ha
bugbrar: bonjour
thejakesummers: do this in COBOL
liams: Suuuuuuup
mutrx: yo
CaptCalifornia: gang shit
eldac_kno: wazzzup
cod4_lightning: what is muzero?
masters8: do it in coq
mattdougherty22: how was alpha go
atlas193: How long will it take someone who doesn’t know how to code to learn hacking?
luchesijoao: Hey George!! Wazzzupppppo
mik3xx: Why do you use a MAC? Just preference?
JerWasTaken: Hey Geohot. Are you able to help me calculating Quaternion to Euler angles in C# :D I have been trying for the last 10 hours or so but I can't figure it out
DecayingSkullz: UNIX like OS
bugbrar: ^^^^yes, why mac?
moizai: George ! is comma still operating right now?
singularitytoatea: My guy geo very hots is backkkk!!!!
eldac_kno: cringe bro
Infinitelym: what we doin today
singularitytoatea: lmao higher quiality
singularitytoatea: lmao
masters8: i like it
optimizely: what are we working on tonigh?
keith282: This is my last day as a sub FeelsBadMan
moizai: is comma still operating my dude?
mattdougherty22: how was alpha go
fedexkinkos: take some theanine bruh
tremendomendez: monkaS
TheSkapegoat: TheSkapegoat subscribed with Twitch Prime.
joseanavarrom: Are you sweating?
ited01: kk hello
masters8: lol
masters8: quick
eldac_kno: is art of programming worth reading/studying through
masters8: gotta get my low qual memes in
aar0npham: aar0npham subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! how was alphaZero?
Mint2bSpiced: click the cog in the right hand corner
ited01: just increase de reedeem price
Mint2bSpiced: its under chat settings
erichtp: rip thx low qual plebs
thodeannn: no more free msg :(
axlebear: Free the plebs
Santiago_LHC: We are back!
alexyzdev: sup team
Penguino138: Holy shit two streams in 1 day
optimizely: send link to the article
cromed56: !uptime
ited01: increase the price
fkndean: https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/geforce/guides/nvidia-rtx-voice-setup-guide/ If you have rtx card its pretty good at eliminating background noise :)
Santiago_LHC: Plebs are free
VandaleBot: yo
Detonat3D: !uptime
Mig1939: George what do you think of YOLO?
aayaanamir: hello from Pakistan
Penguino138: Release the plebs :p
ivche1337: What's MuZero?
egb3: hello
tremendomendez: :D
Shelledlizard4: freedom
mattdougherty22: how was the movie?
Detonat3D: hi
alexyzdev: Heyyy he did it
achamorro008: ddd
plazmacsgo: @ivche1337 an RL algo
Penguino138: Welcome back George we missed your insightful and ASMR filled streams
Santiago_LHC: I can help mod.
masters8: yay
achamorro008: geooohotz
optimizely: send link to the article
mutrx: wait didn't you just ask how to
csal90: ayeee
tremendomendez: no mods?
thodeannn: he did not )
ivche1337: @plazmacsgo tnx
K_I_N_N_Y_B_O_T: that protein ever fold?
masters8: meme away folks
alexyzdev: lmfao
mutrx: @georgehotz you just asked how to turn it off?
thodeannn: goerge is cringe bye
pwnbase: its /unmod
Mint2bSpiced: you just type "/subscribersoff" as a mod
aar0npham: https://help.twitch.tv/s/article/channel-points-guide?language=en_US
Penguino138: Looks like the only mod in here is Mutrx? You can click the People button next to "stream chat" to view them
eldac_kno: it's the United States of George Hotz
joseanavarrom: Twitch can be complicated
gigafact: wow we are back
Jehhred: https://help.twitch.tv/s/article/channel-points-guide?language=en_US Scroll down to the Streamer Section - it's Manage Rewards
joseanavarrom: For how long do you usually sleep?
Santiago_LHC: I can mod. You could also use https://nightbot.tv/
Andremm2: You know the UI is bad when even a known hacker can't use it LUL
Penguino138: Georgemojis
Penguino138: You earn channel points just by watching the stream
keith282: You earn channel points by watching the stream
sophisticatedgaming291a11: LUL
gigafact: it did not even finish uploading to youtube should I just attach this stream as well to just one upload George?
ad5k: have you seen wolfram's new theory of everything
saff__: give me points
pwnbase: make it 1337 points
gigafact: OK
Mint2bSpiced: you earn channel points by watching hours of your stream
joseanavarrom: For how long do you usually sleep?
Penguino138: Is it still subs only?
aar0npham: looks like it now
Penguino138: Welcome productive and positive members of the stream... Lets program
nashesvobodnoye: nashesvobodnoye subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! <3 is heart
eldac_kno: can we ban sleep questions
TheSkapegoat: Hey GeoHot, which company do you think is an underrated competitor in the autonomous vehicles market?
Lizardan: Subs only PogChamp .. hello plebs HeyGuys
Penguino138: Unless george says so, questions should be related to the stream topic
microx0ft: are you only using python for this?
gigafact: people can "lash out" on youtube if they want. there is quite a few strange people on youtube but majority of people really love your streams George
grey_street: what's your idea of optimal sleep Kappa
aar0npham: facts
Penguino138: @georgehotz did you make any progress since last the stream?
bugbrar: I am not a subscriber, but I would like to able to learn by asking questions, so I would appreciate it if people stopped asking unrelated questions/spamming. Please.
Santiago_LHC: keyword: prediction
saff__: don't do it
saff__: end of
xeeton: what is the real-world length of each time step?
Killeraing: wow you were coding all night?
powerofpickle: You have gone on tangents in past streams so I guess people are adapting
jasondesante: love you dude
Penguino138: Yeah some of the nature hacking streams had great thought provoking convos too
eldac_kno: do you think gpt 2 is overrated
jontowtruck: how are you still trying to implement this lol it probably has the most descriptive/informative appendix to dissect
devm0d: What are we hacking on tonight?
gigafact: I am currently working on a project and it's really wearing me out. It's not healthy at all but the result is going to be amazing. It's all worth-it in the end.
TheSkapegoat: Can AlphaZero be applied to truly everything or do you think its inherent to strategy based activity?
xeeton: @georgehotz thx for the answer
devm0d: Thank you
keith282: @gigafact Are you okay bro?
joseanavarrom: What are you planning to use it on?
TheSkapegoat: Do you think AlphaZero is a leap in AI or simply a noticed step?
Santiago_LHC: AlphaZero knew the rules to the games, right?
gigafact: Have been sleeping only a few hours a day. I have not been so tired in all my life.
alfyfav: So why don't you go to sleep @gigafact ?
Jehhred: @gigafact Maybe you shouldn't be on twitch then and instead doing the project?
Penguino138: @gigafact Try to get some sleep and it might help overcome the project obstacles you're facing :)
Lentaij: Anyone have a link to the paper?
eldac_kno: just google it bro
ak0ya_: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1911.08265.pdf
gigafact: The problem is that even when I am going to sleep I am still thinking about the project. I can't seep for very long... Don't know if you had that feeling...
hurzg: I wonder if a prediction network is really necessary, if the world is based on relative simple physics... however in this way its a nice and general approach.
grey_street: twitch prime can chat
axlebear: I'm twitch prime
alfyfav: @gigafact maybe I could help you with your project. Follow me on twitter. Username: localhost666
devm0d: I’m also twitch prime
tremendomendez: :)
Penguino138: Lay down the law george
bugbrar: Thank you
DeeboMC: I was just in the middle of subscribing lol
gigafact: is someone having a party there?
aar0npham: n training steps
eldac_kno: yes, chad party goers
aar0npham: in terms of hyperparameters
Penguino138: Is there a party outside?
Penguino138: hahahahaha
joseanavarrom: Loud party
isyraq1: @georgehotz how would you recommend someone go about learning programming? Books? Online courses?
xraichuux: why do you use mac ?
tremendomendez: monkaS
Mint2bSpiced: thoughts on RTX voice AI
ad5k: immediately how to program questions loool
TheSkapegoat: Do you think quantum computing is what will truly accelerate AI or is it mostly figuring out the software side of things such as what you are learning from this paper?
Mint2bSpiced: for the background noise reduction
DeeboMC: 7 in nyc lol
synthetic11000: 7pm cheer
calcmath: is he starting from scratch?
eldac_kno: yes
DeeboMC: He said 8
alfyfav: @isyraq1 he have sayed that before. Just sit down and think about what you want to do, and do it investigating and reading, just like he's doing it rn
Rashad242: Rashad242 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! I'm just here to c greatness
hurzg: quantum computers are pretty useless right now I guess @TheSkapegoat googles QC can only generate a certain type of random distribution
Santiago_LHC: Interesting clip from a recent Lex Friedman interview with David Silver (one of the authors of the MuZero paper) on AlphaZero and self-play: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e77NkSjnyH4
axlebear: pytorch DansGame
eldac_kno: wtf are these questions
Mig1939: What exactly are you trying to do with MuZero on this stream?
raisedbyphantom: how long is he streaming
optimizely: can you make terminal bigger
DeeboMC: Ima go ahead and subscribe anyway homie.. hold on a minute
programmer42: which python's vim package are you using ?
lebop: WHAT IS MUZERO
raisedbyphantom: !stream
Santiago_LHC: MuZero is the latest ai from DeepMind
eldac_kno: wtf is this chat
calcmath: muzero is reinforcement learning algorithm
aar0npham: why do they use elu instead of leakyReLU?
alfyfav: @lebop why don't you google it?
CensoredAlex: what are we doing?
eldac_kno: writing muzero
ak0ya_: muzero paper reading
tremendomendez: :)
Penguino138: Muzero is an AI model that was used in AlphaGo for those wondering
optimizely: can you make terminal bigger
eldac_kno: petaaah is about to get banned
CensoredAlex: nice
asselbergs: Good evening George. Fun coding time again.
Penguino138: A complicated AI model that is used for predictions if I am right
josalt: Hey everyone
dalvasorsali: dalvasorsali subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
axlebear: LUL
Jake_Miller_: LUL
Junki4: HeyGuys
JonathanH8686: JonathanH8686 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
eeXecute: LUL
Jake_Miller_: hi josalt
asselbergs: Thanks Penguino138
Penguino138: Let's get some wholesome hype
calcmath: He is using it to balance a stick first
eldac_kno: dat $tick
CensoredAlex: PogChamp40
Penguino138: Yeah basically doing physics based AI prediction
williami000: Hype Train
JdPaulBlart: elu activation function OP
williami000: skunkp1Nine skunkp1Nine
ToxicVulpes: @georgehotz can u use AI to break bitcoin private keys?
mrmusicmaine: so we’re using muzero to solve the classic cartpole, what’s the vibe here? Just learning muzero?
Bootstraps: did george shower?
JdPaulBlart: using muzero to find coronavirus vaccine
JdPaulBlart: duhhh
greaserthegreat: greaserthegreat subscribed with Twitch Prime.
logicssoldier: logicssoldier subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 4 months! luv ur face
eldac_kno: just as always, george is gonna play with some new model/algorithm and that's about it
Bootstraps: @georgehotz can you give a brief summary about what we are trying to accomplish?
hurzg: the idea is: start of with a simple problem to learn and understand the method
CensoredAlex: PotgChamp
greaserthegreat: Connected my amazon account just for this
Penguino138: Welcome new subscribers
CensoredAlex: @greaserthegreat SeemsGood
williami000: congratz on subbing
calcmath: increased font size of code would be helpful
greaserthegreat: Thanks yall
Santiago_LHC: "MuZero learns a model that, when applied iteratively, predicts the quantities most directly relevant to planning: the reward, the action-selection policy, and the value function. When evaluated on 57 different Atari games - the canonical video game environment for testing AI techniques, in which model-based planning approaches have historically struggled - our new algorithm achieved a new state of the art."
aar0npham: can u just load pretrained weight?
JdPaulBlart: no thats cheating
calcmath: i think the point is to learn how the algorithm that creates the weights works
Bootstraps: george what are you trying to accomplish?
memogainz: memogainz subscribed at Tier 1.
mrmusicmaine: thanks @santiago_lhc
JdPaulBlart: solving coronavirus with muzero
Jehhred: @Bootstraps World Domination, obviously
mrmusicmaine: @calcmath Yee same
PristineBanana: MercyWing1 <3 MercyWing2
Abnico: herro georgey looking cute this evening HeyGuys
eldac_kno: thoughts on 3b1b youtube channel sorry if offtopic
CensoredAlex: @Bootstraps Getting the optimal quantity of lysol in a vaccine Kappa
Bootstraps: inject disinfectant
neilsweb: Thank you soooo much for donating $1 billion worth of your equity in Square to fund COVID-19 relief around the world. Donating roughly 28 percent of your net worth is remarkable.. thank you!!!
mrmusicmaine: 3b1b is wonderful
Penguino138: keep the chat on topic
aar0npham: i think its time to get back to sub mode
ak0ya_: :(
rickoftheroot: monkaS
CensoredAlex: true, sorry.
tornpaperyoyos: @penguino138 no
mrmusicmaine: fair
Santiago_LHC: I can mod the off-topic nonsense
jmp0ut: hi all what's working on?
Killeraing: you could change the chat few to ban politics
Bootstraps: LUL
rickoftheroot: LUL
axlebear: LUL
mashafique: LUL
Killeraing: rules*
TheBlackzillian: what is muzero?
memogainz: Can you quickly explain what's the purpose of Jupyter in your workflow?
Major_Spicy: @georgehotz what is your goal with this program u are making?
Abnico: can i be a mod im also gay
jmp0ut: @geohotz you see the kernel chocolate_milk gamozo has been working on for fuzzing, literally 0days all known hardware and software, 1 shot
JesseSkinner: sub chat includes twitch subscribers
Mig1939: 0.0001% of chat understands anything you do here.
joseanavarrom: I think submode does include twitch prime people
Penguino138: @TheBlackzillian It's a complex AI prediction architecture used in things like AlphaGo
leonardssh22: mornin' geo
SHREKonVHS: umm george are u well
JesseSkinner: sub chat includes twitch prime subscribers, i mean
Gree_OW: @georgehotz Did those proteins ever fold?
Santiago_LHC: Thank you, I'll instate order
Santiago_LHC: and fear
jontowtruck: please for the love of god use the vim keymaps
rickoftheroot: monkaW
iKanak_: iKanak_ subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 2 month streak!
Penguino138: @Santiago_LHC Congrats on the mod upgrade!
neilsweb: because when u suck at coding you can test your code blocks easily and often.
jcernuda95: @memogainz the code seems to be controlling a openai gym environment that is a balancing pole on a wheel by using a new ai model released recently
Abnico: what is he using muzero for?
eldac_kno: nothing for now
Abnico: i wanted a chat observer but muzero was to hard for me
Penguino138: @Abnico For a physics simulation to balance a stick sort of thing
jmp0ut: also faster computation
hurzg: balancing a stick
Penguino138: ALEXXXXXX
Bootstraps: HI ALEX
leonardssh22: hi alex
mashafique: HI Alex
aar0npham: hi alex
c0sm3s: Hi
rrittenhouse: sup?
rickoftheroot: HI
axlebear: HeyGuys
Abnico: oh ok
8FollowSonik: HeyGuys
Incurs0: HeyGuys
grey_street: HeyGuys
neilsweb: nice chair
rickoftheroot: HeyGuys
Mig1939: hey alex!
joseanavarrom: HELLOOO
eldac_kno: lol
Santiago_LHC: Hello Alex
CensoredAlex: hey
aar0npham: lol
Killeraing: sup
Penguino138: It's tough dealing with friends who freak out about it
Bootstraps: alex are you coming over tonight?
SHREKonVHS: george are u being friend zoned
p4ri: LOL
Bootstraps: bring steak!!
p4ri: who is talking too
p4ri: he*
rrittenhouse: LOL
rickoftheroot: KonCha
Abnico: george, ur wifes boyfriend makes good steaks
SHREKonVHS: f r i e n d z o n e s
Junki4: the sound of ur HHKB is so relaxing
r00tkey: You are still up!
Drifter0o: georgeeee!!! nice to see you
aar0npham: bans coming up
Bootstraps: george do you like your steak well done?
ralaxe: what are you doing exactly i don't understand
bugbrar: That was very sweet
eldac_kno: do you like 3b1b videos?
diazz_15: Smooth fckn operator
Penguino138: Alex and George = goals
Newlax: terrible things
Santiago_LHC: Behave guys, Alex will be in chat
Newlax: @programmer42 https://github.com/geohot/configuration
PristineBanana: now I want steaks
neilsweb: Can Alex write python?
eldac_kno: english only, amigo
Gree_OW: @georgehotz Did anything ever come of the protein folding? I really enjoyed those streams
Santiago_LHC: English only
cod4_lightning: can you show your mac dotfiles?
dalvasorsali: I have a frozen steak but no idea how to cook it from frozen...
Abnico: protein is still trying to fold u can check the status on proteinbank
neilsweb: first time i see him reading slowly. usually he just skips overr everything.
calcmath: I think main goal of MCTS is to balance exploration and exploitation
sajugabru: lmao
BumD197: hi, is there a target application he's trying to implement or just exploring the muzero?
SHREKonVHS: imagine if newton said it doesnt work before writing principia
JdPaulBlart: using muzero to solve coronavirus
Penguino138: @BumD197 Right now we're just exploring and understanding through this paper
SHREKonVHS: sad gamer moment
jmp0ut: one pagefile
aar0npham: is it a subspace then?
Newlax: @cod4_lightning https://github.com/geohot/configuration
calcmath: i think time is still discrete
eldac_kno: bigbrain moment
gigafact: I wish some smart people like Lex would join the stream and help.
eDONze: DuduSoloTop subscribed with Twitch Prime.
neilsweb: nobody liked my joke, where i confused him for Jack Dorsey :-(
ad5k: why is it a continuous space?
Major_Spicy: @Penguino138 what is he trying to exactly? I just joined.
jmp0ut: ad5k because a protein can continuously fold
jmp0ut: until it reaches original
Drifter0o: George you ever used the app magnet?
DeeboMC: Subscription incoming
Penguino138: We're learning how Muzero, a complex AI Predictive network works, and applying it to a relatively simple physics simulation to keep a stick balanced
Penguino138: @Major_Spicy
Major_Spicy: Thanks a lot dude framedOh
ad5k: isn't the context chess, atari etc where position is discrete
DeeboMC: deebomc subscribed at Tier 3.
calcmath: the neural network can handle continous states
DeeboMC: Party time
ooMariaoo: caught the stream :)
Bootstraps: are we watching alpha go on stream together late today?
greaserthegreat: Could it be possible that continous is just the theoretic and is implemented with a finite number of discrete states. The delta in time could be small enough to provide a close enough answer to the continious model?
SHREKonVHS: bruh the ice chewing has returned
eldac_kno: chewing ice hurts bro
hurzg: isnt it quantized by the time steps?
sajugabru: they start at initial state and deterministically step through the space
Mint2bSpiced: @Penguino138 is this like the AI used in SteadyCams and drones ?
SHREKonVHS: no
Penguino138: @Mint2bSpiced I'm not sure, it maybe be more applicable to games but I don't believe so
Abnico: steady cam does background stitching
achamorro008: geooohotz
Bootstraps: POGGERS
Bootstraps: psuedo code
dalvasorsali: Isn't this similar to q learning/sarsa?
doganigooo2: yo helloo what's going on here
Major_Spicy: Fancy framedPOG
eldac_kno: btw in russian it's pronounced geohot -g-like in garden
calcmath: i believe the difference is a model of the environment is learnt
BumD197: the thing is if only given rules makes this AI algorithm somewhat find the problem and solves it, pretty amazing, but i imagine it couldn't be easy as it sounds
doganigooo2: @BumD197 probably it is not
Penguino138: @doganigooo2 Learning about Muzero, and complex predictive AI network
abhi1o1: i went to sleep go up and he is still streaming
bfpixels: @georgehotz im sub VIM vs VS Code?
calcmath: you need balance exploration and exploitation
DeeboMC: That’s nice pseudo code
Mint2bSpiced: @Abnico I mean the AI for the stepper motors inside the handles of the Steadicam, not the video editing software stabization
eldac_kno: ide question is the new kb question
Bootstraps: this pseudo code looks better than my real code
Bootstraps: wtf
sajugabru: what is the purpose of the tree search?
eldac_kno: that's what pseudo code is for
calcmath: UCB is the principled way of doing it, with theoretical backing, but ya simple would stilll work
diazz_15: @bootstraps I was thinking the same shit lol
DeeboMC: Same lol
axlebear: What is a leaf node again?
Penguino138: @sajugabru typically the tree is used to path out the predictions for future possibilities and moves in a game
Abnico: @Mint2bSpiced okie yeah
eldac_kno: leaf node is final node
calcmath: leaf node is end of game
DecayingSkullz: It's a node with no child
ad5k: leaf node is an end state?
1boi: really
gigafact: at least they have comments in the code
puffgrape: r we folding protein or we past that?
sajugabru: so if the functions that represent internal state stop changing then you've reached a leaf node?
ak0ya_: folding is done
eldac_kno: we are past that
puffgrape: ahhh ok
ak0ya_: this is a new project
eldac_kno: protein question = ban
hurzg: is a node itself simply a "move" in the game?
puffgrape: shit didnt know lol
dalvasorsali: @georgehotz Isn't this similar to q learning/sarsa?
guinness84: have you explore counterfactual regret minimizartion
guinness84: explored*
calcmath: only way to see reward if its realised only at the end of the game
Penguino138: @hurzg pretty much yes, it is a step, and typically has a weight attached to describe the probability/prediction
guinness84: o cool
kevin21071: what so you have to know the max moves for each game?
hurzg: @Penguino138 thanks
posixninja: if this has nothing to do with protein folding I'm lost
greaserthegreat: I agree it seems like it can't go to a true leaf node? maybe an arbitrary point is chosen and a score is calcualted?
greaserthegreat: new to this technique so just throwing out ideas
ad5k: is reward probabilistic in intermediate time steps?
socialnotsocial: what do you think about the general stagnation argument presented by Peter Thiel, Tyler Cowen and others?
calcmath: if game has no intermediate rewards or reward shaping, you sort of have to do it till end right?
CaptCalifornia: ICE CRUNCH monkaS
Penguino138: @posixninja we are past folding, moving on to AI prediction applied to physics
sajugabru: why isn't there intermediate reward shaping?
calcmath: in chess you only know if won or lost at the end
posixninja: molcular dynamics?
calcmath: not applicable for stick balancing
calcmath: but algorithm is general
ad5k: "MuZero also extends AlphaZero to a broader set of environments including single agent domains and non-zero rewards at intermediate time-steps."
gigafact: George would you work at Deep Mind?
raisedbyphantom: how long has he been streamin ?
DeeboMC: Like 30 min
posixninja: can someone point me to the whitepaper?
ak0ya_: @posixninja folding project is over
janpoonthong: How did you learn python by coures? or Turtuoirl from Youtube?
PristineBanana: https://arxiv.org/abs/1911.08265 @posixninja
ak0ya_: https://arxiv.org/abs/1911.08265
DeeboMC: 45 maybe
Penguino138: Yeah chatt has approved a lot so far
JdPaulBlart: its because im here
DeeboMC: No it’s me bro
JdPaulBlart: i increase the average intelligence of the chat
DeeboMC: Oh yea ur right
raisedbyphantom: def
sajugabru: @calcmath so it seems the main contribution of the paper is how they can make a model of games that don't currently have perfect simulators?
kisspapa: you ever have any fun with the open source voice builder tool google released
calcmath: yeah you simultaneously learn a model for the environment, as recurrent neural net
JesseSkinner: hm could it be applied to a game like .. the stock market?
DeeboMC: That’s scary stuff
JdPaulBlart: this light mode is hurting my eyes DansGane
JdPaulBlart: DansGame
sajugabru: then which tree search algo you use is irrelevant to the goal of this research right
posixninja: I'm still learning the personalities of amino acids :-(
calcmath: yeas so long as it balances exploration an dexploitation
janpoonthong: How did you learn python by coures? or Turtuoirl from Youtube?
calcmath: he can just implement an epsilon-greedy version instead of UCB version, but it will be less efficient
Nussinov: im trying to learn coding for 2 months now and I feel utterly retarded
dalvasorsali: @janpoonthong you learn by doing
Penguino138: @janpoonthong you learn to code through tutorials and just doing it
grizvok: 2 months is nothing
DeeboMC: Fred Baptise’s Python Deep Dive series on udemy
diazz_15: 2 months is legit nothing
gigafact: maybe this will help? https://medium.com/applied-data-science/how-to-build-your-own-muzero-in-python-f77d5718061a
diazz_15: Try 10 years and still not knowing wtf is going on lol
MorningLightGamer: if you google for "muzero-general" you can find a github repo that can maybe be helpful
nick_larsen: I gave 30 min talk on this in the live coders conf a couple weeks ago
nick_larsen: MCTS not MuZero
tragic_tf_up: what did you do when you were younger to motivate yourself?
DecayingSkullz: ban incoming
Nussinov: wait 2 months is nothing? that makes me feel better I suppose
JesseSkinner: @Nussinov yeah thats like, learning to read for 2 months ...
nick_larsen: What the question right now?
Santiago_LHC: No keyboard talk. Chat 101
Nussinov: @JesseSkinner oh LUL i thought i would just kinda pick it up quickly since a lot of people seem to know it
janpoonthong: What's your IDE?
hsydf92: what is being coded
Penguino138: @Nussinov You will likely have a long journey with programming. Full of failures and successes. You have to enjoy it for sure
JesseSkinner: @Nussinov some people have been doing it since they were kids.. its a new way of thinking for many who pick it up later in life
janpoonthong: from musro.model import musi.model
Nussinov: @JesseSkinner damn that is a huge advantage LUL im 20 now so its not so bad
janpoonthong: I think
JesseSkinner: @Nussinov and the biggest thing is getting used to things being broken 99% of the time. when it's working, you're done!
Penguino138: Exactly, and programming will give you serious power and freedom, so it is worth it in the end
bfpixels: my only advice is build things. It can be easy to stay in tutorial purgatory.
jsnfly: jsnfly subscribed with Twitch Prime.
grizvok: @bfpixels agreed. a huge mistake people often fall for.
grekler3: @Nussinov im 2 months stuck just learning data management in flutter lul .. i mean i can just copy a yt vid, but i need to go back and re learn dart and sql fundamentals, i need to fully get the concepts
Nussinov: @bfpixels luckily I have a degree in biochemistry so the applications are abundant in bioinformatics-related areas
Penguino138: @Nussinov Yes always go for practical programming examples, and slowly crawl your way through, you will learn a ton!
janpoonthong: @bfpixels So you mean tutorial are ehh
ivche1337: eyy sub only is gone lesgoo
ak0ya_: chat became an emotional support group for Nussinov :)
Penguino138: @ak0ya_ better that than the toxicity that caused sub only mode earlier today
socialnotsocial: @georgehotz what do you think about the general stagnation argument presented by Peter Thiel, Tyler Cowen and others?
Nussinov: @ak0ya_ hell yes! im feeling much better lol
echobrother: what's the IDE
hsydf92: vim
hsydf92: @echobrother vim and jupyter notebook
ak0ya_: dev env
bfpixels: @echobrother it's not an IDE he's using a text editor called vim.
Santiago_LHC: No stupid offtopic questions
Bloodswordz88: We fold fam
hsydf92: @santiago_lhc no questions are stupid
Penguino138: Someday ill be lucky enough to join Santiago and keep the chat clean dotsHappy
BumD197: does George have github page?
DeeboMC: Ban
ivche1337: there are no stupid questions, only stupid answers
Santiago_LHC: That a stupid question, but I'll allow it, because it's not entirely off topic :P
quinquanonagintilliard: What's the stupid question again?
ivche1337: Kappa Kappa
BumD197: my question?
dontbeameme: Did make cold fusion yet?
DeeboMC: “Does he have a github”; yes
Santiago_LHC: @BumD197 https://github.com/geohot/
BumD197: i looked at info below there wasnt any info so i asked
HalluCinogen151: Whats up man
calcmath: yeah i dont know why there are 2 num steps
BumD197: better put it some info if you dont like that question being asked
hichm19956: what happend boss?
dontbeameme: Singularity in 3 2 1
calcmath: can you zoom the medium post a little
beefydangles: did you ever figure out that beer virus?
gabryelportuga: windows > linux, and who disagree is right
Penguino138: @beefydangles no he moved on from it
hsydf92: zoom vim screen a little
iIyaRPV: stop writing cringe jokes and stupid questions in chat BlessRNG
MorningLightGamer: @georgehotz or mods, can I post a github link that may (or not) be useful?
beefydangles: @Penguino138 10 4
WhispyHerc: chat what is he working on?
gabryelportuga: @WhispyHerc muzero
WhispyHerc: yeah but what is he building @gabryelportuga
Penguino138: @All He is learning Muzero, a complex predictive AI network he is using to apply to a basic physics simulation
WhispyHerc: thanks @Penguino138
Santiago_LHC: @MorningLightGamer Yeah
DeeboMC: @Santiago_LHC pardon the off-topicness: Anyone know why the stream, on my laptop, is like 9-10 seconds behind the stream on my phone?
MorningLightGamer: https://github.com/werner-duvaud/muzero-general
LiveCustoms: Dude can you end corona already
LiveCustoms: I wanna go outside
WhispyHerc: so how is he implementing AI in a basic physics simulations? @Penguino138
Penguino138: @WhispyHerc you may see it soon, but we are using it to run a physics sim that balances a stick
WhispyHerc: how so an entity has to figure out how to balance a stick? @Penguino138
WhispyHerc: *oh
WhispyHerc: sounds interesting
hurzg: the thing is that the prediction network can learn all kinds of dependencies... also things, that can not be easily modelled via physics... its about learning the method itself
calcmath: why is choosing complete random actions correct here?
aaryan4: what are you working on?
gabryelportuga: he is pissed, aparently
Penguino138: @WhispyHerc Chat can correct me if i'm wrong, but I believe it uses the tree search to predict the best physical translation/action to take to keep the stick balanced
HalluCinogen151: He's hacking at corona
l1ght5p33d: everything is a tree search
l1ght5p33d: we want lookup tables
WhispyHerc: i see
eDONze: cocktop
gigafact: George did you see this https://github.com/koulanurag/muzero-pytorch been tested on CartPole-v1?
forkdb: Wow
posixninja: george just likes talking to himself and doesn't want to feel crazy
roletro: @georgehotz mcts is just a random search (with many samples) to a final state and relying on the statistics of the randomness to represent the overall picture of an action that prompted the search.
forkdb: Amazing....
forkdb: HelloGeorge
hichm19956: great,
posixninja: <3
forkdb: How are you doing?
hurzg: as far as i understood, the algorithm has to decide in which direction it has to accalerate the stick at each time step. each step is a node. and the tree search finds the best movement for each node
Penguino138: Yeah what hurzg said
WhispyHerc: i wonder how many nodes there are in say a second
blueberryguac: ban me
WhispyHerc: if thats even how that works
WhispyHerc: or "step"
gigafact: Someone already used MuZero for your problem George https://github.com/koulanurag/muzero-pytorch
l1ght5p33d: lol @ cartpole
shoji22: !uptime
ET_515: ET_515 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Penguino138: Welcome ET
calcmath: need to revisit UCB to implement MCTS
calcmath: i think discounted root value is you find the empirical reward for some rollouts
roletro: you don't have to stick to the formalities, you hack hack together a mcts that doesnt have to set up anything fancy. you arent writing a paper.
DeeboMC: 👆🏽
realdigitalflow: !uptime
calcmath: you can just use epsilon greedy for exploration
forkdb: Hello George... big fan.. you are an inspiration to all, especially me... please give some insight on how to become good at learning and understanding and implementing things, how are you sooo good at programming especially
DecayingSkullz: just stop asking these questions please
calcmath: practice makes perfect
Protoxus: 1. don't be noob
forkdb: Am not asking for answers
DeeboMC: Wastes of 380
forkdb: I just want to understand his thought process
WhispyHerc: waste
DeeboMC: Lol
psychicsides: Like they are worth anything @deebomc
raisedbyphantom: @Protoxus what a brilliant advice
khilshot: which programming language do you use for programming interviews?
masters8: take my points
roletro: well the goal of mcts is to randomly search until it reaches a state where no further action is needed or possible.
erlsek: waste
Hamled: I think the previous message about practice is an accurate representation of his thinking
shoji22: PRACTICE MAKES PERFECT GUYS, THAT'S THE KEY
Protoxus: raisedbyphantom I was just paraphrasing George
greaserthegreat: @khilshot the one you are most comfortable with and supports OOO
Hamled: you won't get good at anything you don't practice
raisedbyphantom: @Protoxus I know, no pun intented ;)
Protoxus: raisedbyphantom :P
raisedbyphantom: :P
bfpixels: are headaches normal when researching something like what George is doing or do I need to see a doctor?
jax05_: just don't practice the wrong way heh
DeeboMC: What part of the head?
Jakob753951: All of it lol
BumD197: why does it matter @forkdb you can't understand people's thought process, and if you understand that you wouldn't ask
Penguino138: @bfpixels Your head can hurt from learning too much stuff, but make sure you're hydrating and have enough protein for ur brain
WhispyHerc: cerebrum
calcmath: its an exploration policy
DeeboMC: @bumd197 exactly
bfpixels: tension headaches especially trying to read what he's doing.
DeeboMC: Normal
quinquanonagintilliard: George, can you explain to me how nvidia rtx voice works? they're really good
Waldoqq: oh shit we back
lithiumx4900: lithiumx4900 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 4 months! What happened to protein folding?
datswhatigot123: what a fine Saturday
Waldoqq: wuzgud my man
roletro: does muzero do the alphazero thing where some fraction of mcts branches are simulated till the end state and some are aborted by the value function?
shoji22: WKWKWK
young_beans_and_lean: Yaaay I’m in time for a geohot stream ... can’t wait to become a YouTube caption
singularitytoatea: Nn
ak0ya_: @roletro https://medium.com/applied-data-science/how-to-build-your-own-muzero-in-python-f77d5718061a here is a comparison explanation
forkdb: Thank you all for the expert advice
jdwillys: sup gangstar
posixninja: balance the stick... is the stick a carbon atom?
posixninja: or just a bond?
Penguino138: @posixninja It's a cart and a pole
fatpanda168: what's he doing chaterino
posixninja: that lost me
Penguino138: You should see in a minute if it compiles
fatpanda168: I 100% have shittier naming for variables
posixninja: are you just trolling?
pelegogrosso: dude, i'm not understanding nothing
DeeboMC: Socrates didn’t either, don’t worry
posixninja: I understand only 82%
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: !uptime
K177: :(
Penguino138: @posixninja It's called "CartPole-v1"
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: !time
posixninja: explain yourself then
fatpanda168: time to fold some protiens almost forgot
mr_stochastic: Just training on CPU?
K177: damn you going to speedrun it?
calcmath: if you implement MCTS like the paper you need to have a tree data structure as you expand leaf nodes dynamically
pelegogrosso: why not create a cheat game? is funny too
ak0ya_: implementing mu zero
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz did u finish the alpha go movie?
jasondesante: I hope he's vibin right now
Penguino138: PIZZA TIME
pelegogrosso: @posixninja: where start learn CS? you're looks be a pro.. or not?
Santiago_LHC: Pizza time!
pzuko7: should have a command for those asking whats he doing.
mashafique: Pizza time PogChamp
jasondesante: at the end of that documentary the dude quits playing go forever
ad5k: yeah nightbot could be handling these questions
jasondesante: the machine marries his mom and becomes his step dad
DeeboMC: Damn.. I gotta see that
Santiago_LHC: Mods can't install nightbot, saddly
WhispyHerc: what documentary
DeeboMC: 😂😭
pzuko7: ohh i see
Killeraing: pizza time
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Just hack George 4Head
socialnotsocial: @georgehotz what do you think about the general stagnation argument presented by Peter Thiel, Tyler Cowen and others?
pelegogrosso: codecademy is good or books are better?
ak0ya_: it's no off-topic question chat today
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Books are better
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Any given day
RomeroCesar: that's a personal choice @pelegogrosso
DeeboMC: They’re complementary
Protoxus: @pelegogrosso Depends on what you're learning. For frameworks and languages, I'd say online documentation is better since it's updated. For general concepts, books are better.
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Develop a habit of reading to partially become as smart as George
Protoxus: - My opinion, at least
RomeroCesar: I prefer books, but many prefer lectures, other prefer hacking. Knowing how you learn best is important
DeeboMC: You can’t become smarter necessarily.. knowledgeable and skillful, yes
bcihacker: what happened to #hack-covid?
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: You know how George reads stuff from papers and directly implements it , u need a hell lot of reading practice for it
WhispyHerc: you can become smarter but not more intelligent
lolzmaster99: What game os he applying muzero to?
ak0ya_: @bcihacker its over
lolzmaster99: Is there a new paper out?
Penguino138: @lolzmaster99 CartPole-v0
DeeboMC: Eh, semantics
ak0ya_: it's a november paper
bcihacker: @ak0ya_ oh. lost touch a bit.
DeeboMC: I use “smart” interchangeably with “intelligent”; am I wrong?
lolzmaster99: Yeah implementing papers is tough working on one rn
pelegogrosso: some good forum to learn languages?
WhispyHerc: i like to use "smart" as level of knowledge possesed and "intelligence" for intelligence
Santiago_LHC: Sigh
bcihacker: @lolzmaster99 wdym implementing papers? Just came on chat, so lost context a bit lol
DeeboMC: Fair enough
lolzmaster99: Taking a research paper in L and writing code to implement the algorithm described in it
lolzmaster99: ML*
in_just: Saw your podcast interview with Lex recently, not too shabby
DeeboMC: Minimally shabby
RomeroCesar: @pelegogrosso assuming you mean programming languages, I prefer reading a book instead of following some tutorial or lecture. Something like the "in a nutshell" series from oreilly are good if you already know at least one other language
calcmath: did he already implment make target function?
in_just: It's weird how he runs it out of a hotel room but I guess the point is to get the audio so doesn't really matter
lolzmaster99: geohot have you tried TF Agents?
RomeroCesar: was there a new one with lex?
DeeboMC: I think the locations vary
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz https://youtu.be/Ir7wCAQINqw comma.camera?
bcihacker: @lolzmaster99 hmm that sounds interesting. So does that mean that your algorithm needs to figure out the algorithm written about given an ML paper?
DeeboMC: No; he’s referring to the original I believe
in_just: Yeah the original
lolzmaster99: @bcihacker No, the paper proposes an algorithm and you implement it
in_just: lol
DeeboMC: Good choice
bcihacker: @lolzmaster99 any more info on it? article/paper/etc
Santiago_LHC: That's what he thinks
bcihacker: @lolzmaster99 sounds pretty interesting.
lolzmaster99: @bcihacker MuZero from DeepMind
calcmath: is make targets implemented already
thatguywithadik: i got too drunk and stopped coding for the night
dantehemerson: Nobody can explaint it lol
thatguywithadik: what's George doing
bcihacker: @lolzmaster99 oooh. i get it. pretty cool stuff!
Jaime_Medina: !uptime
Protoxus: @Jaime_Medina If you have BTTV you can do /uptime
Santiago_LHC: Manual uptime: 1 hour 45 minutes
calcmath: MCTS has to give you an estimate of the value function given previous version of the policy, then you iteratively improve
dantehemerson: Is this ML, DP or what is this?
dantehemerson: DL*
lolzmaster99: ML
calcmath: it gives you both
worraaa: RL, coding muzero to solve cartpole :)
dantehemerson: @lolzmaster99 is basic or advanced?
fatpanda168: anyone excited about nvidia announcement in may
lolzmaster99: Advanced
calcmath: I think it gives both, value function dicates policy so its more fundamental
pelegogrosso: is there some restrictions in this chat? because i'm new in the cs and maybe some questions mine can sounds idiot.
soldierheadsmite: new graphics?
gaocaandra: it's the first suggested implementation in deep dive into deep learning
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Do t ask about key board
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Don’t *
in_just: @pelegogrosso I think a certain level of knowledge is expected before typing...
worraaa: tab > space ty
ak0ya_: @pelegogrosso it has to be related to the topic
DeeboMC: Keep to topic?
worraaa: Kappa
DeansGamingRoom: What's the current project?
UltraPh3onix: !uptime
worraaa: !uptime
DeeboMC: U see the title?
raisedbyphantom: he is been streaming for 12 hours lmao
Santiago_LHC: @pelegogrosso We are not taking off topic questions today. IF you have general programming questions, just google
eDONze: where is your piano
calcmath: vstack or hstack?
DeeboMC: Dude... thank you for finally saying google.. jeezus
dompatobbe: is george still doing the corona thing?
gaocaandra: no
DeeboMC: Make it stop
dompatobbe: Aight thank you
posixninja: I'll leave you to hack and try to catch up on my own. this was the next course I was going to watch so I might be back
posixninja: if I don't solve it on my own
calcmath: good old off by one errors
satire_: are you done with low level stuff?
in_just: Is the AlphaGo algorithm publicly available?
Santiago_LHC: Ha, no
DeeboMC: What would u do with it anyway
in_just: Play Go
DeeboMC: 😂
ohheyitsrainy: absolutely embarrass Lee Sedol
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Best lee sedoy again
gaocaandra: create a swarm of drones
calcmath: do you eman the weights or the meta algorithm used to train it?
worraaa: there's some open source implementation
worraaa: but training will be expensive
frznn8: vai dormir filhoi
Santiago_LHC: There's Leela Go, which is based on AlphaZero Go
gaocaandra: how big a gpu farm would you need to train a model like that?
in_just: For Go? They spent $25 million I read
ohheyitsrainy: depends on how much time you have :P
gaocaandra: dayum
PFY1: whats muzero
Santiago_LHC: 25 million? I doubt it, that's too much
in_just: Until I stand corrected I stand correct? lol
robonhansonem: Still PoleCart?
DeeboMC: I agree
concurrentx: hi george! i've been watching you for years. One thing, I'm always curious about - what's your typing speed in WPM?' could you please do few races on TypeRacer?'
BumD197: isn't that algorithm trained in 4 hours or something
BumD197: for go or chess
Penguino138: PIZZAAA
gaocaandra: 35 million By one estimate, the training time for AlphaGo cost $35 million;
gaocaandra: thats what google says
alfyfav: I got scared because I thought that noise was on my place
in_just: I stand corrected LUL
carlosalfarodev: Hahaha
Santiago_LHC: Interesting. It wasn't anywhere as expensive for Alpha Zero
carlosalfarodev: I got up to check if it was in my place too
rickoftheroot: PogChamp
ohheyitsrainy: apparently alphago zero hardware cost was ~$25 mil? at least says wikipedia
DeeboMC: Yea but you were righter than wronger.
peakyDicers: what is jupiter notebook used for?
ohheyitsrainy: not that goog actually paid that much
in_just: righter than wronger, gonna have to remember that one
calcmath: dont you have to call make_targets
calcmath: before training
Biffingtonn: that pizza looks like you should get ubereats
RomanBanana: 'well thats stupid' LOL
DeeboMC: Lol
calcmath: ohok
calcmath: code not zoomed hard to read
microx0ft: Basically implementing the Monte carlo search will be used to select moves?
balloonpopa: What you got brother... a personal pizza?
pwnbase: have you messed around in MuJoCo?
Waldoqq: its not delivery its DIJORNO
Santiago_LHC: Hammer time
niko174_: Здравствуйте
calcmath: Maybe i am missing something here in your simplified version of MCTS, not sure why it would work
ak0ya_: no russian today :)
niko174_: So sad
in_just: baking a frozen pizza instead of microwaving. i took am a man of culture
guy_ross: guy_ross subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 4 months! OhMyDog
Manalope: Manalope subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
balloonpopa: What happened with the protein folding thingy?
ak0ya_: it's over @balloonpopa
DeeboMC: Timed out
balloonpopa: ahhh gotcha
Killeraing: pizza asmr
worraaa: mukbang stream PogChamp
mik12f4: are you tired or bored?
gaocaandra: aparently biology is kinda not a thing
BumD197: most likely it unlearned
k3ags: !uptime
guy_ross: @k3ags 2:08:40
calcmath: biology took too much compute
Abnico: hmm
dontbeameme: Hot pockets
calcmath: these loss curves just mean you are overfitting to each batch separately right?
dontbeameme: You live in America and u eating hot pockets
Santiago_LHC: No dumb off topic questions
DeeboMC: It’s not a hot pocket.
dontbeameme: Gotcha
dontbeameme: @santiago_lhc
DeeboMC: But #hotpocketlivesmatter
murkythunder: buy a hot pocket and you too can have the dinner of pro programmer jorge hotz
DeeboMC: 😆
calcmath: is any one else following whats happening here?
DeeboMC: #metoo
BumD197: little bit @calcmath :)
calcmath: werent those loss curves just overfitting
calcmath: on single batches
vaskogomez87: guys what is he doing? just arrived
slowpolka: have you cured coronavirus with a car yet
calcmath: need longer than 200 steps to judge quality of balancing
z00fle: trying to balance the stick?
ratakamom: yeah, the cart pole problem
Ayowayway: ai learns to balance a stick?
DeeboMC: Next time on dragonball z..
worraaa: exercise: explain the loss spike
Rowro: george im the biggest fan you'll ever have, I think we should be together @georgehotz
Ham3113: hey man. im a com sci student going into my last year of uni and i want to start learning more about how to implement neural nets. ive already taken an ai course that went over the general concepts of neural nets like back propogation and weight and bias calculations but i havent actually had the chance to make one. do you or chat have any suggestions for resources that would help someone at my level. thanks man love the stream.
Santiago_LHC: He does.
calcmath: he is not clearing his loss array so after restart it look slike loss spike
DeeboMC: @calcmath u the real mvp
calcmath: gradual improvement
DeeboMC: Lol was being serious tho
z00fle: oh its solved
Manalope: nice
Bowlgirlblergh: atpGasm
worraaa: ooh i thought it went to explore new regions of state space so there is spike
calcmath: lol thanks @deebomc
rickoftheroot: Pog
baby_janitor: what ide is that
DeeboMC: Np
calcmath: let see the balancing for 100 steps
vloodp: whats the project?
Santiago_LHC: The name is right there at the top @baby_janitor
calcmath: 1000steps
Penguino138: look at him wiggle about
Ayowayway: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
calcmath: moar steps
rickoftheroot: PogChamp
z00fle: uncap it @georgehotz
PiroFloydian: whats going on here friends
arrabity: PogChamp
dontbeameme: 👏
calcmath: mosr steps plz
dontbeameme: We are the champions my friend
calcmath: yes uncap it
lebop: please ELI5 what ish appening
aPosterior: now forbid it from harming humans
Protoxus: lebop Machine learning makes pole not fall over
calcmath: an AI is learning to balance a stick, the AI has no exposeure to physics before
StopitDonk: whats so exciting about 200?
lebop: ^
calcmath: maximum reward
calcmath: it fails very human like
z00fle: what's considered "pass" ?
calcmath: reward is to last for as many steps as possible
BumD197: it looks like too easy job for this AI
calcmath: pass is it balances for long time
z00fle: for one trial? or X in a row
calcmath: if truly learnt in a general way, it should balance beyond 200 steps even though it was trained only for 200 steps
lolzmaster99: One run should be able to last indefinetly
lolzmaster99: Due to the simplicity of cartpole
BumD197: in theory calcmath?
calcmath: yes ideally
cieph4: !uptime
jmp0ut: modulo your memory addresses as a quotient of your total memory space
jmp0ut: faster
jmp0ut: surprised our computers dont do it already
birkett0011: What we learning today boyss?????
jmp0ut: simple math
calcmath: otherwise its just fitting a table with a neural network, its good, just less impressive
mr_stochastic: This being run on CPU or GPU? Not sure if someone already mentioned that or not.
calcmath: whole point of the algo is it grasps the dynamics aka physics
birkett0011: We doing some RL?
z00fle: GG
lolzmaster99: Is the initial pole position fixed at vertical for each new replay?
Penguino138: Glad the chat got their shit together somewhat
socialnotsocial: What do you think about the general stagnation argument presented by Peter Thiel, Tyler Cowen and others?
rickoftheroot: SeemsGood
calcmath: and generalize beyond the training nest
Ayowayway: SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood PogChamp PogChamp
aPosterior: im a different man now
Waldoqq: can we g et more anti gov rants now? :)
BumD197: but it requires more training since it solves the problem but doesn't mean it solved physics?
jmp0ut: instruction sets as well
Trenz2: pretty good job
calcmath: last longer than 200 steps
l1ght5p33d: SeemsGood
mr_stochastic: Which RL game is next then? Cool stuff tonight :D
lolzmaster99: it can have a reasonable response to new instances
calcmath: not saying its bad, just interesting to see how far you can push it
DeeboMC: ML=/=AI
z00fle: brute force programming
lolzmaster99: Great stream. Looking forward to more paper streams
calcmath: can you uncap and run once?
worraaa: what are you trying next for muzero?
mr_stochastic: Yes!
worraaa: card game Kappa
calcmath: un cap in the evalution
jmp0ut: R programming is harsh
mr_stochastic: Yeah diff env :)
Santiago_LHC: Can we merge MuZero with Twitchess
vloood: this calcmath sperg lol
Penguino138: @georgehotz When did you say you were moving to the new apartment?
calcmath: lol @vloodp ill take that as compliment
worraaa: add discretization code
l1ght5p33d: discreet + small random continuity = continuous. no problem
birkett0011: @georgehotz Have you messed around with any dynamic simulation software? Like https://cloud.anylogic.com/models
k00kieeeez: xqcM
lolzmaster99: What about breakout-v0
lolzmaster99: same action space
lolzmaster99: left/right
balloonpopa: does the simulated environment account for external forces... i.e. wind ect.?
calcmath: harcoded policy
Manalope: jupyter is an IDE? what do the In / Out lines mean?
DeeboMC: Lol I don’t think so
DjAlma1991: What's up... First time here... Whar are you doing?
calcmath: i think you have 2 actions pace hardcoded policy in your "MCTS"
DeeboMC: @djalma1991 It’s kinda winding down atm, u were a lil late bro
calcmath: more hardcoded bugs
calcmath: [0.5,0.5
lolzmaster99: When are these gonna be posted to commai archive? Missed a lot of it
calcmath: its should 1/n, bot 0.5
calcmath: not 0.5
DeeboMC: U’d have to ask whoever that is that runs it
DeeboMC: @lolzmaster99
lolzmaster99: @deebomc Yeah just figured someone in here knew
DeeboMC: I’d like to know myself but they seem kinda cagey about the whole thing
DeeboMC: They’re in here lurking tho I’m sure
calcmath: sparse reward
BumD197: real test the muzero
calcmath: can it even reach in 200 steps?
lolzmaster99: breakout-v0
QUOTE_IF_NEXT_YEAR_BETTER: You start with artificial intelligence that can learn, adapt and improve itself. Because computers run so much faster than the human mind, the artificial intelligence becomes smarter and smarter at an exponential rate until it is so much more intelligent than we could ever imagine. Public figures such as Stephen Hawking and Elon Musk have expressed concern that full artificial intelligence (AI) could result in human extinction. How do you plan on stopping this from happening?
l1ght5p33d: laundry folding simulation
Killeraing: ban him
lolzmaster99: ban this guy
imkonst: sorry im new to this, is he using machine learning principles right now?
rickoftheroot: hammer incoming? LUL
DeeboMC: Hopefully
QUOTE_IF_NEXT_YEAR_BETTER: ban that guy
calcmath: reinforcement learning
QUOTE_IF_NEXT_YEAR_BETTER: evolution innit
gaocaandra: banhammer
DeeboMC: @quote_if_next_year_better How do YOU plan on stopping it?
theirishtripleking: All it takes is one semi colon removed thats how you combat it...
DeeboMC: Very niiice
calcmath: python doesnt care about semicolons
BumD197: we re doomed then
birkett0011: have you seen RL applied to any real life complex systems? Currently only seen small games with it
theirishtripleking: sorry colon*
l1ght5p33d: boston dynamics
CHENLOLA: What software the up and down arrow icon is?
skinnypuppy69: whats he making
calcmath: big games like dota and starcraft too
QUOTE_IF_NEXT_YEAR_BETTER: ^
t0rment1337: @georgehotz u need to change 1m2019.com to 1m2020.com
Anton_gashi: !uptime
skinnypuppy69: is he making a bot to play lunar lander??
lolzmaster99: Lunar lander can also be done as a convex optimization right?
cieph4: !uptime doesn't seem to work
masters8: There's no bot
Ayowayway: what about youtube celebrity Kappa
calcmath: gotta learn the physics before you land on the moon
Dgreen420: Dgreen420 subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! Big up George
worraaa: LUL
l1ght5p33d: don't need to learn any physics just approximate iwell enough
Ayowayway: SeemsGood SeemsGood
calcmath: yes just the practical aspects of physics
calcmath: muzero is very pragmatic, it only learns what it needs to achieve its goals
l1ght5p33d: pretty good
lolzmaster99: Needs more exploration
imkonst: is he plotting the loss function outputs?
lolzmaster99: What time tomorrow?
Mlewii: but can it learn poker though
birkett0011: pretty keen for this simulation tool : https://docs.hash.ai/core/ all python
lolzmaster99: What loss is that? Not familiar with muzero do they have actor/critic?
CHENLOLA: George, What software the up-down arrow icon is.
lolzmaster99: end-to-end?
lolzmaster99: Is that what you mean by correct?
鼻史: @CHENLOLA reverse scroll ?
l1ght5p33d: most underrated stream in ai
worraaa: this task needs more exploration
calcmath: poker can also exploit human behaviour by building models of specific humans
memogainz: Anyone recommend an intro to AI book?
Jski101: But you're hawking it Kappa
worraaa: which you might not get without proper UCT
Santiago_LHC: Nash
pwnbase: i have built a poker bot, i think the current literature is a bit clickbait
lolzmaster99: Understanding Machine Learning by Schwartz
worraaa: or just epsilon greedy
kevin21071: are these notebooks available on github?
鼻史: MIT open course ?
calcmath: yeah thats good generalizauton
lolzmaster99: It should go idnefinetely once it's learned to keep the pole within the learned space
Santiago_LHC: @kevin21071 Yep: https://github.com/geohot/ai-notebooks
bloodborne24: pole game strong PogChamp
therealariel666: !uptime
socialnotsocial: @georgehotz what do you think about the general stagnation argument presented by Peter Thiel, Tyler Cowen and others?
georgehotz: !uptime
masters8: nope
Santiago_LHC: 2 hours 30 minutes
WiseSwift: Can someone catch me up on what he’s doing?
masters8: lol
鼻史: u need bots in chat LUL
therealariel666: Thanks
Santiago_LHC: You need to install https://nightbot.tv/ @georgehotz for the commands
skinnypuppy69: you need a chat bot
skinnypuppy69: that would be cool
lolzmaster99: Question: Will you install a dark theme on your notebooks
socialnotsocial: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Great_Stagnation
skinnypuppy69: nevermind
BumD197: wanna see his on robotics type on simulation
DeeboMC: “Not now mom, I’m building a heuristic”
Santiago_LHC: Mods can't do it.
Protoxus: I think most of your mods can do it
waterpaste: Ninja LUL
calcmath: do you think mu zero like algorithms canone day be used to run corporations?
crawcraw66: i think its economic growth by high unemploymenmt
Ayowayway: ninja who Kappa
ggtom: ?????
Protoxus: @Santiago_LHC If he just sets it up, can't he give mods the rights to administrate it?
Protoxus: Haven't used Nightbot in a long time, but I think I remember something like that
l1ght5p33d: We're so productive everyone could get fired and we'd still produce everything
Gamer_nohope: just me or sound is too low?
Santiago_LHC: @Protoxus Yeah, we can add commands and edit, but he needs to install it
ggtom: i arent read that tbh ngl
eddtarlin: why coding isnt popular there like games
CHENLOLA: @鼻史 gotcha, reverse scroll. thanks.
jmp0ut: greedkeeping babies
waterpaste: d
borang: hello
jmp0ut: weirdos
calcmath: I think AI can open a new frontier for more growth
pepelaugh0: @georgehotz thoughts on simulation theory?
Ayowayway: religion philosophy made us here imo
WiseSwift: Yeah but everyone is doing yoga, all about eastern philosophy now brah
jmp0ut: religiosity also leads to tech fears
Protoxus: Hermetic philosophy is pretty dank, IMO
jmp0ut: some of which are unfounded
ggtom: i agree it gives focus as well
jmp0ut: and others lead to subversion cults
jmp0ut: which is horrifying
Abnico: what happened to matt's crypto religon?
Gamer_nohope: you can join games and coding...
agentvenom2: iterated prisoner's dilemma favors nice strategies though
balloonpopa: Religion is a matter between a man and his God - Thomas Jefferson
calcmath: progressivism i a kind a new relisigion, so just looking at olny old fashoined religion is not enough
socialnotsocial: You have an interesting point. Does religion help to keep people away from zero sum games? "Do not copy what your neighbor wants" etc
socialnotsocial: in some sense
DeeboMC: What about the Nordic countries tho. I think religiosity is being given too much weight
calcmath: it fosters cooperation to avoid prisioners dilemma
lolzmaster99: No religion is the new religion
jmp0ut: general buck naked repented and ate childrens hearts while giving them rifles to commit war crimes now he's a preacher
gaocaandra: maybe we've shifted from mass organized religion to smaller groups
pwnbase: they cannibalize eachother all the time
Thotshotgg: Are we putting our cure to covid on hold for now?
Ayowayway: nationalism makes the new religion force?
jmp0ut: hinduism believes in never being clean of sins and it's one of the oldest still surviving
balloonpopa: Where God builds a Church, there also the devil will build a Chapel - Martin Luther
memogainz: Why does it have to be religion and not simply promote good values?
therealariel666: @jmp0ut true
pwnbase: did you hear Shkreli is engaged?
l1ght5p33d: FDA won't let geohot cure covid
AzzoDio: sister is on immunosuppressants, parents are both super high risk
Abnico: 0xΩ
masters8: What kind of argument is that?
jmp0ut: @therealariel666 pay for it in this life or the next kinda thing
calcmath: universal human rights is a way we avoid conequences of zero sum condtions on large scales
Thotshotgg: lmao I am kidding. i just want our economy to reopen.
ahahahaitslit: unless you have a health condition
masters8: Fuck the old I guess
jmp0ut: i'm glad hindus dont have the fears of murder or genetic engineering
patroniv: Religion produced great art and architecture as well. Maybe sometimes not through the best means, but their cathedrals are amazing
lolzmaster99: But you could infect others
jmp0ut: they just do what needs to be done
tripcloth: when does your religion start? and are you gonna waco mode fks my wife?
Jski101: No point getting it
therealariel666: Well one of the sayings is that a person has to spendsome time in hell before going to heaven.
TheCellarDoor: Unless you love someone who is old of course ...
pwnbase: "Shkreli is asking to spend the remainder of his seven-year sentence with his bride-to-be — whose name is redacted in court papers — at her Manhattan apartment so that he can, they say, work on a coronavirus cure."
Penguino138: @georgehotz have you ever gotten into kernel convolution for image processing?
DeeboMC: @tripcloth 😂
masters8: lol
lolzmaster99: You also live alone
Abnico: art distributes cult/culture
ahahahaitslit: is kim jong un dead?
WiseSwift: So many nerds have asthma
balloonpopa: The people that need religion the most are the ones that are the most religious - balloonPopa
bloodborne24: based pharmabro Kreygasm
marckkhoury: We're not fully aware of the potential long term complications even in the young. It seems this virus can impact a lot of your organs negatively.
therealariel666: He is brain dead PogChamp
jmp0ut: shkreli is just a troll
cieph4: RIP KIM LULW
slev0182: Shkreli is the only one who can jailbreak the corona virus
jmp0ut: to prove money is broken
lolzmaster99: Lmao you and Shkreli should colab
lolzmaster99: Get Shkreli on the stream
Thotshotgg: Kim Jong Un had a botched heart surgery? haHA
calcmath: it can still affect your lung capacity
balloonpopa: No way... let Skereli stay in jail
Protoxus: lolzmaster99 Pretty difficult from prison, I think
Protoxus: balloonpopa Why?
masters8: what?
ahahahaitslit: the economy would've been fucked either way
jmp0ut: @georgehotz what do you think of the silver tsunami, pension funds going to /dev/null
lolzmaster99: I don't agree that net no lives were saved
Thotshotgg: exactly, lets reopen this country already. People are going to suffer more and more.
Abnico: its likely everyone was getting it before febuarary lol
kevin21071: yesterday they found 50k new cases, highest ever
DeeboMC: I disagree as well
Abnico: so many people got it without knowing
tripcloth: george, what is step 1 to hack the simulation??
t0rment1337: sweden is the only one that got the policy it right
Krakatoa77: !uptime
calcmath: even if you dont die, a significant propportion can be left worse off
marckkhoury: The sampling of those studies is questionable.
lolzmaster99: What did Sweden do?
FreddiesDeadieButHasAces: I tried to get a test they said I wasn't sick, but I work at BK so I thought it was a good idea months ago
ofaas: im so weary of these doctors giving economic forecasts while comparing them to their worst case models
Protoxus: lolzmaster99 Pretty much nothing, for the first month of it
Santiago_LHC: Lockdown keeps the medical care system from saturating. That's when people who shouldn't die, start dying of stupid reasons like lack of respirators available.
lolzmaster99: Discipline is the difference
Abnico: authoritarian countries #1
DeeboMC: Yea I don’t think Sweden’s case is applicable tho
ahahahaitslit: i've heard from actual swedes that the lockdwon is still basically self imposed amongst the people
kayoeyumisaolegais: !time
DeeboMC: Apples to oranges
yogi_1010: what about the non-covid patients it saved? Because the hospitals did not get flooded with all the +45 yolds
ahahahaitslit: like it's not government mandates but still
balloonpopa: Haha
ggtom: Santiago_LHC i think that the main reason for lockdown. otherwise, the hospitals get stressed and u make decision of who to let die.
jmp0ut: Palantir's CEO went to live in a nuke bunker in New Zealands, five eyes new operation center since australia was janked off forest fires
Protoxus: I live in Denmark - most things have already opened up again here, which is nice.
lolzmaster99: American culture is not disciplined enough to employ more lenient lockdowns
Thotshotgg: HA
nihonzera: I live in Tokyo. The governor said is impossible to have a lockdown here.
JdPaulBlart: shoutout to the bernie bros
Trenz2: nobody is
Penguino138: My favourite joke of the day was when you said the partyers were cheering for the healthcare workers dotsKpog dotsKpog
socialnotsocial: Australia and NZ have done well.
calcmath: dont you think a government need to wrr on the side of caution in these situations
jmp0ut: NZ is official police state
Thotshotgg: Are airplanes/airports operating at this moment?
Penguino138: Aren't hospitals going bankrupt cause they had to cancel most surgeries?
jmp0ut: here in Canada we have military medics working 24/7 to manage our inefficient healthcare
Jski101: That's the second best way to catch it
l1ght5p33d: Is Japan still radioactive
Faceless_Bard: out of the loop here: What does mean "they got policies right" ? what exactly did they do ? or not do ?
Santiago_LHC: @nihonzera I'm surprised by how few cases there are in Japan considering how early you guys have been exposed.
jmp0ut: yes it is l1ght5p33d
Thotshotgg: Dang
therealariel666: Wish I could keep my apartment as tidy as yours :(
eddtarlin: iam new there, whats going on?
l1ght5p33d: sweeet
kevin21071: the spread out the seating in restaurants, etc
kevin21071: they*
nihonzera: @Santiago_LHC the thing was the Olympics: they tried to keep fewer tests to keep a low number to try to keep the event going
Protoxus: @Faceless_Bard I think balance risk-minimizing without compromising the economy - and especially not taking "risk-minimizing" to extreme levels that don't really work that efficiently.
Major_Spicy: Did you get far with the Muzero thing today?
Thotshotgg: It is really depressing to hear college campuses and other schools talking about remaining virtual into the fall semester.
asselbergs: What about Brasil??
Games4Stream: In Sweden, they don't have the power to initiate a lockdown. They have literally no plan for a pandemic.
asselbergs: Brazil.
Faceless_Bard: Protoxus SeemsGood
jmp0ut: should we create healthcare camps like the FEMA tailerpark camps from the hurricane days
DeeboMC: How many airports are in Sweden vs USA tho
jmp0ut: you know
DecayingSkullz: I wonder what the new normal will be after this is all over
socialnotsocial: Do you worry about engineered pathogens?
lolzmaster99: People are pointing to the relatively low public health impact in the country as evidence that the lockdowns were unecesry
jmp0ut: china was working on broadspectrum antivirals a year prior to COVID-19
asselbergs: The French are fumbeling this worse than the USA even. The lockdown there is brutal.
Nussinov: will anyone learn their lesson?
skinnypuppy69: isnt the corona virus suspect for being engineered
lolzmaster99: But the lockdowns made the lowimpact possible
Turtle_L9: bro my brain gets tired after 2 hours of coding how you do it for hours straight?
l1ght5p33d: Engineered pathogen ::: poison dart frog on a stick
jmp0ut: @socialnotsocial the militaries of the world were concerned with the research on broadspectrum antivirals
Protoxus: Spain is implementing permanent UBI following coronavirus, which I find awesome
calcmath: Did you see the detailed medium post that outlined all the circumstantial evidence that it was lab made
jmp0ut: 2 years is about right
Santiago_LHC: "nothing to do with capital, it has to do with humans".... what's the difference? lol
balloonpopa: Thought 5G infrastructure is coming soon?
MrSheepe_: Hi
nihonzera: After postpone Olympics the numbers got higher here. Anyway, I think Japan still do very well considering the traditions (using masks by default, alcohol to clean hands everywhere..)
jmp0ut: if you look at the hotel and service industry directly correlated
balloonpopa: ...then exponential growth
tripcloth: epoch times told me this shit come out of a lab brah
tisd_: Why is Pakistan doing fine, i am from Pakistan btw
l1ght5p33d: noooo
skinnypuppy69: why did the chinese lie about cases
kevin21071: lol well if it did, means it can be now
axlebear: holy shit
jmp0ut: look at the stock prices of hotel and resort companies
deepfrieddeals: ooh are we talking stocks here?
jmp0ut: exact same as DOW
Thotshotgg: How does a virus just escape
Abnico: it isnt real, its 5g
ofaas: did you read reports of china buying up mask supplies from abroad while they were concealing the extent of the spread?
Penguino138: i got to this corona map way too often
WiseSwift: Oops
BumD197: is this 5G wars?
Santiago_LHC: Blame the dashboards
crawcraw66: 200k deaths tho, reasonable to panic
THX1342: what about the overwhelmed hospitals?
calcmath: what about hospitals overflowing?
therealariel666: There are rumors China is testing the cure on Pakistanis, which is kinda sad if its true.
Penguino138: French Daily cases dropped a few thousand if you look at daily cases
malledive: It's 10x deadlier than the flu.
THX1342: Italy
jmp0ut: Ontario, Canada, overwhelmed
crawcraw66: uk, italy
calcmath: italy/NY
therealariel666: Italy
tripcloth: nyc?
THX1342: Brazil is over capacity
Trr67: a lot of places
Ayowayway: good website design SeemsGood SeemsGood
marckkhoury: You think this is comparable to the flu?
Santiago_LHC: NYC
asselbergs: Italy, France, NYC
THX1342: Spain
pizzashotgun: @malledive based on current numbers
Trenz2: in italy they are..
asselbergs: Ecuador
pizzashotgun: the death rate is most likely lower
THX1342: Ecuador
lolzmaster99: New York transporting bodies in 18-wheelers
Jehhred: I've enjoyed working from home though. Keep the fear mongering high so I don't have to go back
Biffingtonn: What? Italy, Spain, NYC, Wuhan
DeeboMC: New York
Trr67: ???
ahahahaitslit: i think everything you've said about this is wrong
tripcloth: idk dood seems serious
Nussinov: yup this is true in minnesota
t0rment1337: more people died in italy last year march than this year march
THX1342: NYC, Ecuador, Spain, Italy
skinnypuppy69: we got lucky that it was a stupidly insignificant epidemic and not a actually threatening one, gives us good practice
AppleGrape: link for this?
lolzmaster99: I mean the volume of the transport
balloonpopa: just the first want right now
MrSheepe_: What do you think about US lockdown compared to South Africa's lockdown?
malledive: @pizzashotgun It might be even higher. Most people aren't tested post-mortem
kevin21071: yeah the hospitals where I live let a ton of people go
jmp0ut: why is the U.S. so oversaturated with virals
DeeboMC: Seattle?
Protoxus: I agree @skinnypuppy69.
calcmath: bodies in streets in ecuador
Thotshotgg: I think older folks should continue to isolate. But people need to get back to work and kids need to get back in school.
pizzashotgun: @malledive and it probably does permanent damage to the lungs
jmp0ut: is india and china worse?
balloonpopa: just the first wave right now
skinnypuppy69: thank you @Protoxus
THX1342: just wait to watch souther hemisphere winter....
WiseSwift: Wasn’t it the New York lockdown that contributed to that
patroniv: This has been an incredibly confusing time, made worse by the connectivity and the media. It seemed as though every week the truth was different and those to blame changed as well. Crazy
plazmacsgo: you have a point
Abnico: @georgehotz https://www.theverge.com/2020/4/24/21234457/apple-google-coronavirus-contact-tracing-tracker-exposure-notification-shut-down
cars1n: so corona is a joke?
skinnypuppy69: no one knew how to deal with it
azer0s: I mean...what about Italy? Hospitals in Austria were overwhelmed as well
jmp0ut: i think thats a joke
plazmacsgo: like the flu
Mariosavitch: so is obesity
therealariel666: Obesity
Turtle_L9: you are fear mongor
pizzashotgun: beard scratch noice nice
tisd_: In Pakistan lockdown is pretty tough, only groceries and stuff, roads are pretty much empty
tripcloth: if 10k later, why 1million now?
jmp0ut: it's a love bug
jmp0ut: cooties
MrSheepe_: Kim Jung Un death a hoax or nah?
Abnico: "Apple and Google pledge to shut down coronavirus tracker when pandemic ends"
skinnypuppy69: obesity is a free vaccine
cars1n: China learned from this pandemic and next virus it releases to the public will be much more deadly
nomemesplease: You said before this was a once in a 100 year event (vs 10 or 1000), still think so?
skinnypuppy69: running == vaccination
Abnico: particularly funny
DeeboMC: What about bill gates saying to expect a Pandemic about every 20 years from now on?
guinness84: how many unique coronavirus as time --> inf
pizzashotgun: China doesn't benefit from this pandemic
kevin21071: so it's official or is it still a rumor?
asselbergs: Weaponized influenza.
MrSheepe_: are you self taught?
cieph4: hey guys, China bad
Penguino138: @georgehotz have you ever messed with convolutional kernel image processing?
azer0s: bro no one benefits from this pandemic
FlySociety2o9: D:
balloonpopa: you see the documentary on the Spanish Flu?
socialnotsocial: are you interested in this? https://www.lifespan.io/road-maps/the-rejuvenation-roadmap/
jmp0ut: they're greedkeeping and dont wanna die
asselbergs: Bring Math to Medicine.
Ayowayway: D:
Krakatoa77: D:
jmp0ut: :(
l1ght5p33d: smoking cures corona
pizzashotgun: @azer0s exactly, i don't see why they would release it on pupose
AppleGrape: CAnnabis MAY CURE CORONA]
l1ght5p33d: weed only
Protoxus: Not true. I benefit from it 'cause it's likely to create more work-from-home jobs @azer0s
Penguino138: Car alarm in the background? Or is it cheering for the healthcare workers?
jmp0ut: TheIlluminati
asselbergs: http://evaxion-biotech.com/
Thotshotgg: Wouldnt there be evidence/record of COVID19 existing in a lab then if that is where it originated?
TheDkbay: @georgehotz It did cause irreversible lung damage to a lot of people though even if it didn't kill them that still sucks
Trenz2: @georgehotz how is comma going man ?
Protoxus: @TheDkbay Hey buddy
azer0s: @protoxus I mean...fair...but our economy was still majorly fucked by it.
Faceless_Bard: jesus add some margin on the left
azer0s: so yeah...single individuals might benefit
gaocaandra: quercetin and resveratrol really work
ofaas: i didnt watch your full corona genome stream, did you gain any new insights from looking at the genome?
gaocaandra: they are dope as fuck
Protoxus: @azer0s Sure, I don't have stocks right now, so it doesn't really harm me either
tripcloth: 5g airpods cause coronacancer u heard it here first
lolzmaster99: I'm not comfortable marginalizing the death of people who might've had 10-30 more years. It's kind of gross to write off life like that
gaocaandra: if you have asthma
Santiago_LHC: This has been going on for a while: https://medium.com/@tomaspueyo/coronavirus-act-today-or-people-will-die-f4d3d9cd99ca
azer0s: but overall it's still horrible for our economy
guinness84: LUL
asselbergs: Like Dengue, having this may be a setup, for a secondary fail.
forkdb: Hello george
DeeboMC: @lolzmaster99 Agreed
MABunglawala: Who is George working with rn?
balloonpopa: The virus has adaptability(mutations)... the human body has tolerance and intolerance
Nussinov: look at those CURVES
FlySociety2o9: lol
guinness84: he works for the cia
lolzmaster99: Yeah fuck Medium
azer0s: @protoxus yes...again... individuals are one thing, overall economy another
cookienz: THICC curves
Penguino138: What is California's reopening plan?
asselbergs: lol
forkdb: He works for nsa
Nussinov: act today, motivate a fatty to get on the treadmill
plazmacsgo: what do you think the world would be after the lockdown is over?
Santiago_LHC: Why does every single epidemiologist say different then?
Ayowayway: we could not know the otherwise
balloonpopa: it is a matter of exposure over time and how the body reacts over time
lolzmaster99: But that's in hindsight. We didn't know the dynamics
lolzmaster99: at first
Protoxus: azer0s Sure, but your initial statement was "no one benefits from this pandemix"
MABunglawala: yall bugging
guinness84: excitement
node_storm: what's up geo
forkdb: What do you think about Elon musk saying ‘people weee overacting about covid19”?
bloodborne24: life gets boring if it gets too easy
calcmath: cultural allergy
t0rment1337: there was a chinese flu in 1958, 2 million people died yet no one remembers that
jmp0ut: UK's medical licensing schemes are very future oriented
markodern: World war 3, for example?)
ofaas: my supermarket wont let me in without a mask now
azer0s: @protoxus that is correct. if our economy is fucked, in the long term, even if you benefit rn, you gonna be fucked as well
asselbergs: Heading in. Thanks again for a good session George. Go out and have some fun out there.
JdPaulBlart: lockdown aint over until schools open up
Penguino138: The world after lockdown: Digging sand out of skate parks
forkdb: Ohh. Really
tribegvng: yo
pizzashotgun: the chat delay seems really low
deepfrieddeals: Until they remove the sand at the skatepark we’re still on lockdown.
WiseSwift: Girls aren’t letting me smash. Lockdown isn’t over.
jmp0ut: economy of pension plans is fucked hard
forkdb: But there was no cure
azer0s: it's more like temporarily fucked
lolzmaster99: So the prolonging is the wrong move not the initial policy? I can agree with that
plazmacsgo: damn in new jersey we are still in lockdown and im on my senior year
727_tf: couldnt there just be a mandatory mask thing and we get on with our lives
jmp0ut: unless we all turn instant billinoaires
jmp0ut: and then what
balloonpopa: the virus is affecting more than just the respitory system
Newlax: crypto is future
Ham3113: i wanna start implementing neural nets tommorow for the first time. where do i start?
l1ght5p33d: Hodling
forkdb: When do you think the cure would be available?
l1ght5p33d: Alwaysss hoddlingg
patroniv: Stonks
tribegvng: centivax got the antibodies
balloonpopa: yes the economy will come back
Thotshotgg: @balloonpopa what else is it affecting
Santiago_LHC: There is this Mamoru Oshii (Ghost in The Shell) movie called The Sky Crawlers, which is about clones which take part on this made up war, just because mankind needs conflict to endure.
therealariel666: "never
l1ght5p33d: when you're rich enough
skinnypuppy69: everyone buy stocks now while things are low
ofaas: would you get a corona vaccination?
Nussinov: now that youre talking about corona title your stream "reverse engineering the virus" again Kappa
skinnypuppy69: with your mattress money
guinness84: no cure is worrying if more unique coronaviruses pop up
balloonpopa: blood clotting, the liver, the heart, the brian
plazmacsgo: LOL
forkdb: Ohhh.. man... am feeling saaad nowwww
azer0s: I mean...there is Oseltamivir and there's a vaccine for the flu
balloonpopa: Google covid toes
Abnico: bill gates said the lockdown should continue until the vaccine
FancyDawg_: why
plazmacsgo: you never know when the market will buttom out
azer0s: so...there's kind of a cure for influenza b at least
WiseSwift: Lmao
FancyDawg_: why wouldnt you get a vaccine for cov19
l1ght5p33d: i like my virus raw like my meat
WiseSwift: Anti flu shot wild
FancyDawg_: you didnt get one for swine flu?
LordHord: Covid toes?
Penguino138: @georgehotz thanks for the streams today, was great to have you back!
Jski101: Get the vaccine 30 days ago
calcmath: do you think there are methods to foster cooperation , other than religion, capitalism and the governemnt?
tripcloth: >>> corona_virus_vaccine == mark_of_the_beast True
Thotshotgg: YEah we missed you
Abnico: vaccines give u autism
trconway: Favourite ML paper?
Newlax: why don't you get a flu shot? @georgehotz
balloonpopa: no flu shot here either
技術宅: sushiWOW
jmp0ut: @Santiago_LHC more interestingly Tsutomu Ohashii who made the musical score of Akira is likely working on these problems now considering his research into consciousness, more likely to create genetic variants and invariants than clones
skinnypuppy69: leave lockdown 30 days ago
darthbearjew666: Can we model how much inflation the stimulus will cause on food and rent prices? Also, what if the stimulus produces data supporting UBI plans like Yang’s?
技術宅: facts
forkdb: I love you George.. you read all my chat, am happy now
Sharlock93: do you miss the jailbreak days george?
Trenz2: but what if the gov pushes you to take a vaccine ? how you feel about it ?
bloodborne24: -380 gang LUL
azer0s: @people who said crypto is the answer: crypto sux.
kingvoneduard: Everybody knows now that is a laboratory made virus.
plazmacsgo: is there a reason why you think its a scam?
Santiago_LHC: @jmp0ut That's fascinating
Kiskiss: gang gang
jmp0ut: N-4 center DNA strands in heavy water or higher gravity environments
Thotshotgg: Whats going to happen to oil prices
Abnico: de urbanization would be cool though
socialnotsocial: What do you think of Girard's mimetic theory? We copy our desires form others and imitate them and the implications of such tendencies.
jmp0ut: nitrogen centers are intruiging
lolzmaster99: What will it take for wider adoption of decentralized currency?
jmp0ut: synthetic DNA
Nussinov: what do you mean most of medicine is a scam? that sounds like an extreme take
kingvoneduard: Made and escape :)
kevin21071: JPOW go brrrrr
DeeboMC: What do you think about this?
tribegvng: 😂
jmp0ut: can't be affected by viruses and bacteria in the same way
deepfrieddeals: The best way to avoid getting the flu is to avoid contact with coworkers that have children.
Aceinyourface: alright we reverse engineered that covid lets go boys
DeeboMC: Bill Gates warns that a coronavirus-like outbreak will probably happen ‘every 20 years or so’ https://www.businessinsider.com/bill-gates-warns-coronavirus-outbreak-likely-every-20-years-2020-4
cookienz: 😂 OIL HAS CRASHED! oh wait where did those jobs go
calcmath: it can only cause inflation if it incresed spending, but with decresed spending due to lockdown, i doubt this will cause inflation
darthbearjew666: Hell us understand negative oil prices
jmp0ut: there's even a programming language called SBOL to create synthetic life forms
jmp0ut: including viruses
thediamnd: !uptime
balloonpopa: worth a watch... https://youtu.be/UDY5COg2P2c
deepfrieddeals: young ish
WiseSwift: What if you get tetanus?
kingvoneduard: Placebo is better
Protoxus: -(2^8+2^7-4)
jmp0ut: SBOL is an open standard for the representation of in silico biological designs.
SOmedude456: bacterial infections
Nussinov: LUL
pizzashotgun: most regular medicine is just treating symptoms
Santiago_LHC: comma.med
Aceinyourface: where we at master george
Newlax: You should make a crypto for comma!
balloonpopa: haha
Abnico: doubt https://www.theverge.com/2020/4/24/21234457/apple-google-coronavirus-contact-tracing-tracker-exposure-notification-shut-down
tripcloth: Exxon staff changed hands, time to start the area51 hack op bois
Nussinov: I mean obviously some diseases and things are treated with drugs, so what you're saying can't be right
forkdb: One last question... what advice do you give for a beginner programmer? To become an expert in problem solving and coding
azer0s: @newlax problem is that crypto kinda sux
l1ght5p33d: There's no way the virus came from the lab why would it spread fast from that point but not from it's original point
tisd_: I think people realize, now how fucked is US Healthcare
skinnypuppy69: @georgehotz what do you think about renewable energy industry? wind energy in particular? does it have a future?
Abnico: its already on ur phone
plazmacsgo: is there a reason why you are using mac and not linux?
ez_clappers_: i just want them to put more sand in the skate parks. fuck those skaters
Aceinyourface: we need socialism bro
Aceinyourface: simple as that
jmp0ut: https://sbolstandard.org/applications/
Santiago_LHC: #optimism
simmy7: the US is the kid with gucci belt
jmp0ut: make your own chimera today!
Kiskiss: is the world going to be a better place after covid?
gaocaandra: since when does the government need you to install an app to track you? it's a ploy by google and apple
jmp0ut: how does conservation of geothermal energy work
balloonpopa: pull up Covid Toes on the screen
Santiago_LHC: Conservatives
kingvoneduard: Atomic energy is better
skinnypuppy69: @georgehotz i dont wanna conserve but i want a job, is it feasible
worraaa: so how was the theorem proving stuff?
jmp0ut: agreed @kingvoneduard Thorium in the oceans can fuel humans almost indefinitely
skinnypuppy69: okay okay i see
plazmacsgo: is there a reason why you are using mac and not linux?
Newlax: but think about Africa
DeeboMC: Read this:
THX1342: our sole purpose in the universe is to consume energy to increase complexity
skinnypuppy69: wind energy
Penguino138: How many more people will distrust the news after lockdowns are all over?
skinnypuppy69: oof
forkdb: One last question... what advice do you give for a beginner programmer? To become an expert in problem solving and coding
Protoxus: @plazmacsgo unix is unix
jmp0ut: almost being exploding earth from solar luminosity is unavoidable currently
plazmacsgo: I see
DeeboMC: Bill Gates warns that a coronavirus-like outbreak will probably happen ‘every 20 years or so’ https://www.businessinsider.com/bill-gates-warns-coronavirus-outbreak-likely-every-20-years-2020-4
mazsociety: has chewing ice been confirmed as a covid cure yet?
Abnico: https://metagame.wtf/ open source religon
socialnotsocial: Thoughts on seasteading?
bloodborne24: install gentoo Kappa
plazmacsgo: does docker work on mac?
Thotshotgg: The news is criminal
calcmath: what if the discount factor provided by capitalism is inaccurate in predictiong the value of the windmill
DeeboMC: He says it with no evidence to support it
Nussinov: news in 2020
Faceless_Bard: humans forget :) they will keep trusting news
azer0s: unpopular opinion: the US is the richest 3rd world country in the world...like....I don't wanna shit on the US. But hear me out here: education in the US is a hoax, many people can't afford healthcare, public transport barely works, the FDA is a hoax
balloonpopa: Google Covid Toes
FileTheSystem: why the 20 years though. why not 10 or 30
Protoxus: @plazmacsgo https://lmgtfy.com/?q=docker+on+mac
manirte: what do you think about brave browser?
DeeboMC: Why?
Penguino138: I thought after the 2016 election everyone would hate the news, but still many trust them. I hope this time is different
darthbearjew666: Ya Covid toes is cray
pizzashotgun: the food pyramid was made by the department of agriculture
Thotshotgg: Freedom
tribegvng: braves gone shit lately
alfyfav: Freedom?
Nussinov: bill gates believes the biggest threat to mankind is a pandemic
Faceless_Bard: amerikan dream
lolzmaster99: Capital makes the US 'great'
ahahahaitslit: 'murica
Krakatoa77: Freedomland
lolzmaster99: We're not even that free
bloodborne24: freedom aint free KKona
balloonpopa: The DeVos family are scammers
newlifestartsnow: you never lived in Russia
Abnico: the us is great cause of punanai
SOmedude456: yo hotz are you Jewish?
lolzmaster99: Rights infringed daily
pizzashotgun: singapore go brrr
cieph4: KKonaW
jmp0ut: https://sbolstandard.org/publications/
newlifestartsnow: its shitholeeee
gaocaandra: you dont have rights in australia?
socialnotsocial: Thoughts on seasteading?
Krakatoa77: Freedomland KKona
Eyachi: thats so bullshit though there are so many other countries that have "freedom" and all those things so much better
jmp0ut: human hardware abstraction layer development
kingvoneduard: You cannot have socialism and freedom.
iamnotdmt: Australia is really bad, people not realise
pizzashotgun: ^
gaocaandra: you cant get out of student debt
jmp0ut: maybe you dont need freedom
deepfrieddeals: Plenty of countries have freedom
jmp0ut: just socialism
tisd_: How to not panic about Corona: Don't listen to the media.
lolzmaster99: We're not free we're wage slaves, extorted by corporations
skinnypuppy69: @georgehotz the push for "clean" electricity, like tesla, solar companies, wind farms, is that ever going to pick up over gas cars and coal companies
gaocaandra: no
spockshocks: court system is on the way to being politically compromised
dr_set: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VMqcLUqYqrs
Abnico: almost like bill gates made money cause of the hype..
balloonpopa: haha
Thotshotgg: Bring Snowden home
birkett0011: bureaucracy in Aus is bad
WiseSwift: Good joke
plazmacsgo: Ye I am not going to college to not get student dept
iamnotdmt: Australia ; you cant pay more then $10k cash for anything, we will be one of the first cashless society's
FileTheSystem: USA has the poorest labor law
Protoxus: Because of covid, the Danish government went "Our equivalent of the 4th ammendment? Yeah, doesn't apply anymore."
toxyviper: u being in Russia? SeriousSloth
ez_clappers_: i just want them to put more sand in the skate parks. fuck those skaters
jmp0ut: with socialism snowden would have his christmas coffee which is all he wanted
donasaurus: You can get out of student debt don't get a bullshit degree.
ofaas: in my country you should never talk politics to anyone ever because every second person is a government informant
birkett0011: bureaucracy
Eyachi: cause goverments can be good lol
balloonpopa: The US has class warfare
Eyachi: ours is just trash
mazsociety: plenty of countries may have freedom, but only 1 has in n out
Thotshotgg: HA
ofaas: jordan
jmp0ut: all Snowden wanted was to be home feel safe and have a coffee from his fav barrista
gaocaandra: i dont think it's as black and white
dr_set: That's Chomsky's opinion, not the media
deepfrieddeals: We need more anti government attitude. Too many are oblivious, worrying about superficial social bs
ahahahaitslit: ayy lmao
balloonpopa: This is class warfare, and my class is winning - Warren Buffet
Penguino138: Wonder how many sheep will convert compared to the 2016 election mess
borang: 1st year salary is like 2x college tuition + loans for rent and shit. dont get why ppl complain
lolzmaster99: You;re privileged
plazmacsgo: do you think we can be multi-planetary species ?
jmp0ut: buffett is an oldie foldie
balloonpopa: haha
rickoftheroot: LUL
Abnico: go to milwaukee george
azer0s: live in Austria. it's kinda great. so is Portugal and basically any other EU country. yes...you can't glorify WW2...so not free speech. but imo that's not as important to me as the other things I mentioned.
gaocaandra: how free is snowden?maning?schwartz?
skinnypuppy69: is privilege real
Penguino138: Paris is great
ez_clappers_: i just want them to put more sand in the skate parks. fuck those skaters
socialnotsocial: Thoughts on seasteading?
jmp0ut: schwarts is dead
Thotshotgg: Applied to Google today. Cant wait to get the rejection letter
calcmath: baster rest endpoints for food
guinness84: be honored i wrote this backend bro
balloonpopa: This is class warfare, and my class is winning - Warren Buffet
azer0s: @gaocaandra +1
lolzmaster99: Again, you're privileged
jmp0ut: manning is free
pwnbase: root vs user
bloodborne24: american clerks can be brusque but genuine
borang: @ez_clappers_ lol fuck you
DeeboMC: @guinness84 Lmao
jmp0ut: snowden is sitting in a pidgeon coop
pizzashotgun: george white george bad funny !
ahahahaitslit: or if you're good looking
kingvoneduard: Obama has privileges.
manorambo: did you see about that album of h4x0r r007z
727_tf: how do we censor the fake media oof
skinnypuppy69: i like this george guy
Jehhred: Lebron James kids have privilege...
deepfrieddeals: Privilege is real but it’s not as pervasive as purported.
toxyviper: Japan is the best country in a world, for Japanese KappaRoss @georgehotz
skinnypuppy69: hes smart
Abnico: george, stop mansplaning
alfyfav: If you're in that situation you're privileged to THAT country
worraaa: codejam 1C next week? Kappa
THX1342: 727_tf you don't censor.. you learn how to consume proper information
forkdb: One last question.... what advice do you give for a beginner programmer? To become an expert in problem solving and coding
dr_set: so you are saying that if you are white and middle class you get caught with a joint you get the same treatment that if you are black and poor?
Thotshotgg: George you should run for political office one day
gaocaandra: how free is snowden? maning? schwartz?
WiseSwift: Race does have an effect even when you normalize for income
cookienz: some people have never touched java
balloonpopa: This is class warfare, and my class is winning - Warren Buffet
plazmacsgo: how do you know if you are smart?
THX1342: 727_tf people need to get smarter instead of government censoring 'fake news'
jmp0ut: some humans are janked from the other priviledged, if you aren't stuck in a refugee deadzone eating reconstituted cardboard for govt subsidy handouts that pay the controllers exponentially greater sums
quinquanonagintilliard: @plazmacsgo my momma told me
jmp0ut: then it's a greedkeeping wageslavery to babyrun scenarios
plazmacsgo: @quinquanonagintilliard LOL
azer0s: do you think there is a "greatest country in the world"? if so, why that country?
Penguino138: @georgehotz do you think they'll open up international flights incrementally and slowly over time? How slow?
balloonpopa: haha
727_tf: @THX1342 wouldnt that involve schools, which have government involvement. Or would it be a person to person type of thing
plazmacsgo: I don't think you can really classify how smart a person is
bloodborne24: KKona
TheCellarDoor: Denmark
jmp0ut: mad lemur
jmp0ut: 2020
stone43_: Antartica, very few people
gaocaandra: the american empire will fall
gcbourdon: thoughts on trump?
patroniv: Biggest privilege, good looking, smart, or rich?
socialnotsocial: Thoughts on seasteading?
Protoxus: @TheCellarDoor What about Denmark?
Abnico: yang 2024
toxyviper: MingLee
jmp0ut: thoughts on COVID-19 from eating fruitbats?
TheCellarDoor: @Protoxus Greatest country in the world
rickoftheroot: LUL
THX1342: 727_tf you don't need schools if you have access to information (i.e. internet). the thing is most people including those who have access to great schools, choose to consume shit 24/7.
balloonpopa: What is more important clean water and reliable electricity... or 5G?
Protoxus: @TheCellarDoor I live there. It's really not.
rickoftheroot: marcus aurelius ftw
Santiago_LHC: Biden = Caesar Kappa
deepfrieddeals: George is so positive. Must be all that California sun ☀️
gaocaandra: we need globalism in the cloud bro
azer0s: how would you fix the education system for good tho?
Thotshotgg: I really want to go to the movies again.
toxyviper: Trump 2024 esy game KappaClaus
darthbearjew666: Is it possible to create true direct democracy by voting on blockchain ??
birkett0011: joe biden
gaocaandra: lets all share a server
bloodborne24: pax colombiano
METH_HEAD_MIKE: KKona thats trump
skinnypuppy69: what is "american prosperity/ the singularity"?
DeeboMC: Was the boat Scientologist?
Penguino138: Won't we not know its the empire until deep into it? Or after it falls?
TheCellarDoor: @Protoxus What do you think is the greatest county in the world? (Assuming there is such a thing)
pizzashotgun: imagine joe biden destroying trump
ahahahaitslit: the two front runners are biden and trump lol
Protoxus: @TheCellarDoor Switzerland
jmp0ut: Emperor Augustus started christianity by sending ferrets to eat the rabies rabbits
jmp0ut: way cooler
ahahahaitslit: what a joke
t0rment1337: they would put the caesar in jail before he gets anywhere near the power like shkreli
THX1342: a Putin?
azer0s: @thecellardoor Austria
TheCellarDoor: @Protoxus =) That's where i live
kingvoneduard: Joe Biden will lose nuclear codes in the bus toilet.
gaocaandra: whats a cesar? a fourth gen harvard atendee?
Santiago_LHC: They both suck
THX1342: ooohh Cesar not Czzar Kappa
Protoxus: @azer0s Nah, Austria's hate speech laws are very, very strict
jmp0ut: religion from rabies
newlifestartsnow: people hate Putin in Russia
jasondesante: one has dementia though
Trenz2: George do you watch Joe Rogan ? :D
FileTheSystem: the senate
gaocaandra: the MAN
METH_HEAD_MIKE: the deep state monkaS
guinness84: the DEEP STATE
ahahahaitslit: illuminati
gaocaandra: they are the man
plazmacsgo: there should be more popular/main parties
gaocaandra: bro
birkett0011: Everything is about individuals today. Not about the institutions behind them
socialnotsocial: Thoughts on seasteading?
DecayingSkullz: Marcus Aurelius' birthday today
lolzmaster99: Legitimacy should come from technical prowess/domain expertise
Krakatoa77: the lizard people
Protoxus: @TheCellarDoor Nice. I've heard Switzerland's education system is pretty messed up, but other than that I think it's a very nice country.
end_zeit: TheIlluminati
Penguino138: @georgehotz what would a Cesar look like policy wise nowadays?
azer0s: @protoxus imo...not a bad thing. it's not top priority *for me*
Thotshotgg: George, You are the Caesar lol
guinness84: 📐
jmp0ut: if everyone is the deep state then it's cool
kingvoneduard: Deep State is crap
toxyviper: SirShield defend murika
jmp0ut: mommy and daddy = deep state
gaocaandra: start the church
DeeboMC: What about the pentagon Microsoft cloud “scandal”?
gaocaandra: common
SOmedude456: what do you think about the rothschilds
balloonpopa: A blank vote is a protest vote... stay engaged, but vote for no one if a viable candidate is not presented
Protoxus: @azer0s Yeah, good point.
calcmath: would blockchain be the casesar?
patroniv: The Karen’s
Trenz2: the caesar of computers then :D
THX1342: how can you be pro-freedom and at the same time hope for a dictator? I don't get it
DeeboMC: Bro...
ahahahaitslit: any thoughts on stephen wolfram's physics announcement?
kingvoneduard: Soros made the virus with Bill Gates
norB88: who's spartacus
gaocaandra: let's go to the desert and smoke toads
balloonpopa: haha... think about it
skinnypuppy69: use your own brain to vote who wants what you want
stone43_: more muzero, less not muzero
THX1342: because you can't question a dictator
routerkicker: do you think some people have access to every computer system in the world if they wanted?
Thotshotgg: By definition
THX1342: you obey and that's all
Penguino138: @georgehotz where on the political spectrum would be a caeser?
plazmacsgo: well because he has all the power
kingvoneduard: Kim Jo if he survive can be the next Dictator
DeeboMC: https://www.bitchute.com/video/fVoOoiwA10ql/
calcmath: would a muzero like algorithm eventually run corporations and countries?
quinquanonagintilliard: Why dictator? what about king?
prakyath_kantharaju: How can there be a dictator with freedom
lolzmaster99: Yeah please increase paper streams
skinnypuppy69: if a dictator is a good idea then why not go to russia or china?
l1ght5p33d: Asassinated
TheCellarDoor: @Protoxus It is a very nice country. Our education system certainly can use some improvement. I love our political system. But your healthcare system is the best in the world.
azer0s: @protoxus I mean...I can see that other people might see it differently. "That's just like...uh...my...uh...opinion man"
THX1342: no, they outsource that to local powers
lolzmaster99: i will subscribe for paper streams
gaocaandra: we need a multivac dictator
cookienz: yeah north korea have loads of freedom right guys
qlutoo: Tech CEO Monarch
prakyath_kantharaju: a dictator can kill his opponents
names_for_noobs: The dictator doesn't have to be a tyrant
DeeboMC: DEMOCRATS AMBUSHED OVER ISRAEL & MICROSOFT & PENTAGON CLOUD SECURITY
qlutoo: Tech CEO Monarchy
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: https://youtu.be/Ir7wCAQINqw@georgehotz
thuganalyst: imo the dictators of UAE are alright
skinnypuppy69: then why is russia so horrible they have a dictator
ahahahaitslit: how can anyone ensure a dictator wouldn't be a totalitarian
l1ght5p33d: we will make them fear us
ahahahaitslit: that's the issue
darthbearjew666: REPLACE ALL THE CONGRESSMEN WITH AI WHO VOTE BASED ON BLOCKCHAIN VOTES FROM THEIR CONSTITUENTS?
Santiago_LHC: Nancy Pelosi is playing animal crossing right now
l1ght5p33d: ::: drones :::
WiseSwift: A dictator prevents a better dictator from taking over
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz https://youtu.be/Ir7wCAQINqw future PogChamp PogChamp
Protoxus: @TheCellarDoor The waiting times can be really bad here. And I don't think our extreme tax rates justify the health care. But yeah, it works pretty efficiently with regular doctor appointments
74c55639: he has full power to design the system that will have full control over your life, he doesn't need to personally micromanage your life.
tripcloth: nancy palosi and zuckerburg have the same lizard dna for sure dude
deepfrieddeals: Nancy is passed out from drinking right now
calcmath: have you watched Westworld?
DeeboMC: DEMOCRATS AMBUSHED OVER ISRAEL & MICROSOFT & PENTAGON CLOUD SECURITY
Penguino138: So the US is still a republic yet we have military bases everywhere and attempt to overthrow govts?
darthbearjew666: REPLACE ALL THE CONGRESSMEN WITH AI WHO VOTE BASED ON BLOCKCHAIN VOTES FROM THEIR CONSTITUENTS?
DeeboMC: “American Jewish activist Jeremy Rothe Kushell ambushes Democrat presidential hopefuls on the issue of The Pentagon Cloud and American national security with regards Israel. This is amazing historical footage. ”
plazmacsgo: our caesar will be an AI lol
Mrclutch963: What do you think about what happened in North Korea? @georgehotz
jmp0ut: vasectomy?
gaocaandra: jajaajaajaaj
THX1342: I do frequently think about that... how 'to solve shit we need a dictator'... but I can't live with the thought of living under one... coming from a country that had military dictatorship recently
kingvoneduard: A Dictature is disfunctional because everybody wait for the Dictator to take the decision.
skinnypuppy69: half of this chat wants AI to rule all lol
gaocaandra: wtf
M0gami: @georgehotz how hot is new North Korean leader on scale from 1 -10 ?
DeeboMC: https://www.bitchute.com/video/fVoOoiwA10ql/
WiseSwift: Bring dan carlin on the stream
balloonpopa: Coumo may get assassinated... or disappeared
l1ght5p33d: wtf
QUOTE_IF_NEXT_YEAR_BETTER: do you think china has developed technological singularity?
thuganalyst: Have you considered beating the stock market using AI?
Lourned: isnt he the guy who murdered germans?
DecayingSkullz: what are your thoughts on drone technology?
socialnotsocial: What do you think about seasteading?
balloonpopa: The down fall of the Roman empire was lead poisoning
AveonGOJO: china isn't real
norB88: read Isac Asimovs Foundation series? Maybe need a side thing going on as he had it there.
plazmacsgo: @thuganalyst many have tried
THX1342: absolute power corrupts absolutelly
stone43_: AI can't beat the stock market
DeeboMC: Do you not want to talk about that?
Penguino138: Dont we have more military bases than all other countries? And try to topple other govts?
l1ght5p33d: 1) get fake money 2) cure all the things
gaocaandra: people in flint got dat fre dom
azer0s: no but for real...how would you fix the education system for good? Because I 100% agree that in it's current form it's a scam that's not meant to educate but to pull money out of people's pockets. but what's the solution?
tkdboy555: look up the song technocracy by samsa
Goooshlrific: what is love?
l1ght5p33d: Like Elon have to get the money first
plazmacsgo: don't u think we should have an AI as a president?
l1ght5p33d: its required
Krakatoa77: Well caesar was killed before it could've become worse
kingvoneduard: Cesar was only for some 10 years before they kill him.
THX1342: Alexander the Great was pretty chill
bloodborne24: CROSS THE RUBICON SwiftRage
Lourned: Nero was the best Kappa
ahahahaitslit: facts don't care about your feelings
pwnbase: Beware that, when fighting monsters, you yourself do not become a monster... for when you gaze long into the abyss. The abyss gaze back into you
newlifestartsnow: What do you think about AI bots beating Dota 2 pro players?
darthbearjew666: Geohot for Prez
gaocaandra: claudio
stone43_: Make everyone drink Brawndo
deepfrieddeals: That’s the hypocrisy of the blaming the Russians for the 2016. We’ve been installing dictators and US-friendly regimes for 100 years and we’re angry we got a taste of our own medicine?
t0rment1337: the banter between republicans and democrats keeps america going tho
Penguino138: @georgehotz What kind of policies would a 21st century Caeser type champion?
skinnypuppy69: if dictatorship was so good then why hasnt it worked since roman times? @georgehotz
gaocaandra: claudio was the vest
Trenz2: Dude its not going to be in this modern world , it cant be ... not possible
prakyath_kantharaju: the dictator will be good if he/she has no power of the financial market and free speech
14btw: who says he didnt?
axlebear: What would happen If China develops real artificial intelligence first?
DeeboMC: China spies on Israel to get US’s secrets.. you see a problem there?
Lourned: I mean anyone can influence the US election not just Russians
THX1342: deebomc everybody spies on everybody else
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: There is nothing wrong with spying
THX1342: USA is influencing elections all the time all around the world LUL
gaocaandra: of course it isn't the same the context is vastly different.
DeeboMC: That’s not my point @thx1342
calcmath: there werent other republics inthose though
dr_set: The British Empire had a dictator, it depends on what you call "worked fine"
azer0s: @skinnypuppy69 doesn't the saying go like "democracy is bad but it's the best we got"?
jmp0ut: @deebomc nothing wrong, Israel is so greedkeeping they murdered Aaron Swartz with policymaking
Thotshotgg: People really do be drinking bleach doe. smh.
Penguino138: What were Caeser's plitical views?
Suspecthum: Augustus FTW
deepfrieddeals: China won’t develop real AI first. George will.
verxile: whats up, whats the goal for tonight?
skinnypuppy69: @azer0s havent heard that saying but go on
jontowtruck: did he ever solve cartpole?
plazmacsgo: wouldn't it be cool if we can make an ai that learns from history and predicts the most probable outcomes fro a given situation or something like that?
Protoxus: @jontowtruck Yes
DeeboMC: @jmp0ut @thx1342 https://www.bitchute.com/video/fVoOoiwA10ql/
jontowtruck: atta girl
jontowtruck: nice
kingvoneduard: Cesar fucked Cleopatra
just_a_coder: bro you are awesome
jmp0ut: that video doesnt load for me
chupakraw: thats a wierd looking protien
jmp0ut: dunno
Mrclutch963: do you trust wikipedia? @georgehotz
l1ght5p33d: Is the shadow government wheel
just_a_coder: bro you are awesome :)
l1ght5p33d: does anyone know linux well enough
skinnypuppy69: i came for the code, but stayed for the questions
gaocaandra: of course it isn't the same the context is vastly different.
therealariel666: You have the 16inch Mac right?
bloodborne24: ai F1 racer Kreygasm
lolzmaster99: Read Francois Chollet's paper on AGI to get persepctive
Thotshotgg: What ignited your passion for AI?
ez_clappers_: @georgehotz when will ai be better than people
lolzmaster99: Michae Jordan has the right idea about ML
un3okapi: do you know what a simp means?
Penguino138: Make AI Caeser
ahahahaitslit: what if it's american putin
gaocaandra: elon should
just_a_coder: @georgehotz bro you are awesome bro
THX1342: @georgehotz if AGI happens do you think it's a 1st mover takes over the world kind of deal?
Santiago_LHC: Anakin Skywalker moment
QUOTE_IF_NEXT_YEAR_BETTER: that's because humans are bad at developing AI, you understand how evolution happens right bro?
74c55639: @georgehotz do you still hold the hope for a self-driving car, or did that fade away?
axlebear: As in an AI that can improve its own code
plazmacsgo: well a president doesn't really have to be smart he just has to hire smart people
Trenz2: The AI Caesar LUL
gaocaandra: all hail elon
Lourned: Trump used to be smart, now he is 80 years old FeelsBadMan
kingvoneduard: Kim Jon Un would be a fat Cezar if he survive
azer0s: @skinnypuppy69 yeah...I think Churchill said something about democracy being the worst form of government except for all other forms of government and I kinda agree
prakyath_kantharaju: AI is good in confined boundary and very well defined rule system
Penguino138: @georgehotz Would this Caeser be a left or right wing?
kevin21071: What about the show Devs Geroge? They predict the future there Kappa
deepfrieddeals: Term limits
cookienz: Caeser! powered by a intern that took discrete maths
just_a_coder: bro you are awesome
jmp0ut: i'm waiting on synthetic sapient sentient artificial intelligence with the ability to spin up time cycles
Mrclutch963: how powerful is AI really? @georgehotz
THX1342: trump is rich, not smart
Gamer_nohope: Caeser 2.0
Trenz2: Ego Maniac ?
jmp0ut: i heard soulmachines.com is trying for it
THX1342: LUL
FileTheSystem: there are many people with Ceasar attributes but they often make it in private sector rather than risking their talents in politics
verxile: do we need self driving cars, or should we plan on self driving flying taxis
balloonpopa: The Roman empire lined thier acueducts with lead paint... that was thier downfall
ahahahaitslit: why the hell are the two frontrunners 80
jasondesante: Trump is the King of Ventilators
jmp0ut: DNA spooky action at a distance with 5G technology
DeeboMC: Talk about it: DEMOCRATS AMBUSHED OVER ISRAEL & MICROSOFT & PENTAGON CLOUD SECURITY https://www.bitchute.com/video/fVoOoiwA10ql/
jmp0ut: optogenomic warfare
gaocaandra: there is a letterman interview were you see trum on his element
balloonpopa: lead poising
gaocaandra: the guy is from a different time
plazmacsgo: @Mrclutch963 no as much as you think probably. it needs a lot of data and other restrictions
THX1342: LUL
lolzmaster99: Can you talk about the application of RL to self-driving as far as where in the model pipeline it fits? Are you guys working on it yet?
Santiago_LHC: Elon Caesar?
Pr0ject414: he cant he isnt natural born citizen
jmp0ut: Elon Musk does what royalty should do
birkett0011: IN MUSK WE TRUST
kingvoneduard: Elon Musk would send everybody on Mars
jasondesante: LUL Elon would not want to waste his time doing that
darthbearjew666: Agreeeeeeeeeed
plazmacsgo: @georgehotz Elon must is definitely a good choice
Trenz2: @georgehotz what about Elon be the president of US ?
QUOTE_IF_NEXT_YEAR_BETTER: stephen hawking
plazmacsgo: musk
skinnypuppy69: @azer0s im failing to see how other forms of government supersede democracy, when democracy == freedom of thought and for it to be heard
Lourned: Elon Musk president of Mars LUL
Penguino138: Definitely need to look up what political views Julius had now
gaocaandra: there is a novel where the dictator of mars is titled elon
jmp0ut: what kind of kings and queens sit around getting fat off chocolate bonbons
Faceless_Bard: 'natural born' lol
THX1342: His plan is Emperor of Mars
kingvoneduard: Elon Musk will be the Dictator of Mars
jmp0ut: instead of doing elon musk work
Pr0ject414: if we arnt talking about president then theres a discussion LOL
jontowtruck: do you think trump will push for an armed conflict against china to gain support for november
deepfrieddeals: Is Musk still seeing that Grimes chick?
plazmacsgo: do yoiu think we will be able to colonize other planets?
quinquanonagintilliard: Dicator + mars = mad max
Pr0ject414: he could certainly bomb us
skinnypuppy69: @jontowtruck no
FileTheSystem: these people are smart they know better ways to spend their time rather than in politics
jontowtruck: lmao
JdPaulBlart: mars is the neww epstein sex island but its elon musk and bill gates
Mrclutch963: do you trust wikipedia? @georgehotz
thuganalyst: man I just wanna have infinite catgirls in my BMI VR
azer0s: @skinnypuppy69 yes...that is what I said. democracy is better than everything else. it's just still not good.
QUOTE_IF_NEXT_YEAR_BETTER: overt war is dead
azer0s: the thing is...if musk were to take over the government...he'd have a plan.
ahahahaitslit: epstein did not kill himself
Santiago_LHC: Have you seen the show DEVS? It's about determinism and an experiment with a quantum computer to recreate reality in a simulation.
fedexkinkos: why u learning this , learn react instead
prakyath_kantharaju: musk has created more jobs and more money in US than trump
forkdb: What if Elon buys comma in the future? Any thoughts
Trenz2: why arms ? why wars ? why this sheet..
Jehhred: Watching the conference with Jack Ma and Elon Musk is hilarious
bloodborne24: speak softly and carry a big nuke
kingvoneduard: Trump and Xi are best friends
skinnypuppy69: @azer0s ahhh i see. its hard to read what you said when chat keeps moving
Pr0ject414: just waiting for north koreans to find out he does infact have a butthole.
DeeboMC: Bro... is anyone willing to talk about this.. this video was removed from YouTube Talk about it: DEMOCRATS AMBUSHED OVER ISRAEL & MICROSOFT & PENTAGON CLOUD SECURITY https://www.bitchute.com/video/fVoOoiwA10ql/
gaocaandra: well china is pretty "agressive"
Penguino138: @georgehotz How long until the people on mars form their own sovereignty?
Eyachi: 16 years.
socialnotsocial: Make deepfake of political leaders recommending citizens drink 1 liter of bleach for virus immunity. Witness natural selection in real time. B)
t0mmv: which gpu are you using?
calcmath: washington was also a caesaer
skinnypuppy69: @azer0s yes i totally agree, everything can be improved, complacency is a sickness
azer0s: @skinnypuppy69 +1
balloonpopa: History repeats itself... it's like a pendulum
gaocaandra: peron was a cesar
l1ght5p33d: no one is really going to want to live on mars
fedexkinkos: what is a caesar?
l1ght5p33d: its going to be military and science and industry only
forkdb: What if Elon buys comma ? Your thoughts....?!!
Pr0ject414: there was no limitation on those presidents though (Constitutionally)
DeeboMC: Let’s watch this video please Talk about it: DEMOCRATS AMBUSHED OVER ISRAEL & MICROSOFT & PENTAGON CLOUD SECURITY https://www.bitchute.com/video/fVoOoiwA10ql/
Eyachi: FDR was really good, need another person who cares about social issues as much
dr_set: Argentinian President
gaocaandra: o boi
Penguino138: It's crazy to think one day there could be a whole different clad of humans who have lived on mars for generations and is way different
Santiago_LHC: Ha, Peron
gaocaandra: hes the spice of argentina
skinnypuppy69: @azer0s +1? haha
kingvoneduard: Evita Peron was the dictator of Juan Peron
DecayingSkullz: ban deebomc
fedexkinkos: can anyone explain what a caesar is?
balloonpopa: haha Pero... no way
THX1342: Peron LUL
pwnbase: chat extra'd af
henryy95: !UPTIME
plazmacsgo: @forkdb he won't buy comma
plazmacsgo: he has autopilot
Lourned: Putin is god king pretty much, he is in power 20 years now
Pr0ject414: its a salad
skinnypuppy69: @georgehotz any ideas for my new raspberry pi??
crawcraw66: lmao
Faceless_Bard: its a salad
jontowtruck: it's like a chad
M0gami: Its a Salad 4Head
azer0s: @skinnypuppy69 I am agreeing with you lol
calcmath: caesar is a czar
rickoftheroot: caesar is a kaiser
Gamer_nohope: superchad LUL
DecayingSkullz: gn
balloonpopa: lol
THX1342: gn
azer0s: @skinnypuppy69 k8s cluster!
Suspecthum: Nooo
Santiago_LHC: Caesar is like the salad, minus the salad.
Thotshotgg: We love you
zounonz: gn
FileTheSystem: Cool hanging out here, later
unluckychickenn: squadL
Trenz2: gn
socialnotsocial: gnight geohot :)
Adictos: good morning
blndv: hi
liqo13: ay whatsup
lebop: hi first viewer
fadihirmiz: suh dude
InfiniteReddit: hello from aus
pioterexe: sup
the_benju: Letsss goooo
great_said: hi
LiveMahs: In hereeeee
singularitytoatea: Goooood mooornning
rmvaldesd: Hi!
cod4_lightning: 3 streams in one day oh yeeaaah
aiex42: Good mornin bro
lebop: hi from brazil
senad20: Hello from Germany
ionelaipatioaei: no more bio?
achamorro008: hello from Nicaragua
32bitrobo: good mornimg
grekler3: PogChamp
Deno_____: senad iz njemacke
knilecrack: nisi valjda
Deno_____: aaaa
Jehhred: That was a quick 7 hours
knilecrack: :D
0xtf: Hey George!
Deno_____: excuse me lord
grey_street: hello!
niceonesonny77: LETS GOOOOO FINALLY SOME CODING LIVE
ogrockefeller: Daddy Hotz
hanisa1: george will you marry me
aiex42: Canadian english?
thedevway: hiiii. this is the first time i'm watching you live instead of recorded streams on youtube :)
knilecrack: what if subbs speak non-english only?
DzyaN_: masonxdJoy
cod4_lightning: would you do hackthebox today? it was awesome last time!!
Deno_____: george please add this to your reading list kalam cosmological arguments by mohammed hijab
great_said: SwiftRage
funwayz: already a sub only chat threat :)
dalvasorsali: morning
InfiniteReddit: George where do you browse papers?
ad5k: Good morning
cutza: sweet
TheSkapegoat: good morning King
dinxpoy: did he upload the coronavirus vaccine on github or not yet? God save us all 🙏
lambdaman0f: hey george. how is backspace.ai going?
maxschneider96: @InfiniteReddit just google the stuff, otherwise u can use scholar as well, or libgen.is for instance
St47ik: Morning Broskies SeemsGood
niceonesonny77: are there any tips you would like to give on who wants to become a computer scientist?
litesam: What is muzero!?
cutza: free books
jaxotp: How are u doing George?
braininavatt: George!
bsx1123: torrents for books
maxschneider96: yeah free books
Sylens__: hello @georgehotz
grekler3: LUL chat stfu
blackskill224: blackskill224 subscribed at Tier 1.
St47ik: Just follow your passion bro 4Head
squiggly_nibba: What are you building?
dinxpoy: how do I code my first hello world program in Python?
dhevinn: Bruh sub tokens kinda expensive
OFFICER_KKONA: @squiggly_nibba cmonBruh
singularitytoatea: Let me try you geo. Whaat keyword do you use ? 😂
St47ik: oh no not the K word
singularitytoatea: 😂
yungtoad1: j
squiggly_nibba: @OFFICER_KKONA is there a problem officer
mistertenko: Kreygasm
St47ik: L-Theanine Kreygasm
dinxpoy: does a good keybοard make a programmer better?
tinkerzwhothe_t: LETS LEARN PYTHON 3!!!
Jehhred: I think people just want the holy bible of projects they need to complete (copy and paste) to get a job. i.e. they want the get rich quick scheme to become a developer.
MrVitoDayz: yo hey @georgehotz :)
Vukasin22: are you more productive when streaming?
OFFICER_KKONA: @squiggly_nibba perhaps greekGordo
TheSkapegoat: @dinxpoy print("hello world") if you are being srs lol
ImJ4Gu4R: ImJ4Gu4R subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! hello
St47ik: HeyGuys
shiz_z: yoyoyo
wajsic: Is that Herman-Miller chair?
Faceless_Bard: unless you are running adds , putting subs only is a good idea, to avoid stupid questions SeemsGood
maxxg: Sayl chair
Deno_____: lol
cod4_lightning: can you show your mac dotfiles?
shissle: it sounds good
St47ik: What's in the fridge LUL
squiggly_nibba: Start handing out bans for dumb questions
iammrrob0t: Is it allowed to ask which mouse he is using?
oreid52: For those who don't know MuZero is an algorithm that when it's combined with monte carlo tree search (MCTS) has state of the art performance on a range of atari games
litesam: What does muzero do!?
mistertenko: Let's take a minute of silence for Kim Jong Un
funwayz: this stream became too popular to be good :)
chillguy269: Does that cup make you a better programmer?
marvluebke: does your hair product make you a better programmer? Kappa
St47ik: Chat stop NotLikeThis
eldac_kno: cause you are an icon
chillguy269: monkaW
jkfsda: most of these cringe messages are probably just kids
oreid52: It's described in DeepMind's paper https://arxiv.org/abs/1911.08265
mugichkablya: I care abut code. Just code damn things
Faceless_Bard: lol good luck with that
Lost_x_Echo: Lemons. Lemons everywhere.
namenamison: Any book programming or cyber security recommendations?
ImJ4Gu4R: chewing ice in the morning? ResidentSleeper
gasman1017: gasman1017 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Pabgp2000: gxpHey
MrVitoDayz: what's the aim of this stream today? Still biopyhton ?;
InfiniteReddit: you did
braininavatt: PogChamp
St47ik: Scam Train PogChamp
cod4_lightning: can you show your mac dotfiles?
Deno_____: george if we are in a simulation who created the people who created the simulation
braininavatt: HYPER TRAINNNNNN
litesam: Monte Carlo Tree Search @oreid52 could you explain about that!?
shiz_z: HYPE
the_benju: Some are trolling u
InfiniteReddit: look up your old internet history username
dalvasorsali: It's as you said, mysql vs postgres or what color should the walls be painted in
niceonesonny77: but you just gotta understand there are lot of people out there who really inspires model and even a role model for some
tangobeer: !uptime
Sylens__: hello
cod4_lightning: can you show your mac dotfiles?
Pabgp2000: just joined, anyone can give a quick summary of whats going on?
eldac_kno: probably there are lot cringe messages by george on anime boards
St47ik: Wise SeemsGood
vloodp: Amen to that
CJslider14: off that real
TheSkapegoat: Hey George, I am a dumb person and can easily tell you the reason why we ask dumb questions is because we think intelligence comes from your personal gear and tastes.
ky0jinjaeger: "there is no such thing as a stupid question, only stupid answers" true or false?
CJslider14: oof*
mistertenko: opinion on latest Tesla software update
chillguy269: Lol
DzyaN_: LUL
shiz_z: lol
marvluebke: even rick might let you down
MJT_au: We just got roll ricked
oreid52: @litesam I'll try and explain as concise as possible. One sec
great_said: you're honest SeemsGood
ky0jinjaeger: LMAO
St47ik: Hippies 4Head
tangobeer: for how long will u be streaming?
cod4_lightning: can you show your mac dotfiles?
markov010: hello !
mlgboy777: how are you geohot?
Deno_____: george I wrote rock paper scissors in python in maybe 2 weeks of coding am I doing well
Jehhred: "People will always let you down, except for Rick Astley" ~ 13:4 Corinthians
tex01: hi
worraaa: monkaS
tangobeer: Could you suggest the best way to get started with data science?
maxschneider96: How´ s the protein folding going?
St47ik: PogChamp
braininavatt: PogChamp
mlgboy777: pog
zennydmt: can u explain how game trees work?
chillguy269: Viewer count is about to drop hard with all these bans coming down
jaxotp: XD
mlgboy777: daym
ImJ4Gu4R: PogChamp PogChamp
braininavatt: SMART AI
Deno_____: HEY THATS illegal
braininavatt: PogChamp
eldac_kno: this is not a stupid question: is this a stupid question?
tex01: ahaha
St47ik: PogChamp PogChamp
BlLL: AI PogChamp
cutza: that AI is insanely powerful
grekler3: WTF PogChamp
zennydmt: whats a game tree
markov010: This is real Deep Learning
ky0jinjaeger: SKYNET
mlgboy777: 2 Weeks of coding lmoa
ZestyZapus: ZestyZapus subscribed with Twitch Prime.
St47ik: Singularity PogChamp
tangobeer: wow
Vukasin22: it's .34 for rock
NixOTrix: wtf was that lmaoooo
gasman1017: Finally sold out and did a web dev bootcamp at 30. Wish I started coding when 20 years ago
pintwenty: Hello
InfiniteReddit: worrying about numbers
zennydmt: have u tried nootropics
namenamison: Can you give some book recommendations on programming or cyber security. Also what questions would you want for us to ask?
CJslider14: butal honesty is efficient period but hardly used in business its lame but refreshing here
LaheyFPS: george doesnt give fucks
catacata92: do this on your chess game ?
marvluebke: I'm very mediocre
jaxotp: I love your attitude.
Mint2bSpiced: Maybe use Nightbot to write answers to commonly asked questions, or FAQ ?
eldac_kno: is this chat a democracy?
braininavatt: AGI ACHIEVED PogChamp
Andremm2: thoughts on quantum computing?
markov010: How can we buy this Rock Paper Scissor software ?
Faceless_Bard: let me duckduckgo it and return with an answer
Deno_____: george real quetion what do you think does god exist
InfiniteReddit: you call the cyber police
St47ik: 300 viewers = more moneyz LUL
anthonykwan: Some ppl are seeking someone to guide, they don't even try to think more, I guess ?!
zennydmt: what do you think about Google Chronicle?
chillguy269: I would but I am afraid I'm going to get banned
NixOTrix: cyber bullying
great_said: this is first time I've been at your stream, and I'm super happy DendiFace
hookedoninfinity: cyber security is hacking for script kiddies
braininavatt: ask him what he thinks about anarchism Kappa
newlifestartsnow: @gasman1017 sold out wahat
MrMemetic: u use cyber- before everything
1ntegral_: best books on MACHINE LEARNING ? @georgehotz
技術宅: could make a pseudorandom script to determine if questionable messages get banned
eldac_kno: america is a police state lol
CompestLive: hey
litesam: Scientology!?
mistertenko: Your cult!
St47ik: Chat NotLikeThis
shiz_z: It's like when you in security but it's cyber basically a brainless job
newlifestartsnow: cyber sports Kappa
juviin: cybersecurity sells better to ppl who have no idea what programming is
calebsuhy: buzzword for “ethical hacking”
InfiniteReddit: cybertruck?
fadihirmiz: bro they are leeching your time...
Avelansh: cyber bully?
MJT_au: cyber-netics?
liqo13: cybernetics was preety cool
gasman1017: @newlifestartsnow to the bootcamps
bloopsterr: cybermen
Deno_____: @georgehotz thoughts on mainstream religion?
singularitytoatea: Wow chill
catacata92: cybertron it is angry
singularitytoatea: Chill
1ntegral_: best books on MACHINE LEARNING ? @georgehotz
eldac_kno: i dunno dude, sony ericsson cybershot was good
zennydmt: im surprised you dont build trading systems
78DHF: have you ever explored cyberspace before?
St47ik: Cyberpunk Kappa
singularitytoatea: My name is cybernoa
cod4_lightning: "Don't be inspired by people be inspired by ideas" That's islamic!
MrMemetic: cyber-chill
技術宅: Bible
markov010: Your rock paper scissor soft has just been nominated for Turing Awards
caslecasle: This reminds me of the good old Twitch Slam rants.
shiz_z: cyberjunk
MJT_au: cyberlink power dvd
generated_human: Cyber memes
zennydmt: do you have interest in building trading systems
marvluebke: put those rules below your stream
abhi1o1: ahh nothing like streaming a video at 50kb/s
ImJ4Gu4R: George watcha ur doing?
0xC3301: 0xC3301 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 4 in the channel!
yungtoad1: ☠️
0xC3301: 0xC3301 gifted a Tier 1 sub to marvluebke!
clicclic_boom: When are you starting your cult?
0xC3301: 0xC3301 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
0xC3301: 0xC3301 gifted a Tier 1 sub to maxxg!
St47ik: PogChamp
gasman1017: hey guys, how hard is python to pick up with solid foundations in JS/TS?
tangobeer: wow
Deno_____: @georgehotz do objective morals exist if theres no god?
marvluebke: @0xC3301 <3
LaheyFPS: Hype train PogChamp
braininavatt: PogChamp live edition of Channel Description
marvluebke: yay
anthonykwan: Ray !
MrMemetic: @clicclic_boom did you mean cyber-cult?
ianhilt: how much code can you get the bot to write for you
ky0jinjaeger: LUL
great_said: pytorch or tensorflow?
St47ik: Doing it live PogChamp
xloveyourmama: xloveyourmama subscribed at Tier 1.
braininavatt: this is part of history chat Kappa
litesam: Hey George, could you do from transistor to browser
marvluebke: perfect
cutza: lol
his_futon: lol
snowbola: why would you even bother doing anything with your time when you could not do it?
matikitli: Yo man! Know you have not been long in Google, but any things you can just say to someone who wants to work there, besides of: yeww need to doo codfin well. < this is not a stupid question, no ban for me >
St47ik: PogChamp PowerUpR
eldac_kno: what are your thoughts on thoughts?
Scylet: !uptime
gasman1017: how many WPM can you type @georgehotz
braininavatt: brb will implement MuZero in Rust Kappa
oreid52: MCTS is basically a tree search algorithm that is used to figure out the moves (or the path down the tree) that the policy tells you to do to reach the best final state. You can think of it as a way to learn the rules of the game by projecting out the paths (moves) from the current state and choosing the best path
Faceless_Bard: @georgehotz put an example i.e
ck1956: hypetrain buoy
1ntegral_: Is this a stupid question ? @georgehotz LIUL
ImJ4Gu4R: lewl
1ntegral_: LUL
cod4_lightning: "Don't be inspired by people be inspired by ideas" That's islamic!
maxschneider96: banning people with stupid questions, nice project idea btw
4zimut: someone make a faq
rudolphdoesgames: wait a second was that a carlsagan42 stream there?
Deno_____: @georgehotz do objective morals exist without god?
namenamison: Isn't asking dumb questions the way to learn what questions are dumb and what smart?
St47ik: Level 3 PogChamp
singularitytoatea: When you speak slower than you code
newlifestartsnow: @gasman1017 started at 30 y.o.? are you employed?
NixOTrix: SirSword
oreid52: That's a gross oversimplification but I hope it gives an idea lol
niceonesonny77: @namenamison such a solid point fr
NixOTrix: SSSsss
Deno_____: @georgehotz do objective morals exist without god?
eldac_kno: define stupid questions
eldac_kno: yes
cleofn: FeelsBadMan
brofessorbob: Would have thought hotzbro would be on linux.
cleofn: FeelsBadMan monkaS
gasman1017: @newlifestartsnow just doing some contract stuff on the side. This pandemic isn't doing me any good with job searching
eldac_kno: maths can't be done without definitions
airinspiration_: !uptime
brofessorbob: Any l33t hackers in chat?
ak0ya_: Morning chat and George
bluechains: mac or windows and why
braininavatt: !todaysgoal
St47ik: morning
namenamison: Also people teach me the smart questions so i don't get cyber bullied
ck1956: arxiv beauty
NixOTrix: bruh I'm so tired of these try hard linux kids, soz I'm not running a bleeding edge test bench. acknowledge that theres a different tool for different jobs and move tf on
newlifestartsnow: why he use jupyter
ck1956: youre echoeing
InfiniteReddit: (mega brain question) it's getting late, and I need to know is it worth staying up for?
Deno_____: @georgehotz kim jong un died
Deno_____: HE DEAD
eldac_kno: ok?
borang: good morning
ck1956: problem with sound
St47ik: @InfiniteReddit you can always watch the VoD
bloopsterr: why are you up so early? i thought you were a hacker
rudolphdoesgames: @ck1956 nope
TheKoreanZombi: @ck1956 No problem with sound
brofessorbob: Real hackers wakeup early
InfiniteReddit: @st47ik true, imma sleep then
eldac_kno: george isnt reading chat now, but he is qt
St47ik: Kappa
Deno_____: qt like my athletes foot
namenamison: btw i am miles away from understanding what he is doing, can somwbody give me a short explanation?
eldac_kno: trying to implement muzero by himself
blackskill224: fap
niceonesonny77: hi
great_said: muzero?
St47ik: @namenamison A.I super intelligence singularity implementation
brofessorbob: Trying to balance a cart pole bro
MrVitoDayz: I will try this too
maxschneider96: When will AI brothels come?
dalvasorsali: what happened to v1 and v2?
Deno_____: @georgehotz DO objective morals exist without god
eldac_kno: just another ai crutch
eldac_kno: yes they do exist, stop asking this question
hookedoninfinity: anything on github?
Deno_____: prove it
dinxpoy: @deno bro stfu already
oreid52: @namenamison MuZero is DeepMind's state of the art algorithm for creating models that play games like Go, Chess, Atari at a superhuman level
great_said: i just miss coronavirus stream NotLikeThis
brofessorbob: Who thinks the VC money in AI bubble is going to pop this reciession?
Deno_____: george can you hack my cousins instagram i think shes cheating on me
MrVitoDayz: @brofessorbob poop is the right word
Deno_____: girlfriends*
lenindeluna: i just miss coronavirus stream x2
namenamison: Thank you
Killon1: @Deno_____ so funny
eldac_kno: axioms dont need proofs, i declare objective morals are axioms, therefore no proof need, now stfu
Deno_____: @georgehotz so murder is alright?
blackskill224: Im writing a shell script that makes moaning sounds when i touch lenovo clitoris button
brofessorbob: @MrVitoDayz AI == poop?
eldac_kno: ban deno plz he is asking stupid questions
minecald: Would it be possible to break out of a simulation during/after a big freeze universe?
fkingplay3r: yow hes been streaming for how long
snowbola: @georgehotz why would you bother doing anything when you could just not do it?
TheKoreanZombi: Let's go subscribers only chat. Much less dumb.
Deno_____: koreanzombie ure not koreanzombie
eldac_kno: imaging ask on twitch about objective morals
niceonesonny77: 한국인 ㅅ?
RexSonix: when we hacking nsa
Harm133: What are you using Muzero for ? What will it learn
Shelledlizard4: hey
tangobeer: wow
tangobeer: do u live alone
Deno_____: I mean those are very important questions
newlifestartsnow: how to be focused like this guy
maxschneider96: finally
Jehhred: Can confirm, lost IQ points reading
rudolphdoesgames: :(
blackskill224: Failfish
TasosTheLord: ResidentSleeper
Jehhred: Where are the mods?
eldac_kno: mods are asleep
gigafact: wow still going?
blackskill224: hey non subs. do you have any tips on how to construct dumb questions?
eldac_kno: by constructing non smart question, duh
TasosTheLord: Subs = dumbs with money 4Head
MrVitoDayz: MrVitoDayz subscribed at Tier 1.
ak0ya_: chat does not look much better
eldac_kno: subs=perfect people
MrVitoDayz: @georgehotz have you tried using alphago from deepmind yet?
x_algorithm: x_algorithm subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 5 months!
maxschneider96: Have u worked with Neural ODEs yet?
Joooooooooonas: thank god that you are streaming again
blackskill224: I swear im becoming more and more autistic bcoz of this isolation.
MrVitoDayz: alphafold* not alphago
gasman1017: Me neither
gigafact: This is going to be very hard to upload to youtube. Syncing chat is going to be a pain...
eldac_kno: ordinary differential equations is just to put a lot of lambdas in solution
ak0ya_: the folding is not discussed anymore
eldac_kno: you are welcome
joseanavarrom: When are you moving out?
0xC3301: I think we will switch to streamer-only chat soon...
gigafact: nice flyer
MrVitoDayz: what is the protest about ?
eldac_kno: looks like scam tbh
blackskill224: oh my god... i mean im from croatia we are not so smart... but still the shit i see overseas...
MrVitoDayz: oh
lotuseatersec: lotuseatersec subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Jehhred: She seems hot
St47ik: I hope people will be wearing masks at least NotLikeThis
ak0ya_: I don't
gigafact: it does not look like you are going
ImJ4Gu4R: and keep the social distance
joseanavarrom: Don’t get yourself arrested
blackskill224: id like a corona and chill with her
Mint2bSpiced: A differential equation is an equation which contains one or more terms which involve the derivatives of one variable (i.e., dependent variable) with respect to the other variable (i.e., independent variable) dy/dx = f(x) Here “x” is an independent variable and “y” is a dependent variable. For example, dy/dx = 5x.
MrVitoDayz: I would not be surprised if tehre will be buckets of bleach brought to it :D
funwayz: cool people are already in jail :)
0xC3301: I’ll bring tidepods and disinfectant. And you we see any Virus we can still blow it away.
anthonykwan: anthonykwan subscribed at Tier 1.
anthonykwan: Yeah ! subscribed !
ak0ya_: :(
rudolphdoesgames: 104 people participating on facebook
eldac_kno: dude everybody knows what ode is, no need to copypaste definitions from wikipedia
blackskill224: I honestly think this virus is just a Social and Economic reset for world society
MrVitoDayz: @georgehotz do you support the opening of the state then?
gigafact: if you see anything funny just run run and run
MrVitoDayz: I agree.
Jehhred: Will you bring a sign though?
eldac_kno: just go to the concert then
0xC3301: Protest Driven Development!
clicclic_boom: It’s not fake news man 😂 some people seem to have a better response to the virus than others
eldac_kno: dogs are gross, they eat their own poop
maxschneider96: release pharmabro
LaheyFPS: bring a joker mask 🤡
blackskill224: McAfee is saying its fake ahahah
gigafact: can you give us house tour before moving out?
MrVitoDayz: @georgehotz but it's more about healthcare systems not being equipped to cope with it
MrVitoDayz: I do work in it, so it;s a ltitle bit overkill.
Deno_____: why does my pee pee come out yellow
eldac_kno: guys is jupyter better than pycharm
blackskill224: Deno... please go do something usefull. dont waste network bandwith on stupid messages. Go learn databstructures or something
MrVitoDayz: for example, Sweden is coping fine without a lockdown, mainly bc their hc system is much more prepared.
whichtom: they are very different things, jupyter is good to prototype quickly and display plots easily
MrVitoDayz: @eldac_kno I just use jupyter in VS code :)
gigafact: so where are we? how many % before this is up and running?
ak0ya_: These are the nodes of the search tree?
MrVitoDayz: not not just US, but UK's as well.
Kiskiss: iguana1Homie
ivylions: drink bleach
ak0ya_: :)
whichtom: the UK system aint so bad
Deno_____: I will be a good boy from now on
技術宅: lol
Mrkz_: SeemsGood Hello there :)
l1ght5p33d: yyyyeeaaaa IIMM INNNN woot
St47ik: Mods PowerUpR
great_said: hi again :)
sakshambhutani2001: hi my first time here
clicclic_boom: Build a wall 😋
TheKoreanZombi: I will be a ruthlessly efficient mod @georgehotz
prvk3: did he sleep?
JackiePuppet: Italy has a much older population, there are more factors to consider
adotout1: here come the shitposts
l1ght5p33d: Solving Differential Equations now is like Chemistry was 100 Years ago Super Fucking Impossible
TVTuzz: G'day Mr. cr00se
knilecrack: :D
blackskill224: here come detergent eating followers
Deno_____: hey thats illegal
williami000: Has he been streaming all night
ohG_Rivenroth: the population's education plays a big role too, no one talks about south korea, where the population is already educated to use masks even if they have a minor cold
l1ght5p33d: who uses mathematica?
Denis0109: don't be rude jessefive, you will learn something from him, instead saying bullshit.
maxschneider96: The US healthcare system is not performing well given that they spend more than 15% of their GDP on it, it´ s a lot compared to other countries.
ortunado: When is the day you get instagram verified, and make millions? FeelsBadMan
hurzg: whats the purpose of todays stream? yesterday the balancing problem was solved... todays agenda?
markov010: @l1ght5p33d mathematicians
jagger_rsw: Can you boost up your mic, you're like 3 times more silent (on - dBm level) than aaanything else :)
niceonesonny77: what is he working on right now? Was Muzero like alpha zero?
hurzg: thanks @georgehotz
nejintejag: I don't think Sweden was so much better prepared. Sweden is a very individualistic society people are very isolated to begin with. Not that that is the main reason why Sweden is doing ok. I think the main reason is just how media portrays the hole thing.
rudolphdoesgames: @jagger_rsw or you could turn your volume op
rudolphdoesgames: up*
niceonesonny77: can anyone be kind enough to explain what he is doing??
ironickilla: u got a nice little apartment there
ironickilla: looks clean
JackiePuppet: Swedish people stay 2m away from each other even before the virus
markov010: Sounds like you forgot a coin on a pants
knitler_: I'm confused how you'd stop an inf recursion when doing tree search's on value itself
jagger_rsw: @rudolphdoesgames than "aaanything else" will be 3x too loud :)
deepfrieddeals: What’s that noise? Is George laundering his jeans?
l1ght5p33d: Anyone done Generalized Fourier Series for solving for DEs? That's about where I failed out of college
MrVitoDayz: basically, from my personal experience: governments do not put enough resources into healthcare. It's like throttling a CPU without a fan.
blackskill224: George what do you think of an GPU based SQL dialect? I wonder why is there no Database B trees running on parralell
Foxboron: @nejintejag Sweden is not doing OK. Look at Norway. Sweden also doesn't have the economy to do a complete lockdown.
rudolphdoesgames: @jagger_rsw for example, desktop audio down, twitch up, gotta play with those values and find the right balance
johngeorgesample: johngeorgesample subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
ohG_Rivenroth: @georgehotz any plans on making a online course or something like that?
huntboom: huntboom subscribed at Tier 1.
Deno_____: my girlfriend lives in sweden we have been in a long distance relationship for 10 years now although her camera is not working but I have seen her pictures
jagger_rsw: @rudolphdoesgames e.. nah.. better I complain to george :)
sakshambhutani2001: george have you tried R? Some says it's better than py, I personally find it not too good. Ps it works on jupyter
kristobalxx: @Deno_____ LUL
gigafact: @deepfrieddeals it's a laundry machine...
great_said: guys help me, pytorch or tensorflow?
Deno_____: because youre altruistic
adotout1: Not giving a shit 101
Deno_____: GEORGE
LaramsZ: do you do this everyday?
l1ght5p33d: Because everyone would buy it!!!
Joooooooooonas: money :D
jaxotp: Money ;)
gigafact: online course it's for grabbing money I think
MrVitoDayz: Sell it!
ohG_Rivenroth: teach us how to think PogChamp
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz so, the benefits for subscribers are as always? we'll get preferential treatment when you take over the world?
l1ght5p33d: just bullshit the entire time like everyone else!
namenamison: Make a course on how to think then?
JaeGeeTee: JaeGeeTee subscribed with Twitch Prime.
ironickilla: Think people, Think
pepelaugh0: @georgehotz do you watch tv at all?
cazklol: have not learned a shit since watching this channel
maxschneider96: Austria and Germany had good strategies, the death rates are really low and in austria they reopen shops again every 2 weeks. They will even allow tourism in summer probably.
whichtom: buy more ice
eldac_kno: online course on rapping
markov010: sounds like you forgot multiples coins on your pants
Mobius5: MONEY IS A SOCIAL CONSTRUCT
AYNSTAYN: @georgehotz you and me both buddy, only if ppl started to think
grenaderaven: buy stuff
JackiePuppet: Think about what?
l1ght5p33d: Start new bio lab
nlulic: I'd buy a rapping course
MatiGoG: have you heard of rtx voice it could help with situation oever here :)
JaeGeeTee: GEORGE! Just subscribed. Much love bro! Keep it up!
tkdboy555: IMMORTALITY IS THE GOAL
ironickilla: u got a nice little apartment there
LolTwitchSecurity: rapping master class
LaramsZ: @georgehotz do you do this everyday??
jagger_rsw: sink people, sink
huntboom: Buy made up things
tessier_ashp00l: only rich people can afford to say that
bovine_shield: Money is worth something in strip clubs
maxschneider96: money is a tool
blackskill224: bitches and coke and go mcAffee mode on twitter
niceonesonny77: u could legit do anything with money
gigafact: I only watch for your social views....
TheKoreanZombi: You'd buy Mac Pro wheels.
kristobalxx: jet ski
PlayersTwitch: feed the poor
KyoshiDeath: jetskiii
Jehhred: Why make a course when he's making a university.
LolTwitchSecurity: Buy an ex soviet mig 21 @georgehotz
TGUK9: jetski Kappa
tkdboy555: EXCEPT LIVE FOREVER
Deno_____: you could buy me babe
niceonesonny77: evaluate what do you specifically mean by think?
Joooooooooonas: a house , a apartment , decent workstation
MrVitoDayz: @georgehotz
tessier_ashp00l: buy a jet ski
kristobalxx: LUL
markov010: More Money = More GPUs
maxschneider96: rich dad, poor dad, great book
ohG_Rivenroth: more like a mil, not 100k LUL
hurzg: be the next elon musk
Deno_____: charity?
FusRoDead: Wouldn't a course get more people to think?
nejintejag: @Foxboron I think Sweden is dong fine and doing a full lockdown is completely unnecessary. The mortality of covid is so much lower than the original estimates. Covid is just not that dangerous.
yungtoad1: only people with lots of money say stuff like this
bambiofthewoodtribe: Jet skis
eldac_kno: money can solve any problem money can solve
jagger_rsw: unless musk gets into jet ski business and it'll become cool
JaeGeeTee: you don't need a lot of money. you need enough money for food, a house, and thots!!!!!!!!!
ggtom: dont be poor 4Head
MrVitoDayz: Invest that 100k, make 1 tril then your voice will be heard and you can teach people to think :D
Deno_____: THANKS IM POOR NO MORE
jwlolol: problems money cant solve are the real problems tho
St47ik: A course about thinking 4Head
JackiePuppet: I told my landlord money was made up and now I'm homeless
aminuuux: poeple that buy course don't think
l1ght5p33d: Let's sue somebody that would be fun... better than protesting
huntboom: Pay people to color HahaThink
Joooooooooonas: do you have your own house/apartment ?
bovine_shield: Its about making enough, but not an excessive amount.
sakshambhutani2001: what bout Yatch, perhaps Private Jet?
gigafact: you can live off twitch if you like
LaramsZ: you can have economic stability and dont worry about it at all, being too rich doesn't give u that much
Foxboron: @nejintejag You are wrong. We know very little of how COVID affects us.
tinkerzwhothe_t: what's the purpose of living?
Deno_____: MODERATE
kristobalxx: not a jet ski
Deno_____: define moderate
alameda13: u want little
maxschneider96: everything u need to know about money and happiness: https://80000hours.org/articles/money-and-happiness/
JaeGeeTee: Money can either attract the thots or keep them away!
Denis0109: But some people will never think, also if they try george. Sometimes it's better to not know, that people aren't THINKING.
clicclic_boom: @georgehotz what about the cult?
grenaderaven: buying lots of cheap crap is pointless, bt there are nice things that can improve ur life
TheKoreanZombi: @Deno_____ He defined moderate as $78k.
colanzio5: @georgehotz It's easy to think, it's harder to finish something to completion than come up with a good idea.
blackskill224: smoke weed with elon in escape velocity
Deno_____: ohh ok
Jehhred: Why get rich when you can be friends with rich people. You get all the benefits without the hassle
raystriker98: in California 78k is moderate
hurzg: the more you have, the more you fear loosing it all... thats the problem
tkdboy555: @georgehotz have you been to Stephen Wolfram's livestream at all these past few weeks? He launched this new open-source project https://www.wolframphysics.org/ for everyone to work on trying to discover the fundemental theory of everything, the grand unified theory of physics
eldac_kno: you wouldnt need excuse to suprass your true desires by pretending "i can buy whatever i want"
MrVitoDayz: well, we currently do not have an economic equivalent to money.
nejintejag: @Foxboron the numbers I have seen puts the mortality across the society is about 0.15 %.
l1ght5p33d: all hail elon.. stress king
LaheyFPS: elon doesnt feel stress
Deno_____: you make at least 130
grenaderaven: money buys power
YOLOMAN1343: when is the next geohot live concert where can i buy the tickets
Mobius5: If money is your core drive in life it's over for you
namenamison: What part of streaming gives pleasure, bc it seems like most of us only annoy you?
alameda13: but u could others with more money @georgehotz
Foxboron: @nejintejag And that is "not that dangerous" in your mind? The current deaths in sweden i 4 times that of last flue season.
技術宅: if you can eat you're good
lebop: iBUYPOWER
St47ik: https://www.wolframphysics.org/ seems interesting
Deno_____: you could buy a private island and host mma events
MrVitoDayz: @Mobius5 for some people it is tho.
技術宅: and medical
clicclic_boom: Are you still paid at comma?
whichtom: thats kinda a weird generalization for the entire country
FargioFarmani: If you feel stressed, can I give you a massage? @georgehotz
warriorgiggles: What part of streaming gives pleasure, bc it seems like most of us only annoy you?
sakshambhutani2001: money CAN give you more Credibility/ Social Influence.
namenamison: What part of streaming gives pleasure, bc it seems like most of us only annoy you?
Jehhred: Keeping in mind he earns 78K working part-time
JackiePuppet: That graph shows the average case, no guarentee that even slightly represents one's own case
alameda13: earn more help more
eldac_kno: i think notch situation seems perfect
Joooooooooonas: more money is a preparation for well being I think
d3adb33: but its Up to the country you live. ...
joseanavarrom: But for some people it’s not enough money for “what they want to buy”
this_is_falcon: part time 78k?
knilecrack: it just means you can't talk shit on twitter etc
grenaderaven: not having a boss is prolly more important to me than money
Mobius5: @MrVitoDayz I find it unbelievable how those people can get fullfilment in life. If you can already buy everything, why would you want more?
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz I'm not sure, if I earned 80k$ I'd be a bit worried about taking mortgage for a house in BayArea or in Switzerland where I now live.
yungtoad1: you're already a thought leaders. just read the dumb questions people ask
tkdboy555: check out https://www.wolframphysics.org/
great_said: do you thinj python still worth to learn?
sakshambhutani2001: I everything elon is, is because of his social influence
Shelledlizard4: id rather have time than money tbh
whichtom: mortgages are a scam
rudolphdoesgames: @great_said learning is always good so yeah! go for it
blackskill224: but guys... that is just a number... like who the fuck cares... tbh if I get respect for contributing to something cool and can eat food and sleep under the roof.
bovine_shield: LOL
gingersniffer: i make £23k and im perfectly happy, maybe im not intelligent enough to understand how i could be happier, but i think that mo' money = mo' problems is true
ggtom: michigan kek
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz that's why I live in switzerland :)
funwayz: no thanks
Denis0109: I wanna learn how to be smart: George: THINK, JUST START TO THINK!
Deno_____: depends on where you live
takkat14: what do you think about WANN?
grizvok: @gingersniffer no it isn;t
St47ik: @georgehotz lockdown made chat a bit worse?
tkdboy555: @georgehotz have you seen this? https://www.wolframphysics.org/
MDIronsTwitch: Ouch, Boston is up there too :(
d3adb33: i am Happy to be in EU 😎
whichtom: 23k is like starting salary out of undergrad in UK
this_is_falcon: but the ocean is cool
Joooooooooonas: BUT if you have enough money, it doesnt matter if the ratio is bad
blackskill224: but if you wanna do coke and bang thots. you need more
LaramsZ: Do you do this everyday duuud
SlaterUSA: has our man cured covid yet
MrVitoDayz: @whichtom lol, for phd stipen you get like 15k so... :D
phrixus_bro: stephen wolfram has done it again
joseanavarrom: In the EU is lower
Deno_____: @blackskill224 hey this isnt sillicone valley
jagger_rsw: @eldac_kno for housing not thaaat true, in comparison to BA. Say 1000sq ft house is maybe 800k USD in Zurich, which is probably less than in BA
knitler_: Is there a way to remove the reward completely for chess since it's not really needed?
whichtom: @MrVitoDayz in the UK?
whichtom: I knew they were low but not that low
FargioFarmani: btw your talk about hacking the world simulation was cool, i wonder how many ppl in the audience got the idea soulshined
whichtom: as usual, salary is a joke in the UK lol
MrVitoDayz: @whichtom Yup.
sakshambhutani2001: everything Elon is, is because of social influence
pepelaugh0: @georgehotz would you ever go on a podcast like eric weinsteins or lex fridmans if they asked?
joseanavarrom: It’s even lower in most of europe
l1ght5p33d: Eric Weinstein knows the next steps of testing string theory
grenaderaven: its not low in London
ak0ya_: string theory is math
joseanavarrom: It’s about welfare state
ak0ya_: not physics
LaramsZ: do you do this everyday
great_said: you deserve more thank Elon Musk for me
bambiofthewoodtribe: Buy houses in Nevada
MrVitoDayz: you do what you love but you struggle af. I don't care that much tho.
maxschneider96: @grenaderaven depends
tkdboy555: thanks for checking it out :)
maxschneider96: @grenaderaven ain´ t that high in many fields as well
blackskill224: id like George on joe rogan... but i bet people said this a milion times
namenamison: @georgehotz If you are not that interested in money, why are your videos subs only?
aiex42: Wolfram project is NOT string theory
yungtoad1: PunchTrees
Deno_____: joe rogan only accepts atheists on his show
tkdboy555: @aiex42 true LP
grenaderaven: if ur earning low in london its prolly your own fault, theres devs with 1-2 years experience earning 60k
tkdboy555: @aiex42 :P *
grizvok: @namenamison literally all of this gets posted to the commaai youtube rofl
rudolphdoesgames: @aiex42 he didnt say it was?
huntboom: What’s your favorite linux distro and why?
jaxotp: Would you like to go to JRE? Sorry if this gets asked a lot, I'm quite new here.
whichtom: SE in london can get you a lot yea, I have a mate getting 100k freelancing
JaeGeeTee: HAPPY SUNDAY! WOOOOOO :rickflair:
WillGreen98: @grenaderaven hopefully so haha
whichtom: but for engineering as a whole, its really low
Deno_____: joe rogan is braindead
ggtom: joe 🅱️ ogan
maxschneider96: @grenaderaven ain ´t that much compared to other countries
aaddrr: london life is expensive af
nejintejag: @Foxboron so normally 250 people die each day in Sweden. Currently about 48 people die in covid every day in Sweden the overlap with those 250 is high. The people who die are mostly old and unfit people that would die from other causes son enough. For amount of work we put in to this covid shit we could save millions and millions of poor African people.
whichtom: im aerospace and my mates are getting like <25k starting salary and its depressing
blackskill224: no man he is not. he eat yelk and jalapenos. and smokes weed. that means he is smart
grizvok: you talking shit about rogan
ggtom: whichtom where?
whichtom: even then you cant get huge raises unless you go into management
great_said: i hate this virus, so depressing NotLikeThis
namenamison: @grizvok shit my bad dude, still weird that they are not free here but yeah mb
Deno_____: does dmt and thinks he knows how the universe is created
JaeGeeTee: @nejintejag, everyone is dead in sweden.. they sold their soul to the govn't
l1ght5p33d: @eldac_kno Why do you say he's a fraud? He at least knows almost what he's talking about enough to deceive very well then.. very sad if true
whichtom: @ggtom south of london
whichtom: not central, near greater
namenamison: But it is not one life
ggtom: whichtom in aerospace engineering? brutal ngl tbh but makes sense
sAfEgUy1: we could of done that before the virus though
maxschneider96: @whichtom I´ m living in north london, tottenham
paranon1: Have you read Marc Andreessen's "IT'S TIME TO BUILD" essay?
qcDENNEMANN: How hot is karen?
St47ik: @georgehotz to be fair this crisis revealed how broken the current global system is imo
Deno_____: theres people dying from fake boobs
AugTV: a thing we will look back on in the future, how the fuck did they have people starving and being homeless when they clearly had enough.
mibressler: When are you gonna go on Lex Friedman's Discord?
ggtom: man ppl need to make tl dr
whichtom: yea idk aerospace engineering in the UK makes me sad. trying to get to the US
LelouchViMoscow: Hey chat. Just broke up with my gf and come here :P
easysleeep: How about Daniel Gross’s piece on World 2.0?
blackskill224: @lelouchvimoscow nice. now go and jailbreak some phones
whichtom: we're still in the pandemic so we're operating on so much incomplete information
clicclic_boom: Food shortage is not really killing anyone these days. It’s mostly disease and war.
gasman1017: @LelouchViMoscow Sorry to hear that. Did you break up with her? That's at least a little better
ggtom: whichtom wat about mainland europe like germany? u can always do petro engineering
ak0ya_: @LelouchViMoscow thank you for letting us know
whichtom: @ggtom I aint selling my soul
Deno_____: bill gates is our lord savior Kappa
jagger_rsw: probably true in conflict regions, south sudan, somalia
ggtom: whichtom ???
whichtom: aerospace industry in the US is the best anyways
l1ght5p33d: If you live in the middle of nowhere you can obviously die pretty easily
St47ik: Whats that noise WutFace
clicclic_boom: Yup
LelouchViMoscow: @gasman1017 now, she said something like 'its hard to work etc, she just wanna find someone who had money'. kinda 5 years goes to trash
Deno_____: bill gates making vaccines and his children arent vaccinated
kingvoneduard: Young people are dumb and leftists
tribegvng: Everything a scam
mibressler: ggtom germany just has next to accurate numbers by good testing
tearisten68: I don't hear people complaining about starving yet, I hear about people complaining about their hair cuts
ggtom: petro eng is legit especially the drilling part
LelouchViMoscow: @gasman1017 i mean "no", not now
LelouchViMoscow: ahahha
sakshambhutani2001: Covid death is not only matter of age, it can be a matter of time you are exposed to it. Many young Doctors and Nurses are dying of Covid
St47ik: @Deno_____ pls stop
MrVitoDayz: I personally see the hospitals inside ( I work on there) so you can't suddenly increase the hospital's capacity by 10 fold... It takes at least some time and most importantly, you need the professionals working there. How will you get 10x support staff than what you normally need? So basically, overstreched hospital = declining healthcare.
this_is_falcon: its just circle of life
Deno_____: @st47ik whats wrong?
MrVitoDayz: And then what you get is that it's impossibelto get healthcare support for simple things like infection. So people start to die from stupid things.
aaddrr: trueee
ggtom: mibressler i was talking about aerospace eng jobs in germany lul
gasman1017: @LelouchViMoscow You will be ok. It sucks at first, but it get's better everyday. Just find stuff to do to keep yourself occupied. You deserve better my friend <3 <3 <3
whichtom: the idea of a mortgage is a scam anyway that drives up prices and screws over the next batch of people buying
mibressler: LoL haha
kingvoneduard: Harvard is a scam to make billions
MrVitoDayz: that is true.
mibressler: harvardx is nice though
MrVitoDayz: They are not scam, but are stuck in the past like most universities.
clicclic_boom: Mostly PPE and testing kits are widely available - not a technology problem. But govt gives licenses to sell these - there was a shortage of licensed products in the market.
Deno_____: harvard is pro slavery
Choruptian: what are you doing with MuZero?
benzojamal: we need a new democracy
gasman1017: Jim Gates says we aren't going to Mars for at least 100 years
LelouchViMoscow: @gasman1017 ty bro :) so it was really heartache first time)
benzojamal: democracy 2.0
sakshambhutani2001: Covid death is not only matter of age, it can be a matter of time you are exposed to it. Many young fit doctors and nurses are dying of covid
aiex42: You NEED to take a serious look into the Wolfram Physics Project: it's about hacking the Universe (simulation) to find the underlying rule behind it all
l1ght5p33d: Robots only on mars at least 40 years
tessier_ashp00l: how hard is going to mars compared to fixing eaarth?
triple__m: Really sucks how short sighted and biased people are, thinking mars is a destination and not about all the things we'll be inventing by setting the goal
Deno_____: yeah but george who created the people that created the matrix whos at the end of the creation chain
whichtom: musk is doing a good job of getting people excited/optimistic
kingvoneduard: You cannot hack a Simulation if you are inside.
ariasteve: Cheers from Canada 🇨🇦 Just found out about these streams, they’re awesome man
tribegvng: :D
lebop: what are your thoughts on VCs in silicon valley?
ak0ya_: This brings us back to protein folding?
l1ght5p33d: Brain is so sub optimal,, 99% recursive lock all the time
benzojamal: people should give up the idea of colonizing mars; it's complete waste of resources
gigafact: brains are amazing
Andrewnagyy: What's a terra flop?
whichtom: ya brains are an incredible piece of engineering
gasman1017: Jim Gates is a string theory guy. He says its an economical problem. When we went to the moon it took 10years and 5% of our year GDP. To Mars it's 100x that, so the math says it's not feasible right now
FargioFarmani: Computers are just rocks which we tricked into thinking
whichtom: lmao what
aaddrr: do you think we will ever mike a ezact functional replica of the brain but wihout the drawbacks of being human?
mibressler: hopefully not repetitive: when will you go on Lex Fridman Discord?
clicclic_boom: What do you think about DNA computing?
MurdocLIVE: Anyone see the new Microsoft patent for cryptocurrency microchip with patent number 060606?
MatiGoG: @Andrewnagyy floating point operations per second,
whichtom: going to mars is v different than going to the moon
sakshambhutani2001: what if we don't work toward increasing compute power but to hack brain
aiex42: Bro, you haven't looked into Wolfram Physics Project... it's not what you think it is
kristobalxx: what is the single most important thing that you look for in people when you hire ? especially for swe
Andrewnagyy: @MatiGoG Thanks
whichtom: mars might actually be easier now than going to the moon in the 60s/70s
whichtom: given how much innovation needed to occur then, and how much was unknown
benzojamal: like string theory LUL
gigafact: Elon is going to bring us to Mars
joseanavarrom: What are your thoughts on bill gates’ opinions about the pandemic?
MrVitoDayz: @MurdocLIVE lol thanks for showing.
StapoTV: curing ageing > mars
l1ght5p33d: @MurdocLIVE TIL Microsoft owns the devil's patent
gasman1017: The problem is our rocket technology hasn't evolved that much since the 60/70's. We're still using bell nozzles
Deno_____: george simulation is possibility but just because its possible doesnt mean its the most probable
whichtom: musk might bring us to mars but his biggest impact will be inspiring people after him
whichtom: so if he doesn't, there will be people after him
Deno_____: bill gates sterilizing africans
MurdocLIVE: @MrVitoDayz @l1ght5p33d Crazy right?! I'm not big into religion, but I do remember seeing something about mark of the beast going in your hand or something
aaddrr: bill gates is washed lul
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz One minute explanation of Monte carlo
calcmath: what did I miss, how long has he been streaming?
tessier_ashp00l: whitney weeb thinks otherwise
l1ght5p33d: lock up Microsoft . No more Microsoft for anyone
whichtom: @gasman1017 because they're good. aerospikes are still pretty w/e. the rocket tech isn't even the bottleneck
mibressler: will you go on Lex Fridman's Disc?
l1ght5p33d: port all Microsoft apps to Linux
kingvoneduard: Bill Gates will save us with a chip in our head.
l1ght5p33d: on a usb
Andrewnagyy: Bill Gates is funding as many researches as he can so he can be the first to come up with a vaccine and then patent it
MrVitoDayz: @MurdocLIVE LOL.
FargioFarmani: There is no strive for innovation anymore. The cold war is over.
Avelansh: what do you think of dan carlin's hardcore history podcast?
huntboom: Didn’t Bill Gates eradicate polio in India? He’s done a lot of good
whichtom: SSTOs are still highly unfeasible and will be for a long time. innovations need to occur for the interplanetary spacecraft, not the launch vehicle itself
gindalf: @chat what is he doing?
whichtom: and obv landing/ascent vehicles on the other planet
qcDENNEMANN: So what are we making?
MrVitoDayz: @gindalf figuring out muzero
whichtom: its largely a money problem, but its really a motivation problem
whichtom: I agree we don't need SSTO
LelouchViMoscow: Anyone have some experience in combined text and image analysis? I work at course work, so I have 10000 profiles of users with text and images data from open sources like insta/facebook, and i need to predict does some content would be liked by user
Deno_____: george my dad created the simulation hes letting me play with you guys right now
smokyandthebandito: dudes sleeping on a one inch matress, gonna have back problems in like a year LUL
Deno_____: do you have any questions
ariasteve: Do you recommend any books to get into Machine Learning?
gigafact: George is pioneering Science & Technology on twitch. It's the only stream about Science & Technology on twitch with any real view numbers
ohG_Rivenroth: george, what's your view on god/metaphysics?
braininavatt: monkaS asking about books
xeeton: funny how that "pseudocode" is actual code
Deno_____: @ohg_rivenroth hes a skeptic
eldac_kno: math theories doesnt need testability, but it is still science
huntboom: Does George have a favorite book?
Deno_____: imagine being an atheist yikes
ggtom: imo actual code can be considered pseudocode
Santytopa73: time online ?
3even: !uptime
a_0__0_a: my internet is crappy, so I am seeing Frodo writing code.
mibressler: math is like philosophy since it doesn't need any emprical observation
eldac_kno: you better time out deno__ he is spammingn stupid shit all stream
gigafact: @Santytopa73 about 1 hour
kito__: up time is 1:08
eldac_kno: math is still science though
niceonesonny77: pseudocode is an actual thing, that's one of the first thing we learn when we take Computer Science Principles in high school.
rudolphdoesgames: @eldac_kno agreed
nitropiece: math is not science
eldac_kno: yeah right
mibressler: Math doesn't tell you anything about the world
gindalf: math was invented by "them" to control the masses. look it up guys, open your minds
filip9i: What is he currently doing?
niceonesonny77: what is he currently doing
eldac_kno: math tells almost everything about the world, but not in the way you think
Deno_____: science can tell us how but it cant tell us why
Skurt2k: hi
maxschneider96: Mathematics is not a science from our point of view, in the sense that it is not a natural science. The test of its validity is not experiment - Richard Feynman
mibressler: science may use math to describe/approximate the world
AlphaBetaGamma: !uptime
joseanavarrom: Math is a tool for science
Deno_____: exactly
niceonesonny77: but without math, no science
gindalf: !github
eldac_kno: feynman isn't some godly authority on what is science
gubbdump262: what is George building
nitropiece: science is the observation and recording of repeatable phenomena while math is purely just a language that happens to be used by science
justenpassant: what are we doing today guys, I see Tensorflow
benzojamal: math is the only thing that matters
gasman1017: @whichtom but we can control thrust with other types of nozzle, reducing need for as much fuel.. therefore reducing price/lb to orbit. I'm not a rocket scientist, but makes sense to me
mibressler: without math science would be just less efficient
eldac_kno: math is also observation
calcmath: he is implemeting monte carlo tree search
mibressler: why is math observation?
joseanavarrom: Science is the only thing that matters, and math is a requirement. That’s it, they’re both important
bovine_shield: math is stupid. only painting and poetry matters.
her3hero: yo whaddup
nitropiece: math is not observation
ggtom: looks like he is doing some reinforcement learning thingy magig
eldac_kno: you observe things then use math to describe them
nitropiece: look up definition
justenpassant: math is an observation? lol. It's a modelisation
Mlewii: @eldac_kno so is math science ?
mibressler: eldac exactly, but it is not mathematics itself that your learning about
whichtom: @gasman1017 yeah but convergent-divergent just happen to work really well. If anything we could look into different types of chemical fuel but its a marginal performance increase
luuwa_: i think yes
gasman1017: how important do you guys think advanced math is for everyday programming?
ggtom: gasman1017 not important imo
Deno_____: you dont need math for programming but you need programming for math
ak0ya_: depends what advanced means
whichtom: reusability seems to be good, with high launch cadence. combined with better long-term space propulsion (really need nuclear imo) would be good
eldac_kno: depends on what programming
ggtom: gasman1017 youll rarely need beyond linear algebra
maxschneider96: Why don´ t u guys just google it, clearly gives u an explanation for why math is not a science. Annoying discussion haha
benzojamal: @gasman1017 you don't need it
MurdocLIVE: Anyone know a good private browser? I'm using Brave atm
Deno_____: my dad is an html developer and hes making BANK
justenpassant: lol the amount of atrocities in this chat are out of this world
sakshambhutani2001: goerge do you recommend any books? like best book you have ever read?
FargioFarmani: You need math for math and programming for programming.
tajpouria: We never back to twitchcoq?
naclEric: uh u definitly do not need programming to do math
gubbdump262: Brave sucks
joseanavarrom: Of course you need it, in many other fields of engineering
ak0ya_: :(
rudolphdoesgames: twitch in a nutshell
vrv_exe: Lol
calcmath: i am paying attention to stream,
raystriker98: just ban people lol
huntboom: Yeah we are a shitty discord
rickoftheroot: BibleThump
clicclic_boom: Build the sub wall 😋
joseanavarrom: And what a stupid debate honestly
vrv_exe: Get these savages back in line George!
0xC3301: ...
maxschneider96: @joseanavarrom yeah haha
Choruptian: I'll still pay attention even if sub-only
maxschneider96: u should create an AI to deal with the chat
maxschneider96: fairs
Jehhred: Twitch chat is the mating ground for degenerates
raystriker98: but they're all incels
joseanavarrom: Do you project you’ll get it working today?
anthonykwan: TBH, What r u gonna achieve tonight ? LUL LUL LUL Still cannot get it too well
Deno_____: Just ban people
georgehotz: https://arxiv.org/src/1911.08265v2/anc/pseudocode.py
calcmath: I think backpropagate here is not the neural network backpropagate, that is what has been confusing me
Tornyl: !uptime
anthonykwan: I see...
FargioFarmani: !join
bilboballin: love your streams man
JdPaulBlart: good morning mr streamer
niceonesonny77: what do you think is the best specific major in computer science? machine learning?software engineering? data science?
maxschneider96: @niceonesonny77 depends on what u wanna do, simple as that
Deno_____: @eldac_kno you dont make rules stop spamming
Jehhred: Would people stop asking for life/career advice?!?!
Foxboron: @niceonesonny77 not a lot of difference between machine learning and data science these days.
rudolphdoesgames: @Deno_____ LUL
niceonesonny77: damn
niceonesonny77: spread love not hate man...
kristobalxx: jesus christ is this chat full of jailbreak-era fanboys that have no idea about how anything works and ask random shit
Deno_____: @eldac_kno its really cringe how youre trying to make him like you
thenomadplayer: Yo bro, gr8 from Poland. U are my code inspiration.
Deno_____: I mean I respect it but enough is enough
gindalf: just make an !advice command explaining that he's not here to give advice etc
sokhibjke: !dc
benzojamal: @georgehotz do you believe RL will ever be used for something more useful than games?
sokhibjke: !discord
FargioFarmani: I never witnessed an angry George
Kriminell00: oof
JdPaulBlart: hahahahhahahahahhaa
braininavatt: LUL
bilboballin: lmfao
gindalf: rip
Deno_____: george savage
JustLOL__: LUL rekt
danrod43: LuL
her3hero: lol
l1ght5p33d: @krispeer Why do you care? Look at what geohot has coded before.. he is one of the best programmers alive
niceonesonny77: LMAO
Deno_____: @krispeer heavy
a_0__0_a: what just happened?
NatePh_07: LUL
her3hero: does it balance a stick yet?
Deno_____: @georgehotz how many letters mmax for a message
whichtom: wait when is it backpropagating
tauzN: !uptime
maxschneider96: safe spaces don´ t work anyways
knilecrack: only thing that is bad when it's subscribersa only that there i no G's "you get a time out"
2sin54: monkaS
grosser_schwanneg: PogChamp
kristobalxx: graphs KreyGasm
ggtom: the network backprop is via minimize loss function. the backpropagate is something else here related to the three
FargioFarmani: How to be positive: George, you look handsome today.
majorawpsome: hey don't forget to save
a_0__0_a: Kappa
2sin54: sir there are weird noises in the background
namenamison: Why do you "time out" people?
JdPaulBlart: george take the change out of your jeans before you put them in the dryer... its loud af @georgehotz
DatGuyVJ: !uptime
jenny_tahlia903: hey mate i know this is off topic but have u looked into self driving tractors cause atm on my farm for it is around 30 grand and about 2cm accuracy surely it should be cheaper
lilou04: how is corona hacking going on?
dompatobbe: !uptime
beckles: Is he making a game
calcmath: its networkx
ggtom: jenny_tahlia903 u could always train one yourself 4Head
rudolphdoesgames: @beckles he is implementing Mu>ero
benzojamal: x missing
rudolphdoesgames: MuZero*
raystriker98: is muZero the best unsupervised ai there is?
Deno_____: I read automate the boring stuff, automated my job and got fired
Vietnomnom: this isnt hacking coronavirus LUL
ggtom: i think it's just recent. the 'best' i duno
Basti_Soldier: <3
tribegvng: Been automating mine for the past 3 years yolo
Basti_Soldier: hi
Deno_____: niceeee
braininavatt: PogChamp
LaheyFPS: when you first learn nested loops
l1ght5p33d: nicee
Deno_____: thicc tree
Izimoney92100: this is christmas !!!
braininavatt: we did it! VoHiYo
Deno_____: that was quick
kubectl: heyyo, what is he building?
Deno_____: a tree
calcmath: during MCTS i dont think you should use the value predicted by the neural right?
kubectl: mkey, and the tree is supposed to do what?
Deno_____: be a teee
Deno_____: tree*
calcmath: oh nvm yeah you predict the reward with a neural net
whichtom: muzero achieves SOTA for a lot of atari 2600 games and does pretty decent on go/ms pacman but I think thats it
SrDead: Any tldr of what is he doing? LUL
whichtom: not sure how it compares to SOTA on go
M0NKEYBAGZ: what is MuZero
Izimoney92100: stop breaking it :(
ggtom: looking good there
Deno_____: ( . )Y( . ) this is for you george boy
brisingr1031: @M0NKEYBAGZ a model that deep mind released a paper on recently
FargioFarmani: It performed even better than AlphaZero in go and chess
qdl_: is google really to much for you people?
M0NKEYBAGZ: ahh
calcmath: this is still without UCB exploration
brisingr1031: @qdl_ whats google??
qdl_: idk lol isnt that these android guys?
whichtom: ah I see yea it matches/outperforms alphazero. neat
danrod43: @jomkingal take it easy with the compliments, this is your finla warning
l1ght5p33d: if you try to tune the weight update for only specific inputs .. Is that considered a hidden layer? I don't get the terminology sometimes
danrod43: @jomkingal good, stick to advice questions
brisingr1031: @georgehotz have you tried julia before?
calcmath: so this is brute force search, like a tree traversal
Izimoney92100: are we hearing the dryer in the background?
calcmath: policy should be combination of value and visit counts
brisingr1031: @Izimoney92100 p sure yeah lol
l1ght5p33d: map of state to action
Sycto: lol
ggtom: you get the kicker boiii
ggtom: Deno_____ i remember someone unironically answering this in a twitch chat
sicandis: what is your keyboa... oh wait
joseanavarrom: Why are you saying so many stupid things on the chat?
eldac_kno: deno stfu aready
r3mote: Hello :)
danrod43: @eldac_kno LuL welcome back
FargioFarmani: Says the guy who got timed out
calcmath: policy is not stochastic i think, its just choose action with maximum UCB score
filipiek1997: i know :)
danrod43: he's a junior mod dude, he's working his way up
bill1929: @eldac_kno - pipe down bro you aint an authority figure
moizai: what we doin today?
ggtom: calcmath i think the same bro
Deni1111: What desktop env do you use at work????
eldac_kno: what question about disposing body has anyting to do with this stream
csal90: Lets have some good vibes boys and girls
ggtom: it ok i whispered him the answer
FargioFarmani: Maybe he means how to have your garbage collector dispose your python objects/ bodies
danrod43: eldac ban inc LuL
knilecrack: :D :D
Jazzify101: :D
nizero: George I'm going to help label your comma data
moizai: when are you doing a meme reveiw george
bill1929: :D
Aki_111: can u help me with my homework
braininavatt: braininavatt subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! HeyGuys
calcmath: Also if you read the medium article, it says there are two phases, for first 30 moves its a different policy from after
maxschneider96: what´ are ur timeout policies?
M0NKEYBAGZ: ManChicken
LaheyFPS: HeyGuys
jagger_rsw: I like code which contains engineering tuning factors like "pb_c_base = 331154353453"
Boza7777: yo
acathon: oh man, don't tell me you are still awake until now :o
Joselinis: If you ask what?
LaheyFPS: Just dont say anything off topic LUL
BetaMalePaypig: trolling gets u timed out, i heard
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz what are you building today ?
Izimoney92100: a tree
St47ik: @calcmath why can't policy be stochastic as in stochastic policy gradients?
calcmath: look at fucntion visit_softmax_temperature
csal90: What's the benefit of using Jupyter notebooks?
eldac_kno: fast prototyping
calcmath: it can be stochasitc, its just that after 30 moves the way they implemented it is it just chooses action with maximum visits
l1ght5p33d: @maxschneider96 You must at least attempt to contribute positively to the intellectual quality of the chat
Boza7777: When did the stream start
maxschneider96: @l1ght5p33d makes sense
whichtom: about 2hr ago
kenan7: omg light mode
kenan7: my eyes hurt
l1ght5p33d: @csal90 not needing to type print()
calcmath: shouldnt you softmax with a temperature ?
andRoStyle: hi
cavad444mm: your voice is low @georgehotz
moizai: agree with you kenan 😂
l1ght5p33d: not needing to type esc shft : x uparrow tab enter
gigafact: making some pasta it's going to be nice
ggtom: calcmath i think they got a funky policy for action selection going on. doesnt seem to follow previous known policies. i gotta read the paper at some point. aka in a cpl of years
fychvhvjh: TALK ABOUT WHAT IF SOMEONE HACKED INTO THE PARTICKE ACCELERATOR
vrv_exe: @csal90 think of it as a vm. Environment is self contained. Easy to share with others.
fychvhvjh: PARTICLE
calcmath: @ggtom read the medium article, its explained better in there
Izimoney92100: it's broken :'(
foosballs: test
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz boost your mic plz
braininavatt: we're close :)
ggtom: calcmath i arent read that. maybe when i do rl again in the future.
foosballs: @calcmath link to article?
fychvhvjh: if someone hacked into the particle accelerator it could change the space time continuum
supplydemand88: Sup
calcmath: https://medium.com/applied-data-science/how-to-build-your-own-deepmind-muzero-in-python-part-2-3-f99dad7a7ad
foosballs: thanks
2sin54: HeyGuys ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ You are now permanently banned.
lemonspree: What happened to the covid project?
anthonykwan: LUL
kalbermatteralan: SeemsGood
calcmath: exploring childs is based on UCB score, finally choosing the action for the real environemnt is based on visit counts
l1ght5p33d: @lemonspree We needed a mass spectrometer
maxschneider96: love python, but compared to other languages I find it harder to find bugs, honestly
calcmath: its the select_action function, they use a softmax with a temp
eaterenrgy: @maxschneider96 Use it strongly typed it helps a lot plus of errors are caught compile time.
l1ght5p33d: what's wrong looks good to me
xeeton: how are you finding the optimal hyperparams for muzero?
maxschneider96: @eaterenrgy thanks for the advice
triple__m: are people just trolling in chat? what's going on?
l1ght5p33d: @xeeton fancy maths or a metric ton of trials
calcmath: ucb score for move right is toohigh for some reason
lilou04: maybe thats the right policy
xeeton: @l1ght5p33d I see, thx
Jazzify101: What kind of game is this thing tying to beat?
calcmath: is this cartpole or mountatin thing?
calcmath: game is just balancing the stick
Jazzify101: ok
FargioFarmani: The problem is that there is no continuity on the simplex w.r.t to the nodes.
nejintejag: @calcmath what stick?
gaocaandra: yoo wassup
calcmath: think inverted pendulum on a cart, cart nedds to move to keep it balanced
gaocaandra: 3 streams in 2 days
gaocaandra: blessed be
foosballs: thanks for the medium article - anyone interested on understanding what he is working on - check out the article, its very beginner friendly.
calcmath: he will show the animation of it eventually
l1ght5p33d: @Jazzify101 He already switched out the game a few times. The game doesn't matter if the inputs are the same data type. The algorithm will learn any game environment . Look at open ai gym
gaocaandra: where is the link?
lordmordi_: first time ive ever caught your stream live. might sound weird to say but I've been looking forward to this. lol
Khalifa1897: @foosballs link
xeeton: @gaocaandra https://arxiv.org/pdf/1911.08265.pdf
St47ik: https://medium.com/applied-data-science/how-to-build-your-own-muzero-in-python-f77d5718061a
gaocaandra: thankd @xeeton
foosballs: ^ Start from part 1 tho
gingersniffer: i love these streams george, they inspire me to learn, thanks for sharing
knilecrack: Hey man, can you take a minute and explain what are you doing, I've missed a big part of the stream
Flying_Geese: can anyone tell me what he's making?
calcmath: shouldnt there be softmax with a temperature somewhere? or is this a simplifed version you are trying first?
foosballs: I'm just mindblown with the idea that you can train a network to learn without any rules.. although it does feel kind of intuitive that after throwing 1m games of understanding whats valid or invalid move at certain positions or representation - it creates a mapping of how to go about the game.
foosballs: Still fascinating shit nevertheless
gaocaandra: he is making a muzero implementation that works on "every" environment
gigafact: nom nom pasta is ready
nejintejag: What are the outputs, and what is the inputs measuring?
Flying_Geese: thanks for the update guys!
xeeton: can anyone not read the previous comments? jfc the same question is answered over and over
whichtom: wdym environment @gaocaandra
l1ght5p33d: @foosballs "no rules" what do you think all the coding is about
foosballs: Come again, didn't get your question
gaocaandra: you have agents that act inside environments (check out python package gym)
whichtom: oh the games
whichtom: im being stupid ya I know gym, just havent used it in forever
WarSwick: You have no emotes?
LaheyFPS: @xeeton people who join cant see previous comments
calcmath: as you visit it a lot the value score should get weighed down
WarSwick: For subs
calcmath: just try for more simulations to see its effect?
bichid69: bro why is nothing working for you on these streams anymore
calcmath: you need the vist count to build up to reduce weigh down effect of value
calcmath: not reduce increse
braininavatt: @bichid69 the stupid questions make him lose focus Kappa
l1ght5p33d: it was a good test then
Vietnomnom: seq1
Sylens__: @georgehotz i just started using vim and my god am i amazed at the commands PogChamp
bichid69: think u peaked bro
garydsmith1: it would be funny if he again quit stream to watch the movie
gigafact: if it does not work it means it's hard problem
calcmath: postive value is an accident of the situation
bichid69: @braininavatt nah bro he defo peaked
calcmath: it will get averaged to low i think with more simulations
xeeton: @garydsmith1 this is like reading the book, before watching the film
routerkicker: !uptime
garydsmith1: @xeeton oh yeah true that
l1ght5p33d: @Sylens__ if you want to do something in vim it will probably be in here somewhere https://vim.fandom.com/wiki/Vim_Tips_Wiki
garydsmith1: how many of you guys use vim?
THX1342: just the 1337
Sylens__: @l1ght5p33d what do you mean by doing something in vim?
bichid69: anyone who uses vim is an uptight asshole
ggtom: vim editor kek i just use notepad++
Sylens__: i was just using the vim tutor atm LUL
THX1342: bichid69 you're trying to hard bro
garydsmith1: no man @bichid69
Snobbysteven: nvim user here
gaocaandra: @bichi69 preach
gaocaandra: use nano
THX1342: he uses notepad.exer
bichid69: @THX1342 too*
l1ght5p33d: @Sylens__ Idk like highlight with arrow keys, copy/cut/paste, delete line, etc
garydsmith1: @ggtom i use notepad ++ as a replacement for windiws notepad
bichid69: fuck nano
THX1342: bichid69 yes, thank you
gaocaandra: jajajaajaa
bichid69: nano is literal aids
ggtom: garydsmith1 it is actually dope. with extensions it becomes super dope.
routerkicker: yeah nano sucks. vim is pretty nice if you learn most of the keybinds
Sylens__: @l1ght5p33d uhhhh thank you but ill figure it out lol
mr_micoos: Vim team
THX1342: arguing about editors is noob shit
eDONze: !uptime
garydsmith1: @ggtom i like notepad ++ a lot but dont like to code on it
Foxxy_xx: whats he doing?
Sylens__: oof
garydsmith1: who like sublime text more then vim?
bichid69: yeah vim is okay once you spend half your life learning random keybinds so you look cooler infront of your friends
bichid69: asshole
garydsmith1: i do! for now atleast
l1ght5p33d: Editing server files can only use command line
gaocaandra: it doesn't matter what you use, as long as you are using it, but we can all agree sublime is shit tho
l1ght5p33d: all your desktop apps are pathetic
ggtom: garydsmith1 why? i love it tbh once i got used to it. just use the dark mode with correct intellisense thingy.
mr_micoos: Atom>Sublime
kingvoneduard: visual studio is better
gaocaandra: i really disliked the whole interface
l1ght5p33d: except intellij
jib1337: root children Pog
lordmordi_: @bichid69 lol, that's the only people learn to use vim. just to look more intellectual
garydsmith1: @gaocaandra lol why is sublime shit tho? it's good as a text editor
gaocaandra: at the time i didn't know as much
bichid69: you know the chat fucking sucks ass when it's aboute code editors
Artara_: please ban code editor talks
gigafact: i really do not understand the whole obsession about text editors in every programming community
gaocaandra: so maybe right now i'd be able to extract more value out of it
BlueSeamoose: lol
mr_micoos: @bichid69 Hahahahaha
32bitrobo: Geo Hot is a genius, he inspired me to learn python. ALL HAIL Cthulhu
Foxxy_xx: LUL
THX1342: code editor talk is noob talk
gaocaandra: but vs code has been doing fine for me
TheKoreanZombi: And keyboards
frunkAF: LUL
calcmath: try upping the simulations count
triple__m: monkaS
gaocaandra: and colab for prototyping
rockthrone: and keyboards lol
garydsmith1: bwhahha that's ture i am bad programer for now
gigafact: are you a 1 or a 0
garydsmith1: true*
kingvoneduard: 1 is The One
moizai: the one is the zero
THX1342: this chat had a higher mean IQ during the biotech streams
mr_micoos: Is it tea time?
Foxxy_xx: @georgehotz do you sleep in your kitchen?
eldac_kno: lol sleep question
jib1337: Water is the best drink
l1ght5p33d: WKB analysis with cohesion
garydsmith1: @thx1342 that's true
bichid69: ITS FUCKING COHESION TENSION BRO
jsnfly: :D
jib1337: Pog
TheLastMrX: hi me when seeing this on YouTube , love you me
gaocaandra: what do you think it will take to solve md
inmygut: real adhd in motion folks
garydsmith1: @foxxy_xx yea he sleeps in kitchen
FargioFarmani: Now turn the glass over and speak about gravity
buddhm: it's just a bunch of vibrations
THX1342: what's this background clicking noise?
mr_micoos: he doesn't need to sleep
gaocaandra: saying that is like saying a plane is just wings
mero_1181: His dryer
braininavatt: @THX1342 coins in the washing machine Kappa
技術宅: this isn't the secret
bichid69: MD is not a question, hence it's unsolvable
THX1342: why does the loss spike up like that at the end?
l1ght5p33d: Water waves always wkb https://pdfs.semanticscholar.org/4929/2ec387f59e0cf926b6bf6ea0141eb5395af8.pdf
garydsmith1: can't he just use pdi to keep the stick balanced?
truemorpheuz: 1111 it is a good idea
garydsmith1: pid*
THX1342: garydsmith1 sure but the end goal is not balancing the stick it's learning the algorithm
rugito: what are we doing this stream?
THX1342: rugito read the title
garydsmith1: @thx1342 oh i get that. but it can be done with pid right?
THX1342: garydsmith1 sure
rugito: I'm too Pepega to understand title
FargioFarmani: Upload the code
eldac_kno: current water simulations look pretty realistic in movies
garydsmith1: @thx1342 right!
calcmath: isnt the MCTS based on the neural network prediciton of the reard, shihc is bad initially
calcmath: I say just give it more simulations
famaz47: !uptime
braininavatt: PogChamp
PeinlicherAffe: KonCha
braininavatt: I want a badge VoHiYo
THX1342: LUL
PeinlicherAffe: GunRun cvHazmat
jsnfly: how?
l1ght5p33d: @eldac_kno probably just a source video with heavy effects, no useful 3D information
THX1342: add that to the channel name
tauzN: but why?
THX1342: @georgehotz
gaocaandra: ye
whichtom: ye
bichid69: why am i missing the point?
Joooooooooonas: probably not
rugito: Pepega huh
fluorogarbage: deepmind always leaves the secret sauce out of the paper
garydsmith1: @bichid69 lol
gaocaandra: whats the bug?
hurzg: if it can balance a stick, then in theoriy it could also keep an airplane stable
eldac_kno: no, i mean current 3d software has pretty realistic fluid simulation
hurzg: its about the principle
THX1342: change name to @georgehotz_if_you_ask_why_you_are_a_noob
eldac_kno: it is not real time though
mattdougherty22: how was the movie?
Jehhred: Missing the point is my middle name
gigafact: how do you debug this kind of code?
kingvoneduard: I don't do anything, George is doing all the shit.
routerkicker: the inference is real time for sure.
calcmath: neural network for reward is not trained well initially, so it will have spurious one sided policy
THX1342: I'm just seeing the code. Is 1 and 0 "left" and "right" commands for the cart?
calcmath: yes
ggtom: uh check the learning rate
lilou04: sounds monkaS
garydsmith1: did you guys know the internet hates bill gates?
sbamCS: !followage
l1ght5p33d: @eldac_kno Well good just do fourier analysis on results of your sim and let all the beautiful maths die
bichid69: bill gates caused corona bro
ibizi77: square it
CaptainAshtar: is the chat today will be only for subscribers?
CaptainAshtar: again
技術宅: it should be
PeinlicherAffe: what do you think?
sbamCS: which keeeeeeeyboard do u have
garydsmith1: for no reason then he said "increasing people's life with vaxcine they will have less babies"
PeinlicherAffe: @CaptainAshtar CarlSmile
truemorpheuz: @PeinlicherAffe yes :)
calcmath: add back the softmax
PeinlicherAffe: @truemorpheuz :)
calcmath: no add it the new place as well
truemorpheuz: :)
bichid69: softmax sandwich
nejintejag: those sounds in the background.. Is there a dog or some animal in the apartment?
chemicalflash: is self.maximum = -float('inf') correct ?
braininavatt: balance my stick Kappa
l1ght5p33d: multi max .. deep mind's secret sauce
calcmath: higher UCB score gets weighted too much if you dont use sftmax
bliutwo: Sorry, I'm new to the stream. I won't ask a question like that next time. Love the stream! <3
rockthrone: pretty sure it's laundry
rudolphdoesgames: @nejintejag dryer
Rocky_88: when you realize chat doesn't do laundry
rockthrone: haha
garydsmith1: DiSHwAShEr
K1ngjulien_: good evening!
garydsmith1: we gona get a hype trin going?
garydsmith1: train*
MrVitoDayz: this looks nice
bliutwo: !faq
K1ngjulien_: what are you working on? invers pendulum simulation?
gaocaandra: what is multimax?
MrVitoDayz: can I apply this to biology ?
bichid69: bro this stream is so frustrating it's ruining my mental health
nejintejag: @Rocky_88 haha actually doing laundry as we speak. But we have a community laundry place in my house.
MrVitoDayz: @georgehotz
技術宅: yay physics sim is doing something
THX1342: Rocky_88 I do laundry at the river over the stone
rockthrone: rockthrone subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 6 months! Thanks for a cool channel!
Rocky_88: im just messing around
l1ght5p33d: @bichid69 leave
garydsmith1: @bliutwo what kind of question
truemorpheuz: i enabled rtx voice, so i dont have to hear his background noise
bliutwo: @garydsmith1 i asked him "why chromium over firefox" and he timed me out LUL so my bad, i didn't get it
bliutwo: new to the stream, that'll happen
fluorogarbage: did you add exploration noise at the root
garydsmith1: @bliutwo lol
braininavatt: #stretchminute chat
THX1342: geo, how do you choose research topics to work on? Is it from papers you read?
braininavatt: go
Basti_Soldier: NICEEEEEEEEEEEEE
THX1342: oh he's gone
技術宅: jenny82Q
bliutwo: @garydsmith1 what if i ask the same question, but i use "how did you decide to use chromium over firefox" xcalThinking do you think he'd ban me if i asked it that way?
rraksut: manneredKappaCyborg
K1ngjulien_: i do not agree with your music choice.
staypeaceful89: !faq
ggtom: bliutwo take one for the team
garydsmith1: @bichid69 won't answer i guess, he uses chromium because chrome has better security and away from google
garydsmith1: @bichid69 he found bugs in firefox
sakshambhutani2001: listen to Skechers by drip report
Lizardan: !uptime
CJslider14: zooming != visualization
bliutwo: @ggtom it's fine, he knows i'm supporting him by being a sub, so even if he bans / times me out , at least he'll know i'm supporting him
Lizardan: Firefox > all
metallsimp: use tor
garydsmith1: bwhahahha
ggtom: chromium PepeLaugh
lilou04: whats wrong with chrome
TheKoreanZombi: Bikeshedding
FargioFarmani: Opera?
技術宅: curl
bliutwo: hahaha truuuu
braininavatt: monkaS
Snobbysteven: edge 4 lyfe!
K1ngjulien_: lynx all the way LUL
3ygun: Firefox nathanGodstiny
fluorogarbage: exploration noise homie
tauzN: internet explorer best
技術宅: you had too much faith
saintmthw: LUL
bliutwo: 3ygun i see you are a man of culture as well
juviin: the face of a disappointed father
eDONze: PokSuicune
tajpouria: There is 1% of chat geo
bliutwo: 3ygun Hhhehehe
3ygun: @bliutwo Of course nathanWeeb
lilou04: what about tweeter vs facebook
HopZe: KKona
getjump: internet explorer Kappa
技術宅: am I timed
braininavatt: there you go chat, ie it is SeemsGood
outgray: terminal
bliutwo: terminal as an internet browser Pog
getjump: tabs vs spaces lets go
Digital_donger: autoplay mizkifS
garydsmith1: why is that a stupid discussion tho?
bliutwo: atom vs sublime Pog
braininavatt: yt autoplay WutFace
bliutwo: vim vs emacs Pog
mondeverest: BibleThump
FargioFarmani: What about Microsoft Edge tho??
bliutwo: LOOOOOL
技術宅: ^ those examples are why
bojosos: Do you think North Korea leader is dead?
outgray: yea
bliutwo: truuuu, i see your point
bliutwo: thank you for explaining
saintmthw: emacs and vim LUL
calcmath: I think adjusting temperature of MCTS softmax might fix issue
dgkng0d: yo George how is quarantine going
fluorogarbage: exploration noise at the root
a_ato: 60%
gigafact: new banned question: text editors?
bliutwo: georgehotz i haven't used jupyter notebooks much, can you tell me what is great about them?
lilou04: 1 is bigger than 0 so 1 it is
fluorogarbage: slap a dirichlet on that bad boy
calcmath: low temperatute means sensitive to small changes in value
garydsmith1: you know why this problem is harder for george this time? he's reading the chat too much
TheKoreanZombi: Browser chat = Bikeshedding: The act of wasting time on trivial details while important matters are inadequately discussed due to lack of expertise by those involved.
bliutwo: truuuu reading chat is pretty distracting
garydsmith1: @bliutwo yes
Zasuslive: 'whats better x or x'.. whatever tool helps you get whatever youre trying to achieve done, thats it.
calcmath: is the cartpole always going to fall right at the beginneing?
outgray: ok use brainfuck
tatsumiss: !uptime
dgkng0d: he got some tunnel vision skills
ggtom: LATER NERD got eeem
dgkng0d: but i can't even focus for 30 minutes Kappa
braininavatt: LUL
god_damn: see thats why humans are gunna be fine, terminator isnt going to happen
garydsmith1: @zasuslive dont you think when we understand why someone's using one tool, we understand what we can use that tool for?
sananelansalak13: insane
bliutwo: @Zasuslive true - personally, i just have privacy concerns, that's all
bliutwo: @garydsmith1 ^
romulan_empire7: romulan_empire7 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Ledouin: HACKERMANS
bojosos: ay I would love to know what that board of keys is but I am never going to find out
fluorogarbage: dankest distribution
ggtom: it's a distribution
garydsmith1: @bliutwo yeah exactly, you get to know about the spyware
bliutwo: @bojosos honestly cm storm tkl browns is my fav
sananelansalak13: :D
garydsmith1: @bojosos search commai archive. you will find out
sananelansalak13: do a ctf
ggtom: fluorogarbage a fellow statistician sheneyEneyW
dgkng0d: and i want to thank the guy who gifted me sub 4 month ago bro I'm sorry I didn't even notice that TakeNRG TakeNRG
mr_micoos: what time is there
sananelansalak13: play ctf
GoosemanTV: do CTF!
Mariosavitch: hulk strength
bliutwo: @garydsmith1 i love google, but privacy is a huge concern to me - not for any particular reason other than i believe in privacy to its fullest extent
whichtom: its 10:00
lilou04: cooking stream when?
garydsmith1: @dgkng0d yeah happend to me too
garydsmith1: @bliutwo yeha i get it
mero_1181: Dirichelet function puts mass 1 on alpha
mightbewill: it's the start condition biased or something,
ggtom: ban this deno nerd
mero_1181: 0 otherwise
技術宅: jupyter is intuitive and easy to get useful data visualization
bliutwo: @技術宅 thank you, that is a helpful answer
Zasuslive: @garydsmith1 yes if you know why someone uses a tool perhaps it may be useful for you too but thats usually in very niche use-cases, in which case u shud be asking specifically 'do u have a better workflow for doing x'
Digital_donger: mizkifSad yes
qatarking24xd: float
aacarm: if eggs are best by today, they are likely still ok.
calcmath: dirichlet distribution is a probability distribution of probability distributions
garydsmith1: @zasuslive yeah i agree with you
mightbewill: sink good
jh_od: I love you 💕
Krakatoa77: sink good
Zasuslive: @bliutwo if u care about privacy to its 'fullest extent' u need to get off the internet and get rid of your tracking devices
sananelansalak13: play a ctf
ostbobmuon: plz give url what he is doing
bliutwo: @Zasuslive true, you have a good point
gigafact: @ostbobmuon https://arxiv.org/src/1911.08265v2/anc/pseudocode.py
ostbobmuon: thx
getjump: Georgo mah boy eating egs
tajpouria: It seems like chat makes george to t think why he even streaming
bliutwo: @Zasuslive i just wish that the two categories "privacy" and "convenience" weren't two separate, completely non-overlapping circles (in terms of a venn diagram)
Zasuslive: @bliutwo sorry that might have came across rude, i just consider 'privacy to its fullest extent' as going full richard stallman
FargioFarmani: He is working on MuZero Implementation. Summary: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ
bliutwo: @Zasuslive you good
bliutwo: @Zasuslive stallman has definitely lost his credibility over time
bliutwo: some shit that guy says is something else
mattdougherty22: I will no longer have lower expectations. My fault Geo
mightbewill: eggs: float=bacteria metabolizing egg to gasses
Himdextermorgan: do you guys think that working as a backend developer can be a start to be a ethical hacker one day?
lolzmaster99: What part of the algo is he working on rn?
rudolphdoesgames: @FargioFarmani damn that was a shitty one
bliutwo: @Himdextermorgan can't you just take a class and get credentials to be an ethical hacker?
FargioFarmani: I'm sorry
Himdextermorgan: not that easy in my country @bliutwo
ggtom: FargioFarmani you are forgiven
mattdougherty22: George, what do you think of Dexter?
bliutwo: @Himdextermorgan damn, sorry to hear that
saintmthw: @Himdextermorgan then how would we know
bichid69: fandango
Mariosavitch: 1111
ggtom: less stupid = more smurt
bichid69: still stupid
just4valorant_: rick and morty out in a week boyzz
Mariosavitch: scramble
rudolphdoesgames: fried
bliutwo: scrambled
aacarm: fried
braininavatt: Jebaited
whichtom: scramble
pakard: scrambled
lolzmaster99: Scramble!
bichid69: scrambled
ggtom: scrambled
eyep1e: scrambled mofo
Himdextermorgan: @saintmthw the point is there is no specific course i could take here which would make be an ethical hacker, but there is a lot for software development
mattdougherty22: omlete
laflame954: How do i get geroge tier hyper focus
bojosos: baked
qcDENNEMANN: What chair is that?
bliutwo: @laflame954 he's still reading chat, so ur boned
eyep1e: scrambled in a tortilla wrap
eyep1e: dont judge me
bliutwo: @laflame954 if that's your goal,* that is
nejintejag: Don't do any type of hacking it has a horrible reputation.
Zasuslive: pluralsight is free till end of this month guys if you want free resources, i dno how good it is but its free rn so its worth checking
garydsmith1: @himdextermorgan just learn the skills and prove that you have the skills can get you a job
bliutwo: i mean, helping people protect themselves against security exploits seems pretty awesome to me
saintmthw: @Himdextermorgan are there ethical hacker careers in your country? look at those and work backwards from there to see what u have to do
bliutwo: that would be considered "hacking"
aacarm: those eggs are fine
lolzmaster99: @Himdextermorgan To be a "hacker" you need to know how things work (networking, web apps, etc.). Start with learning how to build those things, then when you understand you can come back and try to take them down back
PhosphoricAcid: me
garydsmith1: where is my egg
gigafact: marketing people
bliutwo: you can literally get a credential to be one!
ggtom: some nerds lul
nejintejag: hacking for losers
bliutwo: LUL
getjump: B I O H A C K I N G
tajpouria: 😅😅😅😅
saintmthw: LUL
gabrielopesantos: haHAA
chemicalflash: hacking ethics
Himdextermorgan: lol
bliutwo: HAHAHA
saintmthw: i think this dude just doesnt wanna get arrested in his country
bliutwo: eggs look great bro
routerkicker: put prints in muzero/mcts to find out where the bogus values are introduced
Zasuslive: u need some ketchup and toast bruh
greyoctagon: this whole idea of getting a piece of paper that says you're a haxxor is so last century
bliutwo: LOOOL
just4valorant_: give one sir
braininavatt: VoHiYo can I get mine?
Lite98: Ethical hacking ml7Head
saintmthw: PogChamp really?
kaksoispistedeh: dude, i had to visit one of these ethical hacking courses, and it was very useful for me personally. it made me realize how bullshit certifications are
bliutwo: WAIT REALLY
K1ngjulien_: "if you don't get caught its not illegal"-hacking
braininavatt: cant wait to have mine :)
tajpouria: definitely can apply job
bliutwo: ok once i get my job i'll pay you $200 (mainly for the entertainment, but also to put the frame on my wall)
balloonpopa: how do I get one sent to me? I'll frame it on my own
lilou04: PepeHands
Artara_: do you still have your useless waffle maker?
nejintejag: @chemicalflash I think that it just a lawyer.
qubitmanipulator: you described subscribers
bliutwo: qubitmanipulator LUL
bliutwo: qubitmanipulator truuuu
NicosPops: good stuff man!
Lite98: All human beings need a sense of worth and validation from other humans
ggtom: is the m variable the tree?
bliutwo: !git
Himdextermorgan: @saintmthw yeah there are a lot of jobs for that, but the colleges which offers this kind of course is too far from here..
euiq: should have used rust
ggtom: i have a feeling there's an object that needs to get reset in jupyter notebook
rudolphdoesgames: @bliutwo https://github.com/geohot
garydsmith1: @lite98 not to the point where you won't believe yourself
gaocaandra: you have the internet you dont need college
bliutwo: @rudolphdoesgames thanks!
Lite98: True @garydsmith1 @georgehotz
fluorogarbage: exploration noise didn't work?
Kodaly: i don't have any friends :(
bichid69: isn't validation from other people for money necessary for the prostitution business
ophicleidon: Anyone know how easy it is to get a remote reversing job if you just play (and win) CTFs?
bliutwo: @bichid69 LOOOOOL
bliutwo: what the fuck
jontowtruck: today is monte carlito arbol search?
bliutwo: let me just say that i love python because it's basically pseudocode that works
YOLOMAN1343: how many subs until you become a full time steramer
euiq: 1 1 1 1 1
bliutwo: YOLOMAN1343 5k
lolzmaster99: What is the output here?
jonathan865: this looks like it diverges? what is your learning rate?
Lite98: I dont think prostitution has anything to do with validation from either party, its simply a service @bichid69
Zasuslive: does george play any video games
lilou04: what if its some 900 iq ai thinking and we cant understand the output
euiq: @bliutwo for some definition of "works"
mightbewill: it's the sim biassed?
bliutwo: euiq LUL tru
garydsmith1: how do you guys deal with corpall tunnel syndrome?
YOLOMAN1343: learn dvorak @garydsmith1
hurzg: is it set to boolean? :D
ophicleidon: Just dont get it 4Head
eldac_kno: go to a doctor
bliutwo: @garydsmith1 generally i try to take scheduled breaks
bichid69: @Lite98 isn't a sexual service inherently some form of validation
bliutwo: oh yeah also go to a doctor if you actually have it
Aedroth: LOL
braininavatt: mine does :)
nejintejag: @bichid69 do you think the prostitutes that you by actually like you? they think of you like a loser with money.
garydsmith1: thanks guys!
Mobius5: TRUEEE
bichid69: no but evolution bro, sex=validation
K1ngjulien_: Show your worth by doing stuff thats good.
euiq: subscribing is all about belonging to the in-group
jordandiazdiaz91: jordandiazdiaz91 subscribed at Tier 1.
BaRtMan1912: @georgehotz New to the stream, could you tell me wtf im actually looking at right? LUL
YOLOMAN1343: you still with that one white girl @georgehotz
bliutwo: in my experience, having a degree makes getting a job easier, but there are definitely lots of people who don't have a degree who are awesome and employable too
Lite98: @BaRtMan1912 Youre watching smartness
YOLOMAN1343: the one that works for computer
fluorogarbage: Have you looked at pb_c again?
BaRtMan1912: @Lite98 no shit xD
SlowDeluxe: what happend to the razer laptop, mac still the champ ?
jordandiazdiaz91: good job
ophicleidon: Does the optional typing in python help at all? I didn't have a good time with it but it was quite a while ago
bliutwo: georgehotz do you like mario games?
bliutwo: sorry if that's a stupid question
ophicleidon: Saw a -> float there
garydsmith1: @slowdeluxe he said windows is for boomers, i agree and still use it...
eldac_kno: you guessed it right lol
bliutwo: ophicleidon what does optional typing mean? like how variables aren't explicitly typed?
FargioFarmani: a: int = 0
bliutwo: same, i'm a boomer and i play games, so windows is the os for me rn
lilou04: why 1's land = bad?
Zasuslive: windows for boomers, osx for millenials, ios/android for zoomers
ArcherCreatlol: why does chat look so cancer?
bliutwo: ArcherCreatlol whoever smelt it dealt it
euiq: interesting that schrittwieser is first author
euiq: any insiders?
bliutwo: i'm inside gachiGASM
garydsmith1: the sad part is i dont eve play games, linux doesnt work fully in my laptop
garydsmith1: even*
bliutwo: damn, that sucks
bliutwo: i usually use ubuntu, but quarantine prevents me from going outside, so i play games more now
garydsmith1: oh right so dual boot?
bliutwo: exactly
技術宅: sushiWOW
Zasuslive: george do u play video gamez or nah
bliutwo: LUL
mondeverest: Jebaited
kaksoispistedeh: i use arch btw :)
bliutwo: LOOOL
not_Awful: prob
lolzmaster99: No dude
eyep1e: nico pleb
euiq: just don't say the k word
azer0s: azer0s subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! ayy love you George, keep it up!
Digital_donger: windows xp was cool
euiq: monkaS
braininavatt: monkaS
garydsmith1: George is getting so frustrated
Krakatoa77: LUL
saintmthw: are you having fun at least?
Legardovia: hi everyone
bliutwo: me
rudolphdoesgames: @niko174_ he is implementing MuZero
Mariosavitch: you
lolzmaster99: I don;t think you can get away with taking out the min_max_stats
lilou04: me
Vackin: i
crawcraw66: me i think
BaRtMan1912: me :)
Artara_: 42
bichid69: everyone in chat
Zasuslive: lmao
parktype: me :D
3ygun: They’re useful @georgehotz nathanW
eldac_kno: russian letters=/=russian, but that was russian yes
euiq: Kappa /
Digital_donger: mizkifYo
Mariosavitch: who wrote it
3ygun: KappaPride /
lolzmaster99: It normalizes values and long term they will blow up
Spenceri102121: Me :)
gabrielopesantos: KappaWealth
bichid69: nothing works is my new life motto
chemicalflash: didn't you say that the point of the streams is that there is no point?
eldac_kno: point of stream is to make ppl think
bliutwo: at the least, georgehotz you know that your personality has entertainment value and that people are willing to pay for it
mondeverest: LUL
lilou04: LUL
LaheyFPS: LUL
Mariosavitch: LUL
gabrielopesantos: LUL
mhammad123: ay wasap rn
ophicleidon: LUL
bliutwo: LUL
SlowDeluxe: KEKW
jontowtruck: LOL
saintmthw: LUL
parktype: LUL
bichid69: hahahaha
mhammad123: who got banned lol
技術宅: twitch Dan Harmon
williami000: Owned
Krakatoa77: LUL
garydsmith1: bwhHahahhaah
Digital_donger: dictatorship PogChamp
not_Awful: fuck
gaocaandra: banhammer
mhammad123: Bruh wat he did to get banned bruh
ophicleidon: monkaS
lilou04: time to seize de means of donations
Mariosavitch: i aint scurd
bliutwo: LUL
not_Awful: really?
slevinxd: i think i know whos gonna replace kim
namenamison: But can you ban us all if we all raise against you?
rudolphdoesgames: @mhammad123 dont risk it
gaocaandra: you get a ban you get a ban
jontowtruck: kim yo jung for President!
mhammad123: He was a scapegoat lol
Zasuslive: anybody could get it
fluorogarbage: Have you taken a look at the action selection constants? The ones from the paper are for higher dimensional envs
gaocaandra: everyone gets a ban
easysleeep: hahahaha
bliutwo: @namenamison LUL
not_Awful: fear>love?
garydsmith1: someonss making a new account
Plurmorant: monkaS
ophicleidon: monkaS
anguscupcake: will u ban a SUBSCRIBER
TsihTV: george for leader of north korea
bliutwo: monkaS
murermader: do it
lexxy23: relax!
Mariosavitch: monkaS
sakshambhutani2001: lol
gaocaandra: jajajajaja
frunkAF: I didn't say nothin, pls
bojosos: you can't
eldac_kno: fear means respect
lolzmaster99: Chill bro
mhammad123: unban his ass bro :c
bojosos: you need money
qubitmanipulator: create a ban bot.
bliutwo: yeah look at me i got timed out
chemicalflash: or we ban you by not watching?
SlowDeluxe: don't do it chat im trying to learn monkaS
3ygun: He insulted our Lord and savior @georgehotz
parktype: can I be banned? :D
Basti_Soldier: noooooo ajajajjaa
bliutwo: @chemicalflash he's too notorious to have no viewers
braininavatt: just make sure to not choose your heart surgeon from chat Kappa
garydsmith1: fear means fake respect
Mariosavitch: i know why
fluorogarbage: print the visit counts
LaheyFPS: I know why
ophicleidon: @georgehotz twitch chat is just irc, 10 lines of python and you can ban whoever says anything Kappa
alphagainzzz: perks of being a dictator LUL
TheKoreanZombi: He will ban a subscriber to strike fear in the proletariat masses.
Mariosavitch: me :)
bliutwo: @braininavatt LOOOOOOOOL TRUU
bichid69: 1 is the loneliest number
bliutwo: @braininavatt it's never too soon
bliutwo: alright have a great stream, see ya bro
garydsmith1: bye man
LaheyFPS: It's simple why it just outputs 1's
ronnyosnes: does he still do security related stuff or only ml?
lilou04: the graph changed PogChamp
eldac_kno: mostly ml
q4nt3r: you don't need to ban all, just the ones initiating the revolt... hit once, hit hard LOL
Mariosavitch: it knows Pog
SlowDeluxe: Pog
braininavatt: it did something PogChamp
azer0s: @georgehotz create something like chaosmonkey for twitch. instead of killing k8s pods, it just randomly bans people.
lilou04: learning
slevinxd: moves like jagger
ophicleidon: isn't that a lot of 1s :thin\
garydsmith1: did someone actually got banned?
calcmath: good search is inefficient and not scalable
braininavatt: WE DID IT CHAT VoHiYo
ophicleidon: 🤔
JdPaulBlart: anyone want to start a cout with me?
eldac_kno: ban every tenth just like in good roman times
Tuhafadam: Hey
bichid69: I have to go do some webdev now, fucking hate webdev
garydsmith1: is George a nice person in real life?
namenamison: @JdPaulBlart how do you start a cout on twitch?
JdPaulBlart: yes supreme ruler hotz is a very nice person
garydsmith1: @bichid69 for your job?
namenamison: Someone ban @georgehotz
garydsmith1: @jdpaulblart lol
lolzmaster99: Transfer learn old search to the MCTS?
bichid69: @garydsmith1 just freelancing for cash bro, times r tough
garydsmith1: @namenamison what if he bans you?
mhammad123: supreme leader geocoldz
lolzmaster99: Warm start on MCTS
garydsmith1: @bichid69 i would like to do that too, where do you do it?
Mariosavitch: daddy bezos
calcmath: use trained value network in MCTS? to see if it works
guest1GRjBAYo: are drops on?
rudolphdoesgames: @guest1GRjBAYo lmao
takkat14: have you seen WANN solution of cartpole?
JdPaulBlart: we should use muzero to solve your speed challenge on github @georgehotz
garydsmith1: @namenamison lol onle bezos or the twitch social team can ban hots
azer0s: I feel super dumb. what is going on and what is muzero?
eldac_kno: muzero is new algorithm by deep mind, use google ffs
mhammad123: looks like namenison got fuked
garydsmith1: @azer0s he's trying to learn how to make the computer learn to balance that stick
lilou04: MonkaHmm
azer0s: @garydsmith1 @eldac_kno thanks!
rugito: @eldac_kno who's google
Krakatoa77: Pepega
ophicleidon: I think you need a whole lot more than 100
lolzmaster99: You need the normalization!
lolzmaster99: From min_max_stats
lilou04: monkaHmm
garydsmith1: @namenamison can you lend me some amazon stock?
calcmath: use softmax fn, ur susotm one might be overflwoing
garydsmith1: @azer0s yeah!
Mariosavitch: bab
calcmath: softmax overflow bug
lolzmaster99: Put min_max stats back in
lolzmaster99: It normalizes values
azer0s: but like....can't you do the same with fuzzy logic? 😅
mhammad123: @namenamison is u still alive lol
toobossbear7: hi Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1
garydsmith1: @azer0s hes trying to learn how to do it this way
calcmath: classical softmax floating point overflow bug
azer0s: @garydsmith1 fair enough 😂
lolzmaster99: Add 1e-12 to probabilities to avoid overflow
tripcloth: what is mcts?
takkat14: you should use expit
lolzmaster99: No way wow dtype=float64 ftw
mhammad123: @namenamison yEaeaaeEa duUde
takkat14: because of overflow
garydsmith1: just so you guys know, twitch chat is the subtitles of the video
niko174_: Осуждаю за твой поступок <3 Guys I m come back
eldac_kno: remember no russian
garydsmith1: @niko174_ who are you?
jagger_rsw: polish?
niko174_: no
jagger_rsw: yes
niko174_: I from Russia
ak0ya_: @niko174_ where in russia are you from?
jagger_rsw: speak american
lexxy23: uk english?
garydsmith1: @niko174_ oh roght
mhammad123: geohotz chill out يزم
foti_kasparov: Espanol?
jagger_rsw: only brits can speak
parktype: What abt Spanish?
mattdougherty22: Do you know who Daniel Schmactenberger is? Talked with Eric Weinstein about zero sum society and the need/how to design new game recently
技術宅: this is the most 4chan chat in twitch
SurfCat: We speak only American here brother KKona
Mariosavitch: rip
niko174_: Ok, I undestood
Defak: D:
jagger_rsw: Da
Featen: Did we discover how did it win with people in chess?
lemmywemmy: hell yeah brother KKona
Killon1: hi @georgehotz
tauzN: @技術宅 yikes
bojosos: what about Bulgarian?
garydsmith1: @namenamison is dead
Defak: English only 3Head
foti_kasparov: Français?
kingvoneduard: Mesicanos
prafaeltsantos: portuguese?
the_best_russian_bear: Русский?
jagger_rsw: cyka
azer0s: Deutsch?
Mariosavitch: l33t speak?
parktype: speak;
andrewVadeika517: andrewVadeika517 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
eldac_kno: english mf do you speak it
maxschneider96: Only python and english fellas
foti_kasparov: YEAH !!! GO CHANNEL POINTS ! GO PLEBS!!
andrewVadeika517: sup geohot
gabrielopesantos: -430 DatSheffy
qubitmanipulator: Sub-only Kappa
ophicleidon: channel points were a mistake BibleThump
garydsmith1: come on hype train!!!!!!!!
mhammad123: كس امك يزمwhy you enable subscriber only
jagger_rsw: I think distracting George to talk about anything else than the current topic is an art in itself
eldac_kno: agree
niko174_: What do y think about russian programmers?
guest1GRjBAYo: eat ass, smoke grass
garydsmith1: @jagger_rsw yes, but we get less streams
Poralo45: Poralo45 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
maxschneider96: That´ s what I meant with AI for chat previously
LaheyFPS: why not get more moderators?
guest1GRjBAYo: Chat: 1 George: 0
chemicalflash: sub only chat ?
gaocaandra: in the night it's better
Tuhafadam: how do you test it ? on gui ?
garydsmith1: can i be a mod?
Joooooooooonas: The problem is if you are upset, more people try to troll you (because they think its fun), it would be best if mods would just timeout those guys without you mentioning them, less people would try to troll and you would be more efficient
gaocaandra: less shit talk
kaksoispistedeh: less geohot streams PepeHands
gigafact: increase the points to chat even if you are not a subscriber
mangoxavier: Haha
lilou04: when you gonna bring a viewer on stream and teach him how to code?
parktype: parktype subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! Don't take the stream away I like learning D:
garydsmith1: @laheyfps can you chat in sub only mode?
gaocaandra: yo
ak0ya_: @Joooooooooonas agreed
gaocaandra: hypetraiin
braininavatt: HYPEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
azer0s: what @joooooooooonas said.
jagger_rsw: HYPE-r-loop
tripcloth: twitch chat is cancer man, it's just the way it is
jagger_rsw: ok, let's all be serious and helpful now!
MrVitoDayz: Not all of it
eldac_kno: the game looks like gravity game on old phones
eldac_kno: would be fun to teach ml to play that
foosballs: gist of what naive search function is doing?
garydsmith1: SMOrc
garydsmith1: is commai archive on the chat?
jsnfly: Maybe use KnownBounds(-1, 1) to prevent nans
gigafact: yes
smurfd0: is the stick standing or falling?
calcmath: Look up softmax overflow bug
jagger_rsw: is MCTS monte carlo tree search?
garydsmith1: @gigafact wait are you commai archive?
mangoxavier: So close
braininavatt: PogChamp
eldac_kno: no russian bro
braininavatt: !mods
metallsimp: is this like a russian spy hub?
eldac_kno: he is just kinda famous in russia
chemicalflash: have you looked into neuroevolution strategies like NEAT for game playing?
lolzmaster99: You're supposed to normalize the value of the actions, output of value net
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz How do you compute the mean action vector?
brisingr1031: wait so what is cartpole?
lolzmaster99: Can I see where you put the normalization?
jsnfly: :D
foti_kasparov: SpaceX rocket
nomorequity: !uptime
LaheyFPS: 3 hours 17 minutes @nomorequity
gaocaandra: imagine commaX the android of space launch
mangoxavier: This is insanely interesting.
moshiko777: hello
mangoxavier: Are you working local?
mangoxavier: Nvm see url
Joooooooooonas: just take the norm of that negative Kappa
calcmath: can you print visit counts of all the tree nodes, might help to debug
rudolphdoesgames: from retrothrusting to no thrusting
Mariosavitch: because it values death
KyoshiDeath: how long has the stream been going for ?
gaocaandra: how does it know?
chemicalflash: maybe double cart pole ?
lolzmaster99: breakout-v0
poppingtonic: have you tried training recurrent world models?
whichtom: any atari ones?
LaheyFPS: @KyoshiDeath 3 hours 20 minutes
alexlucas__: Ant-v2
Plurmorant: geoguesser
KyoshiDeath: Thanks @LaheyFPS
whichtom: montezumas revenge
DasMastah: Minecraft
l1ght5p33d: @mangoxavier 8888? that mean external for some reason? what u mean
foti_kasparov: Do us
gaocaandra: BipedalWalker-v2
Plurmorant: montezumas revenge is NP-Impossible
lolzmaster99: Mountain car again?
lolzmaster99: It never worked before
YorkLai: can you share your bash and tmux setting?
smurfd0: spaceinvaders?
sondreal: Remember to hit the subscribe button boiiis!!
takkat14: what do u think about weight agnostic nn-s?
Mariosavitch: how does it know what the goal is mr hotz
foti_kasparov: @YorkLai github.com/geohot/configurations
foti_kasparov: configuration*
chemicalflash: double cart pole is easy next step
Plurmorant: tfw no reward FeelsBadMan
michelfugain69: how r u so smart 4Head
DeeboMC: Been at it like 3 and half hours already?
whichtom: Acrobot-v1?
Tuhafadam: Is it memorize how to play or learn how to play ?
ophicleidon: what model is he trying to train?
mangoxavier: Haha I have the same dryer or washer song lmao
Choruptian: wait did you get it to work?
Choruptian: I missed it
Penguino138: Up and at em
michelfugain69: Which GPU do you have @georgehotz ?
K1ngjulien_: @aldelecrane looks like an iMac or something, so a shit one
SlayerX1: LUL
Penguino138: How's the chat been behaving this morning?
michelfugain69: @K1ngjulien_ lol
smurfd0: your lunarlander does not shoot out those "feelers" that it does on the example
rudolphdoesgames: @Penguino138 bad
mangoxavier: There should be a weeble wobble sim
bojosos: We are free
michelfugain69: Double kills from geohot
Penguino138: @rudolphdoesgames Why is that? Been off topic again?
foti_kasparov: Acrobot got some moves
mangoxavier: That would give artificial gyro balance
K1ngjulien_: George how many WPM can you do on TypeRacer?
Seatedfury: Seatedfury subscribed with Twitch Prime.
DeeboMC: Pedro asked if you could hack the NSA
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz Do you think AI will take control over us in the next 10 years?
kaksoispistedeh: fucking Pepega chat
rudolphdoesgames: @Penguino138 a lot of dumb questions and stuff
Penguino138: Oh god i see all the message deleted it must be bad
DeeboMC: But then said he was joking
be9ns: Favorite computer doccumentaries?
ophicleidon: @georgehotz look at a0lite for a very simple mcts example
eldac_kno: protest looks like scam tbh
not_Awful: weak
bojosos: Protestj
K1ngjulien_: protest during lockdown? not a good idea
axlebear: sounds good
KiroShibaa: hi!! i'm your fan <3
mangoxavier: Laundry takes long time.
Penguino138: Protesting what?
gaocaandra: he is under 30
sakshambhutani2001: anti-lockdown protest?
not_Awful: what protest?
gaocaandra: he is ok
lolzmaster99: protests is astroturfing bro
lolzmaster99: youre a sheep
whichtom: freedom to work?
Tuhafadam: corona protest realy ?
axlebear: KKona Freedom
dorkmo: dicks out for harambe
whichtom: oh im down for that
not_Awful: ty
maxschneider96: Any other projects u´ ll be streaming soonish?
Penguino138: Protesting stagnant air in our apartments :p
K1ngjulien_: you gonna wear a mask?
DeeboMC: I wouldn’t have figured you as the protest type
MrJeff_: I agree.
FargioFarmani: Meet you there George
gaocaandra: make sure to kiss everyone in the mouth tho
gaocaandra: just to be safe
lilou04: that protest will turn in a meet and greet for geo
sakshambhutani2001: they are more of Trump rallies!
keith282: COVID isn't fun. Please be careful my guy
r0xtehem0x: r0xtehem0x subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months!
mangoxavier: Lifeguards are totally behind this.
be9ns: give me a good comp sci documentary
whichtom: dude i wish i was in socal
MrJeff_: We can't protest here. UK. We'll get arrested.
tytos01: what is this protest about ?
michelfugain69: 1 meter away
mattdougherty22: Israel has a good reopening plan
eldac_kno: joker masks
garydsmith1: @be9ns snowden
MrJeff_: The UK is a joke.
foti_kasparov: Clean your shoes after coming back
joseanavarrom: But you might be asymptomatic, that's the point
whichtom: the UK is a joke I agree
bojosos: wear a anonymous mask
axlebear: the breeze can carry the virus
Penguino138: Where can one even buy masks anymore? Amazon is like a black market with sketchy selelrs
eldac_kno: joker>anonymous
K1ngjulien_: well the fever takes two weeks to develops
mattdougherty22: Israel has a good reopening plan with a points based system
keith282: Damage has been shown in the CT scans of asymptomic people's lungs
fireposeidoncx: What is your final opinion on the Corona virus?
Tuhafadam: illogical
bovine_shield: Good afternooooooon.
Bacon4Life_: monkaS
braininavatt: monkaS
Penguino138: Oh no george is hot!
mangoxavier: What about the ppl they interact with after?
alphagainzzz: lol
ak0ya_: and girls :)
K1ngjulien_: from christian drosten, the guy who develped the first test
Joooooooooonas: what is that in celsius LUL
keith282: https://pubs.rsna.org/doi/10.1148/ryct.2020200110
joseanavarrom: None of us are doctors George
michelfugain69: Put milk on the cerales
garydsmith1: @joseanavarrom someone might be
niko174_: Nice, metric system
MrJeff_: I had a few drink with mates earlier. (currently 7pm in UK). We don't care tbh.
Penguino138: Is traditional SARS 3x flu too?
kaksoispistedeh: so, 3x0=0?
K1ngjulien_: more like 10x, but only if you 're old tbh
DeeboMC: Are you going to the protest just for something to do or because you think it will make a difference?
nejintejag: If they get infected whether you get symptoms or not they will produce new viruses that they will breath out.
eldac_kno: yes, that's called education
csal90: so true lol
gaocaandra: do you think wolfram lang is what you meant when you said you wanted a mix between coq and python?
bichid69: is it still ones?
jagger_rsw: doctors are practioners of science, not researchers
sakshambhutani2001: In most of the places, these are more of Trump Rallies
axlebear: PepeLaugh
poppingtonic: what's the protest really about?
yuptheladsdownthecans: @MrJeff_ you might not care but more vulneralble people do care
mangoxavier: Healthcare is a scam.
Penguino138: And Alex will probably be there
funwayz: measure temp after protest Kappa
michelfugain69: I hope you dont get sick, we need smart people like you
garydsmith1: you should stream the protest
joseanavarrom: AI will revolutionize current medicine
DeeboMC: Ok cool. That makes sense
bovine_shield: Wiggle waggle
K1ngjulien_: there's gonna be a lot of idiot antivaccs moms there
fireposeidoncx: Are you still using metamath?
axlebear: somebody clip it for when he gets the virus
tytos01: @georgehotz are you going to make a live video at the protest?
sakshambhutani2001: make America great again
garydsmith1: but if we drink bleach we will be safe
eldac_kno: don't you think when you go to a protest you are being used by people who benefit from it
Penguino138: @aldelecrane The only way geo is gonna get sick is if he forgets to wear his jacket when it rains
eldac_kno: any protest
maxschneider96: @joseanavarrom more than 230 companies out there using AI for drug discovery, it´ s already happening
michelfugain69: @Penguino138 LUL its true tho
mangoxavier: I’d like to see George argue with an anti-vax
MrJeff_: @yuptheladsdownthecans Best thing is, we don't have many people in my village. So we just keep calm and carry on.
pashafst: late to the party, what he's trying to make?
thelastkek: Protesting is beneficial, it builds herd immunity!!
lolzmaster99: bro its astroturfing!
spockshocks: its literally astroturfing
gaocaandra: kill off the weak ones
poppingtonic: @maxschneider96 yeah Insilico et al
DrakenZA: she could just be highly astroturfed and not even know it
foti_kasparov: Can we fuck the government by doing a walk?
yuptheladsdownthecans: @MrJeff_ so litreally nobody in your village leaves the village on a regular basis and comes into contact with other people? Seems very unlikely
spockshocks: all the reopen state facebook pages / websites were started by the same guy
DeeboMC: Oh yea, I’d be in if that’s the case
axlebear: surfing addict over here
sakshambhutani2001: fuck the government, but don't be dumb
joseanavarrom: @maxschneider96 and diagnostics
Penguino138: @georgehotz How hard is it gonna be to remove all the sand in the skate parks?
HopZe: Natural Selection boys
maxschneider96: @poppingtonic yeah
nejintejag: I think the 5G theories are fun. Completely insane but fun!
whichtom: protests have worked but not typically peaceful ones
thelastkek: Protesting is beneficial, it builds herd immunity!!.
geohot_pls_fck_me: god bless america
mayaeiouy: are you gonna stream from the protest @georgehotz
maxschneider96: @joseanavarrom I am developing a diagnostics device atm for my master´ s thesis. There is so much potential in that field
eldac_kno: i would protest twitch, if they banned this stream
mondeverest: do you livestream the protest?
thenomadplayer: what happened with 1 milion subs project on instagram?
niko174_: Lol dudes, I have April 27
DeeboMC: In for iconoclastic chicks
foti_kasparov: A walk a day keeps the government away !
IBaydenI: @georgehotz What is that wiggly thing going to be when its done?
sakshambhutani2001: How are you Doctors and Nurses dying? It's not just about age, it's about time you are exposed too
mangoxavier: That dude isn’t wiggling it’s humping.
ophicleidon: BibleThump
kaksoispistedeh: PepeHands
whichtom: the 2nd linkage is meant to get above the black line
axlebear: rip
jagger_rsw: are you trying to traing the chat by using some reward function (more streams if good chat)?
IBaydenI: @whichtom thanks :)
bovine_shield: Its also about the lung damage if you survive
Penguino138: How many other things in life have a 1/1000 chance to kills us? Probably a lot
garydsmith1: @jagger_rsw yes
HopZe: its called hibernation in nature language
joseanavarrom: But it's not kill us, it's kill our families for example
mayaeiouy: do you worry about the increased number of strokes seen in younger people who are covid positive
gaocaandra: you are good backgorund noise to work with, don't leave us.
mangoxavier: It’s literally a battle of your immune system holding out over the virus. Everyone has a diff immune system.
Penguino138: @mayaeiouy Where's the evidence?
whichtom: but people who are covid positive typically have underlying health conditions with themselves lead to a higher chance of strokes?
maxschneider96: @mangoxavier depends on your predisposition generally and the type of strain
whichtom: either way theres too little data for any conclusions
Penguino138: @mayaeiouy I'm almost positive you're references a fear mongering article that talked mostly about 40+ year old "young" people
thelastkek: look if yall want to stay locked up you do that. You cant force people to do the same
axlebear: Just stay inside like a good little citizen
GS540: LOL
whichtom: ya 'young' meaning 30-40 or something
l1ght5p33d: code snippets not allowed in chat?
niko174_: Ладно ребята, я пошел спать. Было приятно пообщаться. Good night <3
garydsmith1: StinkyCheese
eldac_kno: speaking of doctors possessing some extra knowledge after becoming doctors, it's more neccessary thing than sufficient, it's neccessary to have some medical education to make some claims, but not sufficient, imo
logi6000: yo
mayaeiouy: I said younger for a reason
Penguino138: Now I see why the chat has been bad again. Thinking article titles are science fact...
Kromtor: this guy the new hot reaction streamer? kek
eldac_kno: Monty Carlo
Digital_donger: TheIlluminati ?
nejintejag: @whichtom no everyone can get infected your health is irrelevant. Your health is related to the mortality of you get infected.
mayaeiouy: @penguino138 there’s also a medscape article
farlopote: kekers
logi6000: Simpson's stream?
thelastkek: Protesting is beneficial, it builds herd immunity!!
yungdeli_: Imao
Penguino138: @mayaeiouy An article that states 40-50 year olds are young to fear monger is not an article to read
garydsmith1: @thelastkek lol
bichid69: its about being bored
DeeboMC: When was that from?
un3okapi: George, you have a beautiful smile.
mayaeiouy: @penguino138 that’s like nearly half the age we usually see those stokes in
whichtom: again, theres too little data to draw any conclusions right now. when its over we'll have actual answers
zimslv: nerd immunity FTW
foti_kasparov: Then don't watch media
Kromtor: you're trapped in their scope
DeeboMC: Chomsky, cialdini
niko174_: Its like in Russia lmao
poppingtonic: the frame = the "overton window"
leonardssh22: hello geo
Penguino138: @mayaeiouy Yes those age groups may be at increased risk, but to say 40-50 year olds are young means you probably shouldn't read it
yungtoad1: read manufacturing consent by Chomsky it's all about this
whichtom: great book
mayaeiouy: @penguino138 says youngER
yungtoad1: yes great book
garydsmith1: india heavenly thinks corona is made by the Chinese
jagger_rsw: unsure if this follows, if someone says 'herd ummunity b/c of protest' you respond with 'yes, but at a risk of overcrowding hospitals'. Why I shouldn't buy into it?
l1ght5p33d: sue > protest
gigafact: so part 3 coming up later George? will be waiting for you here.
DeeboMC: Persuasion by Cialdini also
eldac_kno: would love to see programming in python in blender
poppingtonic: @yungtoad1 great book
mangoxavier: I need lazygit
Izimoney92100: please
her3hero: Pog
nejintejag: I think you have to stop listening media first to actually understand that frame thing George talked about.
lilou04: im behaving
her3hero: will sub for part 4
ak0ya_: !!
Vietnomnom: Part 4 seqWoo seqWoo
MrJeff_: I'm lurking....
bichid69: wat u doing the rest of the day?
Penguino138: Chat will always behave if it's subs only dotsKpog
PhosphoricAcid: this chat is pretty chill compared to most streams :)
garydsmith1: @eldac_kno can you actually do that?
gaocaandra: great!
Joooooooooonas: pls dont get arrested lol :D
nuffleee: 7 raiders from nuffleee have joined!
bovine_shield: lol that to-do list
bovine_shield: Laundry and protest
not_Awful: persuade only
eldac_kno: yes blender can be programmed in python
fireposeidoncx: Stream the protest
rudolphdoesgames: hey @nuffleee
Penguino138: Can't wait for the new apartment streams
justenpassant: when's the next stream?
Izimoney92100: stream the protest please
LaheyFPS: monkaS arrested
yungdeli_: what protest
justenpassant: a protest for what
lilou04: if you get arrested we will come and protest to get you out
Vrookems: *tries to get arrested*
braininavatt: can you not get arrested? :)
garydsmith1: @eldac_kno can you program python in blender tho?
nizero: George I'm going to label some comma data for you
not_Awful: bail you??
god_damn: jail break
PhosphoricAcid: living on the edge
3ygun: It’s a Russian post
funwayz: its police trap
DeeboMC: Have you ever been arrested?
fireposeidoncx: Stream the protest
HopZe: i hope there isnt one
eldac_kno: live laugh love
jontowtruck: how much better is san diego than new jersey... coming from a shoreman
logi6000: can I get all your stuff if you die
her3hero: her3hero subscribed at Tier 1.
chemicalflash: protest on twitch stream
garydsmith1: if you get arrested no self driving cars tho
Newlax: upload to YouTube channel
Penguino138: haha if geo gets arrested, he'll jailbreak real jail
Tuhafadam: what happend corona virus projct ?
robodemia: montezumas revenge
chair_78: ever done coke?
Vrookems: how u get caught with weed, just smoke it
Kromtor: peace is overrated
grizvok: lol
Kromtor: said my GAN
Izimoney92100: lol
bovine_shield: All my stuff does to you, george
masters8: flawless logic
jagger_rsw: can you enumerate benefits to subscribers, esp. once you take over the world?
l1ght5p33d: ayy lmaaoo
ak0ya_: what about money>
robodemia: you sound like jordan peterson
eldac_kno: interested in blender? it uses python for scripting, you can make interesting stuff
DeeboMC: Damn son
sakshambhutani2001: including the money?
ionelaipatioaei: how much is your net worth?
rudolphdoesgames: relationships are overrated
DeeboMC: That’s hardcore!!
gaocaandra: ethereum sc wills
no_g: What if someone's motivated by burning all your shit?
bichid69: what about your kids man?
CaliburOne: One of my best friends work in healthcare, its fucked out there. Hes doing 12 hour days every day in Florida.
chemicalflash: war on chat
qubitmanipulator: don't you trust anyone?
arakis_djall: what are your thoughts on chatbots?
braininavatt: ask him what he thinks about anarchism Kappa
Newlax: burn all the crypto
Vrookems: why not just donate your stuff to someone who would never want to kill you
nejintejag: @robodemia Explain.
Vrookems: like normal people
logi6000: can I get your macbook if you die
vyle01: Well hopefully you can trust the people you have on your will
ak0ya_: us gov will keep the money
bichid69: you not leavin dolla for your kids?
ak0ya_: so they will have an incentive
her3hero: build a crypto that burns itself upon death PogChamp
DeeboMC: You’re serious?
HopZe: if you die of covid, it should be
axlebear: 5Head
garydsmith1: @vrookems that person would want to kill you
jagger_rsw: anecdata
no_g: What if someone's motivated by burning all your shit? Then you're giving them an incentive to kill you monkaS
l1ght5p33d: thats the way
fireposeidoncx: My will is to see you on the JRE podcast
masters8: not always bruh
aPosterior: what a guy
Vrookems: @garydsmith1 my mother wouldnt kill me just to get my stuff
garydsmith1: @no_g but they will do it anyway
mangoxavier: They could still kill you for your stuff. They don’t need an easy out.
justenpassant: well it depends on if people in your will love you more than they wan to kill you. so you just want to estimate the amplitude of each one with a precision that satisfies you
luigivsf: covid is more media bulls* than reality. Id never know a close person who had that and told the entire story. Always is random people like reading a script to set some paranoia on people
yungdeli_: @fireposeidoncx yessssssssss
garydsmith1: @vrookems yeah, but you never know tho
gaocaandra: george on the portal would be nice
bovine_shield: IRON CLAAAAAD
MrJeff_: We have a load of empty Hospitals in the UK. It's a waste of tax payers money.
BrutalCSkAKAN: Just got here, are we doing Minecraft 2.0?
Tuhafadam: will you countunie programing corona virus seriess ?
sakshambhutani2001: why not drop money from helicopters?
logi6000: in philly all hospitals are overwhelmed they are doubling up people on 1 ventilator. nurses only get one mask per week
nejintejag: Gorge might not look good on JRE.
q4nt3r: some think that only "rich" individuals dying spawns people fighting over their stuff. I've seem families fight over a shitty 50 year old, not even running car.
l1ght5p33d: My apartment is so nice whatchu talkin bout
eldac_kno: speaking of Wolfram Physics, you said science need testability, but math doesn't have, but it's still science
fireposeidoncx: George you should talk to joe rogan
garydsmith1: i mean the BTK killer was a loving father
HopZe: what about other countries?
J3rwin: @georgehotz your streams are chill and cool man.
Vrookems: bombs cost money, drop them instead
bichid69: Why don't we reset the economy after this?
yungdeli_: !uptime
Penguino138: I don't know if I'll ever be able to take news articles seriously
greyoctagon: greyoctagon subscribed at Tier 1.
bichid69: start from scratch
logi6000: I know nurses who say this in those hospitals
cod4_lightning: "Don't follow people, follow ideas" That's islamic!
MrJeff_: google Nightingale Hospital.
justenpassant: watch this if you wanna feel good https://youtu.be/hWzccW4TQkg
nizero: in Phoenix they are furloughing doctors because there aren't enough patients
sakshambhutani2001: and would have been cheaper!
Penguino138: Stream lagging for anyone else?
tauzN: washingtonpost.com/evidence-for-what-geohot-just-asked
joseanavarrom: The health system capacity here in spain was absolutely over-exceeded
eldac_kno: what kind of evidence do you need, can you define
mayaeiouy: what you consider valid evidence do I have to go snap a pic in an icu
yungtoad1: how do you know if a source is verifiable
J3rwin: @Penguino138 twitch having a blip
mangoxavier: Data
DeeboMC: Lack of evidence isn’t evidence of lack.. in general tho.
LaheyFPS: @Penguino138 yes, but briefly
garydsmith1: @eldac_kno basically statics with verifying it
waterpaste: what is good evidence for u ?
sakshambhutani2001: I mean who can you trust as a credible source Trump?
braininavatt: he trusts institutions :)
nejintejag: Hum media media it is just people in the end right...
l1ght5p33d: No one knows it's impossible truth is false
justenpassant: sure, win win, but a better win if they pass their agenda with their win win strategy
DeeboMC: @tauzn Lmao
bichid69: we should reset the economy, everyone starts from scratch after this
foti_kasparov: What you think should be done ?
mangoxavier: Accreditation.
yungdeli_: whats the clip called, that one that George showed
Newlax: Have you heard of Destiny? It'd be interesting to see you two debate
yungtoad1: how can you know anything George with this mindset except what you see for yourself with your own eyes
DeeboMC: @braininavatt 😂
Lefer_: @georgehotz Are you watching Westworld?
tsparkles: what's the point of going to a protest and possibly infecting other people / catching the virus
no_g: There may be a guide on what constitutes a verifiable source, but how can you verify the guide itself?
Bacon4Life_: drink bleach guise
robodemia: talk while coding
no_g: monkaS
Vrookems: is my dad a credible source
jamesquinten: me :)
eldac_kno: he already said he is not interesteed in debates
Sylens__: @Lefer_ i would like to know as well
nejintejag: Define truth....
DeeboMC: Trump makes good points on amazon and the usps tho, to his credit
fireposeidoncx: You should go on the JRE podcast
Penguino138: Yeah ppl need to move on from thinking corona everything, and re-assess the other risks we take every day
no_g: @nejintejag Truth is a tautology
foti_kasparov: corona is more expensive than flu and beers
mangoxavier: You might get stabbed at ocean front idk
robodemia: $TERMINAL
yungdeli_: @georgehotz whats that simsons clip called
jcob5068: What is the protest trying to achieve?
Penguino138: Ron paul might be there
Deltasquadron2579: you might get struck by a meteor by sitting in that chair
Lefer_: liberty KKona
garydsmith1: wait the protest is real???
nizero: George the true libertarian
not_Awful: george, honestly, what is the point of doing anything?
Vrookems: gonna meet some beach sluts
waterpaste: LIberty LMAO
l1ght5p33d: It is a good test in case a real bad virus actually comes then we'll know how lockdown affects industry and life
chemicalflash: liberty to monetize ?
eldac_kno: i kinda lost you on wolfram physics, do you think it's not scientific because it doesn't provide testable(falsifiable) hypothesis?
0xatul: Whats up George?
qubitmanipulator: self-driving cars will never kill you
ak0ya_: coffin right now!
nejintejag: @no_g then storys can't be true.
bichid69: depression
Lizardan: @georgehotz do you support UBI?
ak0ya_: that will also preserve your skin
robodemia: $TERMINAL
ak0ya_: no spf
IBaydenI: @georgehotz do you look at dying as a bad thing?
gigafact: we have very limited time.
ionelaipatioaei: life is meaningless
not_Awful: right
justenpassant: i disagree; in this particular situation, if you assess the risk, the worst case scenario of catching the virus with an rt of 1.5 right now and passing it along offsets the benefits of 1 protest
DeeboMC: @eldac_kno What about wolfram, I missed that
not_Awful: dont know about that
synthetic11000: Do you think that there are any situations where humans acting in self interest is bad for the overall?
yungdeli_: isn't super weird how simsons predict a lot of our future
mattdougherty22: what do you think of effective altruism?
Inoram: dying could kill you
flexxor: Whats good man
eldac_kno: i missed that too, he kinda skipped it
Penguino138: Corona logic: Self driving car killed someone, so we should all stop driving
waterpaste: yes you do
enlightenedgambino: how can something every living thing has to experience, be a bad thing?
Vrookems: @Inoram bruh since when
nejintejag: @no_g you can always find a interpretation that contradicts your current one.
csal90: have you read any interesting books lately?
DeeboMC: @yungdeli_ I would say yes, but I doubt he would
Tuhafadam: it is a pandamic because of that every body stays home
mangoxavier: @georgehotz chompsky recently said if drumph is still in office our earth will die
Repunk: do you think america will be able to come out of this mess without a complete or even a partial constitutional reform?
mayaeiouy: from a cost benefit perspective I don’t see what I gain by not staying inside for a few weeks
knilecrack: what do you think abou tthis: https://medium.com/@sudhakar.dharmaraju/goodbye-linux-the-next-os-317801a5c0ba
masters8: Why does it mattter their age? You ageist?
ak0ya_: baseball games are boring
waterpaste: imagine during pandemic go to visit a day of liberty
yungtoad1: I'm gunna need verifiable evidence that someone got stabbed by a Phillies fan
nejintejag: @ionelaipatioaei meaning is subjective.
Vrookems: the sad truth: covid kills old people who were already dying
Tuhafadam: maybe you wont be ill you can cary on other people
Lizardan: Do you support UBI?
l1ght5p33d: SUE THE VIRUS ITS AGEIST !!!!
fireposeidoncx: @georgehotz must read books?
masters8: Yeah, so fuck the old, right?
tsparkles: you can still spread the virus to old people
robodemia: $TERMINAL
garydsmith1: BUSINESS INSIDER???????
gaocaandra: the point is to stay away from old people
eldac_kno: sad he won't talk wolfram physics
J3rwin: takes 2s
mangoxavier: Lol
0xatul: LUL
lala_style: LUL
Izimoney92100: LuL
Lefer_: LUL
jamesquinten: PepeLaugh
logi6000: looking into my teams
l1ght5p33d: KNIFE FIGHT !!! ok done spamming caps .. so fun
mangoxavier: The fucking eagles man
Penguino138: dotsHappy
0xatul: KevinTurtle
DeeboMC: Verification ftw
masters8: george is such a meme
braininavatt: 4Head
mangoxavier: Check sources
pepelaugh0: KEKW
Izimoney92100: @mangoxavier I hate the fuckin eagles
Lizardan: KEKw
DeeboMC: @mangoxavier Always
justenpassant: hey, we don't use news as a source of data in this stream
logi6000: guess I cant go to a baseball game. I'm a philly fan
eldac_kno: dude hated eagkes
DeeboMC: Bro, that’s Philadelphia in a nutshell
Vrookems: sharpening my knife rn
mangoxavier: Perfect use case.
Sylens__: lmaoo
bichid69: 1111111111111111111111
synthetic11000: Does this guy not give a sh*t about elderly people getting sick?
yungtoad1: honestly good analogy I'm not afraid of covid anymore
Izimoney92100: Kreygasm
mangoxavier: The Dude has left the chat.
eldac_kno: i am more of a doobie brothers fan
Iceeyz: whats the song
Vrookems: its right there dude
worraaa: but did he finish mcts though
Izimoney92100: where
Dynamic_One: eagles take it easy..
frunkAF: it'd literally on screen
Dynamic_One: LUL
Iceeyz: where
greyoctagon: our matrix is just running pandemic simulations, so stay calm and give the simulation interesting data
LaheyFPS: take it easy (2013 remastered) @Iceeyz
fireposeidoncx: must read books?
logi6000: there was a robot that hitchhiked across Canada and ended in perfect condition. they tried it in America and the robot was jumped in philly. my city right here
chemicalflash: but how many people have been conceived during sports matches ?
HopZe: wait didnt he say news isnt a source of info?
cod4_lightning: this will be muted on youtube
Vrookems: rant good
l1ght5p33d: boomers are alright
mangoxavier: Look with your eyes, not with your mouth.
garydsmith1: but there is a risk of this virus mutating and becoming stronger, and we loose lung capacity
DeeboMC: For the simulation, you play, Joe Walsh - Living a life of illusion
eduardoadf1: LUL
Iceeyz: wheres that
bichid69: what about old people?
mattdougherty22: What do you think of Peter singer and Effective altruism?
mayaeiouy: @hopze only the wrong news Kappa
Newlax: WELOVERANTS
GS540: LOL
Dynamic_One: WutFace
Sylens__: @georgehotz do you watch westworld/
Penguino138: That's mostly how the spanish flu died off. Mutated and became less virulent
LaheyFPS: I'm more scared of philly fans than covid at this point...
abk467: Phillies fan becoming stronger. That is the most terrifying thing I have ever heard.
ze_kel: ze_kel subscribed at Tier 1.
uykusuzw: @georgehotz what u think about starlink?
garydsmith1: what about the reduced lung capacity
synthetic11000: Do you believe that it ever makes sense to act outside of your own self interest?
logi6000: @laheyfps why you scared we just jump hitchhiking robots
bichid69: what about the vulnerable?
adykaaa: @georgehotz Hello George, im a big fan man ! :) Do you suggest learning Java or C#? Which one is more futureproof? I was thinking about Java because you can develop android apps with it as well
sakshambhutani2001: also Kim's dead
garydsmith1: but do you want to get lung problems?
joseanavarrom: What about our families George?
l1ght5p33d: @synthetic11000 temporarily yes overall no
DeeboMC: Asymptotic Phillies fans
bichid69: what about your dick?
garydsmith1: helping people feels good, that's why we help people
cod4_lightning: what if you die of coronavirus?
HopZe: why is it all about me? why not about other living poeple
mangoxavier: Kim is allegedly many things right now. All unverified.
altic: but it is self interest to act out of it LULdoes it make sense
DeeboMC: A symptomatic*
logi6000: you know what's scary. philly fans with covid
nejintejag: What is the self.
mattdougherty22: why care more about family than future descendants that could hack simulation?
webuser011: any thoughts on upcoming crew dragon flight next month?
zenderbeg: LUL
her3hero: famous last words LUL
dr_set: Yes, this guys work proves matematically the biological strategic reason behind altruism: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_R._Price
DeeboMC: @logi6000 Lol that’s what I was getting st
gaocaandra: when the media gets you i will testify against you
eldac_kno: you can't have agency without self interest
synthetic11000: Recommend a good quarantine book?
mattdougherty22: Did you already discuss gates foundation and wHO hack?
mayaeiouy: LUL
robodemia: $TERMINAL
Penguino138: It does feel like Corona was a test of fear
cod4_lightning: go merry someone before you die
gaocaandra: i'll tell them you instructed us to kill old people
mangoxavier: What if we are all the same consciousness and when we die we just live another life in the sim until we learn enough to complete the sim?
l1ght5p33d: @eldac_kno yes you can
justenpassant: if fear wasn't a "feature" of living being, the world would've been so much different
kaksoispistedeh: billg is a scam
ionelaipatioaei: do you think that kim is dead?
Lefer_: I care about what George has to say :)
Artara_: you should hack Gates
garydsmith1: you only help people because it makes us feel better about ourselfs
synthetic11000: If you didn't have a job/company, what way would you make money?
fireposeidoncx: Why do u trust Business insider?
bichid69: its 10% for old people? should they be dead?
justenpassant: if fear wasn't a "feature" of living being, the world would've been so much different. imagine there was no fear. you wouldn't be scared of dying, of jail, of poverty, of pain
DeeboMC: Gates has been making himself way less credible throughout all this.
garydsmith1: that's business insider chart - bad
logi6000: everyone fucking drawin on my phillies
sakshambhutani2001: How do you trust this chart?
qube_si: This. is. wrong.
mattdougherty22: https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2020/04/21/nearly-25000-email-addresses-passwords-allegedly-nih-who-gates-foundation-are-dumped-online/
gaocaandra: isn't there, deep down, a common human goal?
mayaeiouy: that’s just cdc data in that chart KKona
eldac_kno: kim was just a puppet in hands of military and higher ups of party, nothing will change
gaocaandra: selfishness is not the evolutionary defsult
Happykillmoor: no new cases if you dont test
joseanavarrom: I don't know if you would think the same way if you lived in a city that actually had it's health capacity maxed out, and you had to go into a hospital for something not related to covid
mangoxavier: Make yourself happy and bring joy. That’s all you need to do.
her3hero: I'm afraid for my parents and grandparents.
l1ght5p33d: @eldac_kno you can have agency with more external interest than self interest, but you're right you need some small amount self interest defined as knowledge and will to take an action
cod4_lightning: have you watched this: https://youtu.be/6Af6b_wyiwI
hichm19956: Hello do you find protéine ?
gigafact: is CDC good?
justenpassant: if fear wasn't a "feature" of living beings, the world would've been so much different. imagine there was no fear. you wouldn't be scared of dying, of jail, of poverty, of pain. chaos
nejintejag: @georgehotz What is intelligence?
Rocky_88: I missed it, what's the overall stance being debated here?
mayaeiouy: @joseanavarrom I’m in nyc and I’m more scared of that than covid
Rocky_88: or "debated" w/e
zenderbeg: Most of the deaths are caused by different diseases, but they all say that COVID was the cause..
Vrookems: oh im gonna use that
l1ght5p33d: Stalin was 1337
synthetic11000: Yeah, but those death probabilities assume the denominator is only those tested.
justenpassant: stallin was smart though
DeeboMC: You anyone know that applied for Scorpion (Computer Services)? 😂
mangoxavier: Ppl acting like we should click links in this Chan... cmonBruh
phrixus_bro: ty big yud
eldac_kno: do you think if kids were introduced to basic of set theory and basic logic, people would grow up less stupid
garydsmith1: do you think privercy is dead?
cod4_lightning: bill gates talked about corona five years ago https://youtu.be/6Af6b_wyiwI
nejintejag: If a liberal person defines stupidity conservatism will seam stupid.
undefined_kek: hi from russia
not_Awful: what philosophy is your strategy to truth?
joseanavarrom: I don't know if you would think the same way if you lived in a city that actually had it's health capacity maxed out, and you had to go into a hospital for something not related to covid
bichid69: nothing is real
2sin54: define less stupid lol
Artara_: most kids don't even get shit that's easier
DeeboMC: What’s that title?
powerofpickle: We need critical thinking classes
gaocaandra: you can become less dangerously stupid
georgehotz: https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/qNZM3EGoE5ZeMdCRt/reversed-stupidity-is-not-intelligence
gaocaandra: if you are educated
justenpassant: I had a logic course in mathematics in highschool, and it helped me much in my life since.
foti_kasparov: We need asian breeds
joseanavarrom: The vast majority of the US doesn't care to overcome stupidity
mangoxavier: Yes. The journey.
white_rose: this was fun
calcmath: how was the protest?
bottonresult: !uptime
michaelmaier007: hello
ogrockefeller: father
phennessey: Did the protein get folded yet?
ogrockefeller: Dad Hotz
cronograf: No
ogrockefeller: Hit a dab for us?
robonhansonem: Still CartPole?
optimizely: It’s so good to see you george
J3rwin: @georgehotz loving the streams man. Have a good day!
l1ght5p33d: yeeeaeaaaa
michaelmaier007: yeah thats why you can write fych whatever @fychvhvjh
ay33x: PogChamp
masters8: A burrito with french fries??
Slaboday: is this a rerun lol
BlueSeamoose: We back
l1ght5p33d: count indexes on back propagation !!!
ogrockefeller: Sir Dab alot
kisspapa: have you ever played with googles tts voice creator
prez7: burrito
DeeboMC: Good combo tbh
deepfrieddeals: Beaches are overrated
megaultraok: yay you didn't get arrested
megaultraok: more code
ay33x: Have you ever thought making a big game ? @ger
ay33x: @georgehotz
cronograf: Linux
calcmath: are we going to fix the MCTS?
shadowdream1245: MacOS imo
linuxtak: Thanks you for this live session. I loved your chat with Lex Fridman and your approach in Comma.ai
calcmath: debug tools?
Bloodswordz88: Hail brethren
DeeboMC: Hail nigga
wainemier: why you writing this?
Bloodswordz88: HahaThisisfine
1ntegral_: ban hellooooo
ay33x: LUL
robonhansonem: What is this?
ak0ya_: how was the protest?
ambush1g: hotzz you make me motivated to program thank you maaannnnnnnn
calcmath: he dint go
DeeboMC: Lol I’m ok but point taken
eeXecute: :)
id7me_: Did you make annoying text?
robonhansonem: K
T3chHS: can subscribers ask what is today's project? (if so, what are you doing?)
phennessey: Did you say pong?
shadowdream1245: Make an ASMR video 👀👀
calcmath: and gave a lion king quote as the reason
l1ght5p33d: we want continuouser
robonhansonem: He is explaining it right noe#w.
robonhansonem: *now
michaelmaier007: turning into an asmr video.
phennessey: Translucent terminal FTW
robonhansonem: Nah. Opaque.
l1ght5p33d: zero or one is boring
ay33x: PogChamp This my first time catching you live on Twitch, always watched you on YouTube
shadowdream1245: Translucent gang
girtss3: Did this just start?
Santiago_LHC: Hello there
shadowdream1245: Yeah like 2 mins ago
LazerActual: you are an extremely talented human George
moamennasser2211: ur insaaaane bruh
THX1342: is muzero.model his own library?
DeeboMC: Zero AND one 😱
robonhansonem: He is aware of his gifts.
kisspapa: so is this a chess thing or something
wainemier: is this your job to wtiye this or you want to?
RexRothx: does he tab or space indents?
DeeboMC: Lol got emmmm
hurzg: Zeros and Ones are like the subs only mode in this chat :)
DeeboMC: ☝🏽
robonhansonem: I am a zero
mhammad123: Im back
DeeboMC: I’m a qubit
michaelmaier007: 🅘🅢 🅣🅗🅐🅣 🅐 🅜🅔🅒🅗🅐🅝🅘🅒🅐🅛 🅚🅔🅨🅑🅞🅐🅡🅓 ?
THX1342: billy corgan wants to speak to you @robonhansonem
mattaculer: I can't even webcrawl grubhub
LazerActual: safe to say i have absolutely no idea what is happening right now
l1ght5p33d: WTF\
DeeboMC: I grok tf outta this boi
mashafique: game dev stream PogChamp
l1ght5p33d: best game ever
michaelmaier007: wednesday tuesday friday?@l1ght5p33d
cefdsahg: Hi bro what r u doing
InfiniteReddit: morning from aus
THX1342: are you using this https://github.com/johan-gras/MuZero ?
DeeboMC: Bottom of the morn’ to yeh breh
calcmath: isnt this too simple to debug the issues?
LazerActual: please make matrix code run across the ecreen and say "im in" just like the movies 😂
axx88: What is this editor?
michaelmaier007: it's freaking midnight in germany....
gigafact: hello everyone
DeeboMC: @lazeractual Hell yea 😎
robonhansonem: robonhansonem subscribed at Tier 1.
sr______: do u know rtx voice , its AI is mind blowing
km_404: hey george what's up
michaelmaier007: the ceiling
aar0npham: how was the protest?
gigafact: ^
DeeboMC: He didn’t go lol
joseanavarrom: That burrito is making us hungry
DeeboMC: Watched from YouTube
DeeboMC: Boss move
aar0npham: make sense
robonhansonem: Is he using Vim keybindings in his browser?
gaocaandra: george for president
Santiago_LHC: Lazy activism is the best activism.
shieeeeeeeeet: what env/simulation is he testing his muzero implementation in?
l1ght5p33d: I surfed today
l1ght5p33d: first day beaches open
DeeboMC: Speaking them big facts now
LazerActual: social distancing
Bloodswordz88: watch out for the sharks
nickcorso_: Hey man, I know absolutely nothing about this stuff but just wanted to say I graduated Bergen County Academies in 2017 and thought it was cool that you were an alumni
aar0npham: when trump becomes president =)
michaelmaier007: and i surfifed today :/@l1ght5p33d
l1ght5p33d: orange county
robonhansonem: Exit over voice.
jontowtruck: bergen community college in teh house!
ferraz42: which timezone are you in?
dr_set: its freedom for them, if you are LGBT, or a Jew or Muslin, etc, they don't mean freedom for you
nickcorso_: It’s going to shit, still a great school but crazy rules and I feel like they’re turning down smarter students for diversity
mik12f4: when did you leave NJ
DeeboMC: @nickcorso_ Lucky cunt 😆
Riqour: Do you need a double major in math and cs to work in ai?
ahahaitslit: goddamn ideologues
nickcorso_: @deebomc What do you mean?
shadowdream1245: Why does he use Chromium over Chrome?
gaocaandra: you dont need a degree to google things
grahamstephan420: I think he’s using ungoogled chromium
SHAVEYY_: @shadowdream1245 no google
shadowdream1245: oh
DeeboMC: @nickcorso_ You lived where good education was availed to you
Bloodswordz88: #Learntocode = #Learntogoogle
joseanavarrom: Fuck polarization and bipartisanship
thehisoka007: what time is it ?
eldac_kno: stick balancing reminds me of Kapitza pendulum
nickcorso_: @deebomc That’s true but it’s also really really hard to get into . I think the acceptance rate is below 10
achamorro008: how much is the subscription ?
grahamstephan420: $50
DeeboMC: @nickcorso_ And, therefore, access to peers
gaocaandra: i know a guy that can get you in fo 40 bucks
SOmedude456: yo george are you religious or ethnically related to a religion?
l1ght5p33d: we want benchmarks
DeeboMC: @gaocaandra Lmao
michaelmaier007: @somedude456 does that matter?
grahamstephan420: @georgehotz If I subscribe will you still ban me?
achamorro008: 50/month ?
robonhansonem: George worships the future brain emulation he will become.
grahamstephan420: No
grahamstephan420: Per week
DeeboMC: @nickcorso_ That’s also the exact point tho bro
SOmedude456: @michaelmaier007 no, I'm just askin a question?
gordon1337: how do you wish someone tasty meal in english?
nickcorso_: Anybody in here an app developer? I have an idea for a social media add-on that I’d like to build but I’m not great with coding
shokoo: @SOmedude456 how dare you LUL / s
rhombicosi: Turing test for AI is to play apex
girtss3: Will you post the last streams on YouTube?
robonhansonem: Learn to fo code it yourself.
eldac_kno: nickorso just lol
robonhansonem: *to
nickcorso_: Where’s the best place to learn how to code apps?
DeeboMC: @rhombicosi Not really
shadowdream1245: Doctors: You can't learn how to be a doctor by googling things online Programmers:
mashafique: @nickcorso_ by googling what you want to learn
2ndsll: whats the game?
gordon1337: asmr
eldac_kno: balancing the stick
ak0ya_: follower
SHAVEYY_: just make it play the game 4Head
gigafact: @girtss3 it will be posted but we hit a technical wall (youtube time limits and blocking copyright song) so you can't even play video... we are working on it
grahamstephan420: Hey I got this great app idea. It’s actually physically impossible due to limitations with current web APIs and available computing power, but that shouldn’t matter. Anyways, you do all the work and we split profits 50/50. Sound good man?
ak0ya_: it should be able to repeat the number 0 or 1
michaelmaier007: gta 6 releasing early i see
rhombicosi: @deebomc ok. to play at least like hal
gaocaandra: ajjajajaja i'd ban you if i could @nickcorso_
nickcorso_: @mashafique Thanks for the insight, never would’ve thought of that
DeeboMC: @nickcorso_ *went to Bergen* *asks that question in here* 🤨
MoProject: @nickcorso_ there are free courses organized by harverd on developing apps, you can check those
SHAVEYY_: internet but bitcoin 4Head
broadsw0rd: ill develop your app for free with no credit
nickcorso_: You guys aren’t very understanding of people that lack technical knowledge.
bored_spagetti: IM FINALLY LIVE FOR THE FIRST TIME
shadowdream1245: lmfao
mashafique: @nickcorso_ Everyone in here will tell you the same thing I'm guessing
bored_spagetti: what project are we doing ?
nickcorso_: I went to school in the academy of business and finance lmao
gaocaandra: Mcprogramming
shieeeeeeeeet: @nickcorso_ you don't need technical knowledge to know how to learn things
J3rwin: D:
wainemier: omg
robonhansonem: @nickcorso_ Pay someone to do it or do it yourself. No one wants to go halfsies on your idea.
nickcorso_: I figured I’d try to shortcut some steps and get some advice on the first step of the process
SHAVEYY_: how do I write a app that has porn on it?
l1ght5p33d: Look at Flutter it's really good for mobile I wrote an instagram clone with it
achamorro008: jajaja
jagger_rsw: Follow RIchard Feynman, learn what he did, and you are a moron :)
gaocaandra: ionic framework easy enough flutter is pretty
gigafact: sometimes I think people just ask to troll you
eldac_kno: is it still stick game?
MoProject: @you can also go on fiverr and search someone
girtss3: @gigafact Appreciate the response, thank you.
nickcorso_: Seems like the first step is just to google and figure it out. Now I know that, thanks for the help
calcmath: soory went to get tea, did it work on follower?
fullcind: how do i make an app to get me laid
shadowdream1245: george pls teach me the beep boop computers
gaocaandra: nphard problem
ak0ya_: no it did not
shieeeeeeeeet: @georgehotz maybe see if alphazero works on this game?
SHAVEYY_: how 2 program in assembloy halp geo!!
grekler3: chat, is using vpn gonna fully affect from what country the views and followers come from , in yt or instagram ?
l1ght5p33d: @gaocaandra what do you mean pretty
eldac_kno: highly unlikely
mashafique: We jammin' bois
rickoftheroot: pepeD
gaocaandra: pretty nice
hayewood: PepeJAM
michaelmaier007: i hope this won't end up in that tiktok bs
ghassane20a: why aren't you verified yet
T3chHS: @nickcorso_ you can always find people to guide you and give steping stones, but independent of your background, everyone can code anything. The internet is a fucking endless source of all kinds of information
grahamstephan420: Defeat Go using the golang implementation of MuZero
dudvdx: what are yeh doin now
l1ght5p33d: @gaocaandra it's probably easier than react
lucemferro_: im afraid to ask....
QuantumDota: still waiting for that Tesla sentury mode open source edition ;)
gaocaandra: coding react right now for a work thingie
andrewispower: explain what are you doing
nickcorso_: Who was your favorite teacher at BCA? Was Scott Lang there back then?
mirceau: George are you Fasting for Ramadan?
calcmath: he is testing his muzero implemntation on a simple game called follower
robonhansonem: Test
DeeboMC: @mirceau 😂😭
routerkicker: how was the protest george`? Did you meet some cool people?
VANRA: i dont think there are stupid questions
Lana_Lux: Yes.
Xaktar: yes
beastars_is_best_anime: yes moon2JR
eldac_kno: yes
rickoftheroot: LUL
mashafique: yes :)
ghassane20a: yes
grekler3: no, 13
beastars_is_best_anime: I LOVE ECK BAK moon2JR
Iluvmf: yes
Creamy_Goodness_: im emotionally 12.
cheese_wizzy: whats your iq @hayewood
megaultraok: lol no
Lana_Lux: It's not?
Xaktar: 12 and a half
ad5k: Fuck 12
abk467: probably
cheese_wizzy: whats your iq @georgehotz
lucemferro_: hey @georgehotz i got a job as a software tester, what are some tips for someone like me with no prior experience with programming? Also i have a math degree.
Santiago_LHC: Is it timeout time?
girtss3: @Creamy_Goodness_ :D
grahamstephan420: Pride100
Ch4oticAU: @Lana_Lux yo! Nice work on Ludum dare
shadowdream1245: teach me the computer beep boop george SirMad
DeeboMC: Yea, fuck 12
gaocaandra: is this a serious channel?
VANRA: my iq is higher than hotz
SHAVEYY_: @cheese_wizzy 392
eldac_kno: 12 year old army
mashafique: Mine are already out :)
andrewispower: make it 69+
Lana_Lux: @Ch4oticAU thanks :)
jagger_rsw: We're helping you to become more resistant to distraction temptations
T3chHS: yes, that's how it works
risky_banana: still cant show tiddys :(
l1ght5p33d: 30 + and ill leave
abk467: LUL im not sure that's what that means
Creamy_Goodness_: u cant show boobies
basecamp27: That would be helpful or just 18 to comment
DeeboMC: 18+ ftw
sr______: lol
robonhansonem: Good for you. Mine is so low it hurts to think.
l1ght5p33d: take one for the chat
grahamstephan420: Yes
Ch4oticAU: Should start body painting Geo lol
michaelmaier007: kids escape is twitch. not going to school they end up in twitch
grahamstephan420: I’m 13
whoishenry123: what cpu and gpu are you using?
rickoftheroot: SeemsGood
Creamy_Goodness_: u cant even show man boobies
Santiago_LHC: 12 year olds, raise your hand
mirceau: Not 12 here
SHAVEYY_: @whoishenry123 some macbook cpu
Digital_donger: twitch chat is a special place FeelsGoodMan
grahamstephan420: 🖕
shadowdream1245: Do 12yos know who geohot is?
cheese_wizzy: @SHAVEYY_ any idea how to raise my iq to that level ?
michaelmaier007: 12 year olds are playing fortnite right now
calcmath: this is not even MCTS, you have it commented
dudvdx: @georgehotz you're a good lad. keep up the good work
whoishenry123: @SHAVEYY_ ahh thx
grahamstephan420: Show your dick or keep it under 18
DeeboMC: 12 inches? 🙋🏽♂️
l1ght5p33d: dooppeee
QuantumDota: @georgehotz I have a private repo with a openai gym + cracked game version for lethal league blaze, a real-time fighting game, I've added you to the repo, would love to see if u could solve it
SHAVEYY_: @cheese_wizzy lots of book
girtss3: Does twitch not have analytics that show what is the average viewers age?
calcmath: @georgehotz you are testing naive search right now not MCTS
l1ght5p33d: wai what no
archiveutility: I'm twelve... twelve inches in your mom
jagger_rsw: ha.. new episode of westworld is up
cheese_wizzy: how many book have you read @georgehotz ?
gaocaandra: plis ban him
hurzg: what game does it try to solve atm?
gaocaandra: all games
Digital_donger: B) what ad?
l1ght5p33d: u make 10 y no better
Lana_Lux: lol no
num_air: WTF BRO
abk467: LUL LUL
Andremm2: nope
erlsek: no
mashafique: nope
SHAVEYY_: B) what ad?
jagger_rsw: nope,
xPolarDreamz: HI
dudvdx: no ads for subs
T3chHS: LUL
num_air: DAFUK AM I WATCHING
DeeboMC: Not subs
gaocaandra: NO GEORGE DON'T
l1ght5p33d: cmd + b
eldac_kno: we just need mods
xPolarDreamz: someone has been uploading your twitch vods to youtube
DeeboMC: Non-subs prolly are
l1ght5p33d: (cmd + b) ^2
T3chHS: be careful of leaks
gaocaandra: don't sell out to the man
T3chHS: yr
T3chHS: ye*
grekler3: oh shit, i dont have ad block enabled, i just gave you money PogChamp
Lana_Lux: I don't think it tells you the age
gaocaandra: wid dem adds
DeeboMC: Lol i remember that
Digital_donger: streamer career PogChamp 📈
DeeboMC: Told you
num_air: COVID streams were great !!!
jagger_rsw: make a poll
qlutoo: im 12 and what is this
l1ght5p33d: (cmd+b)^infinity
eldac_kno: i dont think twitch has age in profile
aar0npham: running ads every 30 sec
bored_spagetti: lol imagine watching a millionaire's ad
mashafique: Only subs don't see ads I believe
shieeeeeeeeet: shieeeeeeeeet subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
cars1n: Damn. He lookin thicc
limnick: hows the covid research coming george? I havent been here in a while but this looks neat
Killeraing: adblock is a thing tho
jagger_rsw: or those who have twitch turbo - an option
NatePh_07: in the Channel and Videos tab in Settings there is a Mature Content option
DeeboMC: Did yal adds? .. I wouldn’t know 😂😂
aar0npham: so u better give george money
andrewispower: why u so sexy tho
cockwizard69: :)
DeeboMC: See^
Xaktar: FeelsBadMan
donald3767: What’s muzero? I’m just tuning in
xPolarDreamz: ebegging
rickoftheroot: FeelsBadMan
DeeboMC: Elitism boii
robonhansonem: Google it.
Creamy_Goodness_: til george hates children
bismarckbamfo: No politics talks.
shieeeeeeeeet: @georgehotz do you care more about higher tier subscribers?
SHAVEYY_: LUL
sight_0: LUL
dudvdx: politics is meaningless
robonhansonem: Says Bismarck.
rickoftheroot: LUL
calcmath: you are not making any sense
WiseSwift: Can you visualize that in the notebook
Creamy_Goodness_: my mom said thinking is bad
WiseSwift: I don’t get it
ad5k: I am a liar
bored_spagetti: george i need a girlfriend what do i do ?
jagger_rsw: So, if politician says that a statement cannot be at the same time 'true' or 'false', I should check if 'statement can be at the same time true and false' and since it's not, then such politician is saying a lie?
Creamy_Goodness_: thinking is the tool of the devil
gaocaandra: learn to code
robonhansonem: Be worthy.
michaelmaier007: ｉ ｈａｔｅ ｐｏｌ ｉ ｔｉ ｃｓ
eldac_kno: not me dont care about not mine non subscribers
l1ght5p33d: can we do pygame snek with muzero w profile benchmark
l1ght5p33d: i dont want to miss the stream
Creamy_Goodness_: why does george hate children
bored_spagetti: what are we building now ?
T3chHS: just run function "getGUD ( )" LUL
robonhansonem: We care about adults.
DeeboMC: @t3chhs 😆
bismarckbamfo: What about non subs helping make the segnet better?
onu4r: yo
robonhansonem: Simple game to debug Mu.
mashafique: mashafique subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak! we out here
lukexfisher: how many Doge coin do you own?
num_air: lol
t00big2fl4il: yo what up?
robonhansonem: Doge is a banned subject.
gabryelportuga: where does george live?
eldac_kno: where are the mods
robonhansonem: No mods.
DeeboMC: Run “getBITXHES ( )”
michaelmaier007: @gabryelportuga planet earth probably
onu4r: Georgeyboi
gabryelportuga: @michaelmaier007 thanks
Shelledlizard4: hey
girtss3: I can't find a way to see demographics on twitch, however, we could create an online poll right now, but then again we would have to trust that people wouldn't troll.
Bootstraps: its a genius
eldac_kno: chat poll on twitch is the worst idea
l1ght5p33d: "q values"
DeeboMC: @girtss3 And why would you trust people to disqualify themselves 🤨🤨😂
calcmath: so model of env is learnt
andrewispower: can you sign my steam profile
Lana_Lux: is this for a bigger project?
DeeboMC: Google info is already unreliable as well.. unless you’re an idiot
girtss3: We are learning things here
limnick: curious, george
guccibruf: 🐛
calcmath: exploration reward?
Lana_Lux: i guess learning is a project
andrewispower: george is a very balcanic name ,maybe you'll want to eat some cabage rolls sometime
Jehhred: George is doing this for shits and gigs
l1ght5p33d: one does not simply "look at the training data"
limnick: show fitness function george!!
Lana_Lux: @Jehhred good enough reason to do it :)
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d 😆
andrewispower: i farted
TeckelDev01: hey
andrewispower: sry
gigafact: @Lana_Lux George is normally just exploring random projects for fun. Check his github.com/geohot for more info
l1ght5p33d: @deebomc WHILE THE NETS RUNNING
Lana_Lux: @gigafact thanks :)
DeeboMC: 🤣🥳
eldac_kno: would be curious to see explore ue4
anguscupcake: opengl is fun
l1ght5p33d: we're gonna need another GPU
DeeboMC: Gonna need a bigger server farm
zup_zup: hey @georgehotz big fan
andrewispower: my dream was always to become a pizza maker
DeeboMC: Get old Macdonald on the horn
manouchehri: Why is there a tiny twin bed in your living room?
l1ght5p33d: pizza is probably the top 3 foods
limnick: @manouchehri hes in SF that's just his room LUL
DeeboMC: I think he’s in SD now
manouchehri: @limnick that looks way too small for two people
andrewispower: georgyboi are you living in a nutshell my men
bovine_shield: Heyyyyy, the protester is back!! <3
DeeboMC: South Dakota, California
calcmath: value of state should converge to 1 for both staes right?
limnick: @deebomc ahh ok
l1ght5p33d: put in sublime
genieyou1: Love you bro
calcmath: or is it iinfinite
calcmath: well there is dsciounting
calcmath: perfect policy is to follow, ehich means every step gives you 1 reward
DeeboMC: White dread heads abound
t00big2fl4il: An absorbing state is a state that, once entered, cannot be left
DeeboMC: Sounds like Florida
DeeboMC: For old people
andrewispower: I'm a boomer
DeeboMC: Ahh.. my apologies then
Major_Spicy: Hows the progress going? @georgehotz
calcmath: trsnsition of states is completely random right?
info303: just increase the learning rate :D
aar0npham: @info303 we don't want overfitting
DeeboMC: Release the noops
chai_wala: !uptime
info303: does overfitting actually matter much in this case?
DeeboMC: Game comes from within
routerkicker: what are ht and gt?
Xaotic: Guys does he only have a mbp 13 ? and runs a 5k monitor on that?
Rezery: Hi george hows it going?
anguscupcake: 16" bro
bismarckbamfo: So what's thr bug?
DiiCE3: !live
calcmath: later steps got a reward
Xaotic: @anguscupcake is this 16'' now?
DiiCE3: how long have you been live? @georgehotz
execrationtv: uptime!
calcmath: needs more steps to converge
DeeboMC: Approximately 30 years i believe
chunks111: What is a tree-based search?
girtss3: @DiiCE3 Almost an hour
12million_dollar_mobileye: 12million_dollar_mobileye subscribed at Tier 1.
bovine_shield: I always knew I was stupid, but you make me feel like an amoeba.
l1ght5p33d: view source
DeeboMC: Mobileye in the building ☝🏽🚨🚨
polysoulz_: interesting PogChamp
zup_zup: 'why doesn't it work' - story of my life
thepeanufamily: do you see eye floaters? / have vision problems?
歡迎羽球單挑: what
t00big2fl4il: what would working look like?
thelastkek: have you tried putting it in rice
roflcho: Putin?
t00big2fl4il: I missed that damn my speakers
Santiago_LHC: I'm reinstating Vjasal, who promised to sub.
t00big2fl4il: very simple game. It would work by guessing,,,,
DeeboMC: It says you went offline on my phone but I’m still watching on my laptop. Did someone ban me, or is this a glitch?
calcmath: it needs to learn that future states cant be affected by actions, that is not that easy, its basically a skinner box and ur muzero is getting addicted
ofaas: :(
wainemier: you shoudnt put the replay videos only for subscriber I
Vjasal: Vjasal subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! sorry for beeing rude yesterday
St47ik: @wainemier they are on youtube anyway
DeeboMC: @wainemier I’m a sub but I agree with this
wainemier: wainemier: you shoudnt put the replay videos only for subscriber only we wanted to watch it
DeeboMC: @st47ik Not always
t00big2fl4il: absorbing points in this simple game?
bloopsterr: @wainemier most of them go on youtube the next day anyway
t00big2fl4il: absorbing states
ivche1337: Hello geohotz! I was wondering if you have ever heard of Voice stress analysis or If you have done any projects on it. If yes, any resources?
brisingr1031: george really putting in the work for this project
St47ik: nah it's just a fun project :D
eeXecute: a switch
gigafact: if it does not work George will put more work into it. other people will give up but not George
DeeboMC: I’m sure he’s heard of it. Anybody who’s watched TV/movies surely has
bismarckbamfo: Check the discount function.
brisingr1031: go george!
Penguino138: And we're back!
calcmath: lower discount value
calcmath: so that ignores future rewards more easily
DeeboMC: im go take a shower. good action
St47ik: high value
DeeboMC: lol
l1ght5p33d: we learned muzero is bad at easy games
brisingr1031: @12million_dollar_mobileye its convenient tho
calcmath: just try MCTS anyway?
SHAVEYY_: @12million_dollar_mobileye its good for learning
St47ik: bugs maybe
Creamy_Goodness_: this code is so.... erotic
ofaas: what do you use 12 million
St47ik: WutFace
routerkicker: please don't talk about text editors. George is gonna get mad again.
brisingr1031: i think talking about keyboards is worse than text editors, he might just perma ban you
St47ik: Stop NotLikeThis you're a sub
brisingr1031: ratirlSad
bismarckbamfo: What about the L2 regularization?
shr1ftyy: lol
anguscupcake: lol
Major_Spicy: 4Head Half of chat just gone
HedgeOnTwitch: haha
shr1ftyy: wiped
0R4NG3: permad KEKW
dantusqq: na
thickbordiga: no
brisingr1031: no they dont
samwilliamson7: What’s good george
soldierheadsmite: nice one
TheKoreanZombi: No money back just a life lesson.
thickbordiga: they also can't even see the chat after they get banned
soldierheadsmite: he fucked himself
gaocaandra: NICE BOAT BRO
Major_Spicy: It's just 5 dollars 4Head If he subbed to Hotz he can afford it easily
St47ik: Comfy LUL
gaocaandra: yea
gaocaandra: stick it
gaocaandra: stick that velcro
Lana_Lux: TAPE IT
gaocaandra: you dirty sailor
ofaas: this is how i install my curtains
St47ik: @Lana_Lux HeyGuys
TheKoreanZombi: So this is how sailing works
gaocaandra: that tape
Lana_Lux: @St47ik hey!
Vjasal: more tape
gaocaandra: was a good metaphore
risky_banana: this is what happens when you live on a boat, you lose your mind
gaocaandra: for this proyect
chunks____: a lot more tape involved then id thought
gaocaandra: tape is fucking great
badpartyhouse: badpartyhouse subscribed with Twitch Prime.
LiveCustoms: George what was your net worth at 21?
shr1ftyy: just remove the fucking lamp omegalul
l1ght5p33d: tape engineering
Penguino138: GeoYacht
gaocaandra: it was fun
l1ght5p33d: not eco freindly
Major_Spicy: I mad that sailing channel :)
St47ik: nice snacc
samwilliamson7: It was great
wycks: used to be really into sailing youtube , now im not
GS540: any phillys fans at the beach protest?
chunks____: maybe the gradient function needs more tape
TheBlackzillian: !uptime
LiveCustoms: As an accountant, what tf is MuZero?
brisingr1031: ratirlGraph
badpartyhouse: Just joined! What are we working on today?
xeeton: sailing + machine learning is a winning combo ngl
wycks: felt like I should be sailing and not watching sailing
Major_Spicy: RatIRL is human trash kiaaREE
Jehhred: Sailing Youtube is nearly on par with Extreme Ironing.. yes, it exists
Penguino138: @LiveCustoms Muzero is complex predictive AI architecture
brisingr1031: @xeeton self-driving boats??
St47ik: it's better than AlphaZero
l1ght5p33d: add logging
Major_Spicy: @brisingr1031 are you here strictly for business?
LiveCustoms: @Penguino138 nice, thanks
l1ght5p33d: not just trying. then theres logs
brisingr1031: ratirlBusiness
l1ght5p33d: no idea
puffnfresh: puffnfresh subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 7 months! I want some more Coq
St47ik: Article for new peeps https://medium.com/applied-data-science/how-to-build-your-own-muzero-in-python-f77d5718061a
brisingr1031: @georgehotz wait so whats the problem?
yungdeli_: @Critical780 no you're confused
TheKoreanZombi: Goodbye sweet prince
Major_Spicy: @Critical780 KEKW
anguscupcake: pwned
Major_Spicy: The bans are almost more entertaining than the stream itself Pog
St47ik: dinner soon
markydothh: Sup George!
markydothh: hey George, can i send you some crypto?
node_storm: give me a good book recommendation and i'll sub
georgehotz: https://www.amazon.com/product-reviews/0833030477/ref=acr_dp_hist_5?ie=UTF8&filterByStar=five_star&reviewerType=all_reviews#reviews-filter-bar
LiveCustoms: The Investors Manifesto is a great book
St47ik: LUL
xeeton: @georgehotz referenced egen's permutation city, I've been reading it and it's good
Penguino138: Did george already talk about the freedom protest?
l1ght5p33d: is this just small random action space
DeadSupra: hello George
l1ght5p33d: does this ever work with any net
l1ght5p33d: do i have to start jupyter now
t00big2fl4il: digital dice computational solutions to practical probability problems PAUL J HAHIN
Jehhred: @forkdb What are you? His mother?
anguscupcake: learning many things is impossible
node_storm: node_storm subscribed at Tier 1.
Major_Spicy: Another one LUL
Riqour: @forkdb rip
stephen422: @forkdb heyyy how did ya get that sweet italics in chat
DeeboMC: back. so fresh and so clean, clean.... What was mobileye talkin about lol
t00big2fl4il: Paul J Nahin
DeeboMC: extreme ironing rips dude
alextodoroki: what was the conclusion for the coronavirus reverse engineering
St47ik: @stephen422 𝙪𝙣𝙞𝙘𝙤𝙙𝙚
Major_Spicy: @alextodoroki im pretty sure he didnt finish it, said it's too hard or sth along those lines
moebe: what r the pros of using jupyter ?
alextodoroki: based
l1ght5p33d: lmao
DeeboMC: mobileye was talkin about nahin? lol
SHAVEYY_: PogChamp
alextodoroki: tfw not sub
Vjasal: hey non subs, what's up
SHAVEYY_: 🚪 👈 non-subs out
Penguino138: Someday the chat will learn
0R4NG3: TriHard 7 in the chat
DeeboMC: but not today..
Riqour: Imagine being a sub TriHard
DeeboMC: im a dom tho so...
risky_banana: ?
fSyLyndon: TriHard
DeeboMC: just a dumb pun lol
TheKoreanZombi: Hard to tell. So many changes
St47ik: discount is higher than before?
TheKoreanZombi: I am talking about from the earlier stream. Too many changes for me to tell.
l1ght5p33d: can't make continuous?
TheKoreanZombi: Did we and the lunar module already?
TheKoreanZombi: *try
Vjasal: teach your code to write better code
WilliamMu6: would you say muzero is better than keras?
Julianhgg: OK
l1ght5p33d: reduce buffer to 3
THX1342: WilliamMu6 isn't that comparing apples and oranges?
THX1342: one is a framework, the other is an algorithm
Julianhgg: !uptime
robonhansonem: If I can get it to work, job?
guinness84: do you drink SD tap wateR?
guinness84: i don't
WilliamMu6: got it
yungdeli_: except in flint Imao
guinness84: LUL
DeeboMC: @georgehotz would you ever consider building simple arduino robot to play around with this shit with, or do u think the lockdown is too close to ending to invest the time into that
routerkicker: us tap water tastes like a swimming pool to me.
mashafique: This chat is so memey at times.
0R4NG3: PogChamp
St47ik: PogChamp
TheKoreanZombi: Nice lander
gaocaandra: o shit
erlsek: PogChamp
DeeboMC: lol ok. well forget about the lockdown aspect
yungdeli_: POG
routerkicker: YES! Progress
Jadess: LOL
ultraolesia: KEK
Jadess: POGGERS
toashh: KEKW
achamorro008: hello form Nicaragua
Jimbo51: Houston we have a problem
mashafique: Progress PogChamp
ivche1337: george, have you ever heard of Voice stress analysis, and if yes any resources for learning more about it?
robonhansonem: Muzero is coming for your job.
THX1342: i haven't followed a lot of these past 2 days but isn't your follower game too 'strict'? one wrong move and the game is over, so the AI doesn't have 'space' to learn
chai_wala: Wish I could learn so fast
robonhansonem: Google, yo.
Th3R3dQu33n: hey, how many Starships is Elon Musk on these days?
THX1342: oh ok... I thought it was working with wrong move == gameover
eeXecute: i give it 4 trys
TheKoreanZombi: There's the old falling lander I love
DeeboMC: do you even hardware anymore?
ultraolesia: rip
adamalex16: homeboy should come over to my house and jailbreak my ps3
St47ik: MuZero supposed to be the "State-of-the-art" LUL
zup_zup: is your chair comfy?
gaocaandra: the more close you see ml the shittier it gets
ultraolesia: @zup_zup his chair looks really uncomfy
gaocaandra: o man
THX1342: is the muzero import your own implementation?
gaocaandra: the cringe
zup_zup: two more weeks?
Lana_Lux: imagine how clumsy the world would be with this as our AI overlords
zup_zup: oh lol
St47ik: LUL
DeeboMC: tumor weaks
lebop: how did you find out about muzero and why is it relevant?
THX1342: from general AI to cartpole AI
THX1342: LUL
FrancescoTommaso: lol
gaocaandra: how sure are you the implementation is correct
DeeboMC: thats why i asked about hardware implementation
gaocaandra: ?
routerkicker: is there muzero samples to download and compare to yours?
Bushfries: can you teach me how to write python code?
THX1342: it's only a matter of designing problems in a cartpole framework
ivche1337: let it find covid vaccine lmao
FrancescoTommaso: maybe it's overfiting
bismarckbamfo: Cartpole solves itself.
St47ik: "MuZero takes the ultimate next step. Not only does MuZero deny itself human strategy to learn from. It isn’t even shown the rules of the game."
lebop: o
Iluvmf: Didn't see all the stream, does the agent start by taking random action with a epsilon type frequency ?
gaocaandra: yeaaa
FrancescoTommaso: is this code going to github?
jeankx23: brbrbr
gaocaandra: it already is
FrancescoTommaso: good
THX1342: alright.. gn
FrancescoTommaso: i will try to improve it
xeeton: you sholud walk through the MCTS
SHAVEYY_: @FrancescoTommaso https://github.com/geohot/ai-notebooks/
FrancescoTommaso: thanks
bismarckbamfo: Will fix Muzero and submit pull request.
goergehotz: goergehotz subscribed at Tier 1.
mashafique: LULW
drdislupo: what is going on exactly?
guinness84: stalker monkaS
aar0npham: did he fix it?
DeeboMC: Eliezer "what a false dichotomy" Yudkowsky
fabaoproo: I'm i big fan of you, from Brazil
g_gWillis: pokeHmm
markydothh: What is the benefit of keeping code in VIM and running in Jupyter?
eDONze: i'm from brazil too kkkkkkkkkkkk
peter35_: clintSuave gentlemen
Th3R3dQu33n: @markydothh easier testing
pwnbase: goergehotz, presadent cumma ai
FrancescoTommaso: I am also from Brazil
olvroger: me too
markydothh: But still have to update code in VIM yea?
eDONze: i can't play football in quarantine so i come to see george
timetrap2e: What’s up georgey
ytazn: My roommate didn’t remember taking a college course on differential equations...
DeeboMC: lol damn thats burnt city... or an assload of edumacation
gaocaandra: i didnt understand what you just did
cod4_lightning: studying for OSCP rn, sup?
gardiyanismet: what is he working on?
loouai: george why do you keep the jupyter default theme
fabaoproo: It is still about covid?
gaocaandra: you assigned p to a ignoring v, to use it to re calculate the state?
3minus2: if i want to start programming/coding, with language should i start with? and what are the differences between them?
ytazn: Oh this is a try random shit measured against some chosen fitness
gaocaandra: WHY?
FrancescoTommaso: is MuZero well suited for this? maybe it's mcts does not have time to explore enough in a short amount of time
gaocaandra: sry caps
SHAVEYY_: @3minus2 the first language I actually learnt stuff in was nodejs
FrancescoTommaso: I was trying to build a bot for generals..io and I had to give up no mcts
FrancescoTommaso: on
ytazn: @gaocaandra because that’s similar to how kids learn
chrispickels: rewrite in rust
SHAVEYY_: I hate nodes syntax though
neilsweb: Somebody was playing too much Mortal Combat when they named this algo
chrispickels: PLEAse rewrite in rust now
loouai: nodejs isnt a language
info303: nodejs is a runtime not a language
raisedbyphantom: is he using ubuntu ?
nsielicki: good evening
routerkicker: YES
ytazn: What’s the measure of fitness?
l1ght5p33d: nooooo
FrancescoTommaso: LOL
yuyaaah: Yes
SHAVEYY_: @raisedbyphantom based
johnpyp: PLEAse rewrite in rust now
l1ght5p33d: push to github
cod4_lightning: what's the point of doing streams about very hard topics that you are only understand?
mburke005: puke
peter35_: 3minus2 i started with C and i liked my path
ytazn: No
xeeton: lol
joseanavarrom: It would hahaha
loouai: broo get a jupyter dark theme plsssssss
ytazn: Wtf is rust
gaocaandra: @ytazn how so
3minus2: @SHAVEYY_ what do you think of python? ive been told its "easy" to learn
l1ght5p33d: im trying to write follower from a blurry screenshot
neilsweb: What chair is that?
nsielicki: any experience with Julia?
bismarckbamfo: Darkmode.
DeeboMC: write that shit in cobol breh
ytazn: @gaocaandra you have some measure of fitness like positive feedback from your parents and you try random shit to trigger that
l1ght5p33d: how u get in pygame always bad shape shape alwayysss whyyyy
robonhansonem: We need a fizz buzz stream.
birkett0011: how do i install pandas
ytazn: That’s how these algorithms work without knowing the rukes
cod4_lightning: I mean what's the % of watchers that actually understand what you are doing?
SHAVEYY_: @3minus2 python is probably the go to for new programmers tbh
chrispickels: put an extra pole in the cart
chrispickels: one pole is too simple
mashafique: I don't think George streams to teach us. From what I remember he said the stream is about talking shit and being somewhat productive LUL
gaocaandra: yeah i understand the whole reward thing, what is confusing me is i thought that was the function that determined which node was visited next
skinnypuppy69: little to none @cod4_lightning
TheKoreanZombi: @cod4_lightning Why are you watching if you don't understand?
neilsweb: I didn't know jack dorsey streamed.
3minus2: hm ok, can you explain a super noob the differences between all these languages?
FrancescoTommaso: is it running a mcts and deciding what to do at everyframe?
chrispickels: one pole is a simpleton's game
gaocaandra: nevermind i'll look at the code later
vHyphy: vHyphy subscribed with Twitch Prime.
ytazn: The only way to understand is try yourself
birkett0011: Have you guys seen any real world applications of RL? not just computer games ect?
vHyphy: My dad loves your shit
cod4_lightning: I mean I watch in the hope of learning more about programming by a professional programmer!
lolzmaster99: @birkett0011 Optimal control theory
info303: @birkett0011 it can be used for stocks, logistics, ton of applications
ytazn: @birkett0011 yeah eventually a car in a novel situation will be able to figure a solution de novo given it doesn’t destroy itself on the process
birkett0011: @lolzmaster99 anything more specific on the simulation side. So far my experience has been dismal for simulation
birkett0011: I work extensively in Anylogic simulaiton and it seem like a perfect match but havent seen any decent applications
vHyphy: How do I share my sub
3minus2: @SHAVEYY_ hm ok, can you explain a super noob the differences between all these languages?
nsielicki: what'd you change in select_child?
gaocaandra: make it rand between 0-1
loouai: @3minus2 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sg4U4r_AgJU&t=1353s
gaocaandra: see what happens
skinnypuppy69: why does my professor tell me to make psuedo code but even george hotz doesnt make pseudo code
gaocaandra: the root has visit count
gaocaandra: in mcts
nsielicki: @skinnypuppy69 because the university education system is about making workers en masse, not making good workers.
cod4_lightning: @skinnypuppy69 cuz he is legend, and your professor is a noob!
chunks____: nah, they dont teach anything about being a good programmer in school
loouai: @nsielicki preach
ytazn: Your professor doesn’t have to write code that people use
gaocaandra: the first time it defaults to the first because uct = infinity for all nodes
skinnypuppy69: geez it was rhetorical lmaoi chill out
birkett0011: Any of you messed around with the #Hash simulation stuff? Seems like good place to apply some of this RL on more complex systems. https://hash.ai/index/search?contentType=Simulation&sort=dateModified
lolzmaster99: Yes
ytazn: Lmao my professors are dumb too
cod4_lightning: I subscribed now I am in the safe zone.
gaocaandra: because n = 0
gaocaandra: the second time the first node will have n = 1
skinnypuppy69: all professors are dumb, youtube is how you learn
gaocaandra: so it will go to the next
ytazn: @skinnypuppy69 true
DeeboMC: Most* professors
guinness84: have u tried gripping the handle differently, your slicing right a bit
ytazn: I prefer to read
skinnypuppy69: i learn by seeing not reading so kudos
gaocaandra: are you counting root visits? i think you should
nsielicki: introductors fundamentals classes aren't taught by the brightest, but if you're lucky your junior and senior classes will be taught by people as smart as george
DeeboMC: well then.. thats never gonna make you elite
ak0ya_: Cold it be that mcts not working is juts a symptom of a bug elsewhere?
ak0ya_: *could
ytazn: Yeah starting out I used videos to get more of the emotional vibes of what’s important
FiZdaWiz: bruh u are a genius
cod4_lightning: I subscribed geo. Show me your dotfiles LOL!
IaMvAzU: stockPray HeyGuys
Major_Spicy: Non-sub chat PogChamp
chunks____: maybe it needs a sigmoidal function
skinnypuppy69: @deebomc me?
DeeboMC: yes
FiZdaWiz: i dont know wtf you ever do and i watch hrs of your videos so interesting
SparksCx: shameless
ViktorTV: @georgehotz Consider a system with two components. Transitions among the states of the system can be represented using a Markov chain as shown in the following figure. In this figure, each state of the system represents the number of components in operation. Derive the steady-state probability vector in terms of the parameters r and p. Vary r and p each simultaneously from 0.1 to 0.90, in steps of 0.10, and plot the probabilities of states 0, 1, and 2. You will have three plots, one each for sta
FiZdaWiz: lmao link onlyfans
WEEEEEEEELL_ITS_KNOCC_OUT: buddhaGasm
IaMvAzU: lol
IaMvAzU: whats ur onlyfans link?
l1ght5p33d: whats a dot file
SparksCx: actually shameless
skooches: sup geo, what we doing today
samwilliamson7: Whatcha drinking???
cod4_lightning: we don't have paypal in my country. any other option?
l1ght5p33d: is that what u said
guinness84: send dots plz
DeeboMC: lmao
johnpyp: s
Noxique: gimme the OnlyFans link OH MY GAWD Kreygasm
IaMvAzU: whats ur paypal?
ViktorTV: Consider a system with two components. Transitions among the states of the system can be represented using a Markov chain as shown in the following figure. In this figure, each state of the system represents the number of components in operation. Derive the steady-state probability vector in terms of the parameters r and p. Vary r and p each simultaneously from 0.1 to 0.90, in steps of 0.10, and plot the probabilities of states 0, 1, and 2. You will have three plots, one each for states 0, 1, an
SHAVEYY_: yes
IaMvAzU: yes
thickbordiga: yes
lolzmaster99: Ban Viktor
gaocaandra: ban ViktorTV
slayerdaniel: yes they allow men
ViktorTV: no pls
sit_d: they allow animals. too
skooches: ms added hypervisor tampering checks into patchguard so i'm trying to mitigate them because how else am i going to reverse anticheat for clout otherwise
archiveutility: Yeah
DeeboMC: cashapp and id do it
theirishtripleking: Yes you are allowed to do the helicopter
nsielicki: he's asking for homework help
lolzmaster99: It's a homework problem
SHAVEYY_: LUL
slayerdaniel: they allow men named George too
Mariosavitch: hello mr hotz
ViktorTV: i keep on sending it in the wr ong chat
ViktorTV: the first was intentional
nsielicki: very plausable story
ViktorTV: the second was not
gaocaandra: asking for help with homework should be bannable
TheKoreanZombi: Chat forgives you Viktor.
ViktorTV: @gaocaandra suck me bitch
ViktorTV: @TheKoreanZombi ty
Mariosavitch: i have a 200 word essay due tomorrow
cod4_lightning: I bet if you do "Configuring Mac and Vim like an ex-iphone hacker" you will get more 100k in a month! LOL!
DeeboMC: ok NOW ban him
gaocaandra: wow calm down
gaocaandra: we are a chill collective
skooches: zackfoSQUARE
lolzmaster99: Might as well try min_max_stats
DeeboMC: exactlyu
gaocaandra: of people working overtime
slayerdaniel: bro this chat lol
gaocaandra: and twekve yearolds
slayerdaniel: LUL
DeeboMC: viktor can gtfo.. gaocaandro = 5 viktors, at least.
olvroger: what did i miss wtf
l1ght5p33d: @gaocaandra are you in school
olvroger: PogChamp
gaocaandra: i'm at home cuarantined working 80+ hours a week george is the closest thing to human contact i have
TheKoreanZombi: muzero go brrrr for ones
skooches: mutantfeDollbaby me trying to understand specifically what geo is doing without backstory bro share the notebook or something
gaocaandra: github
Mariosavitch: its aware???
gaocaandra: check his latest commit
guest1GRjBAYo: why stream?
skooches: "github" so specific thanks bro got it i shall open github.com
cod4_lightning: anyone have paypal with 50$ in it and like to exchange with something? geo, you will upload them to a private repo and email the link to me.. OK? LOOOL
l1ght5p33d: @gaocaandra watching twitch
olvroger: geez
DeeboMC: lmaooo @skooches
gigafact: https://github.com/geohot/ai-notebooks
Mariosavitch: are you interested in finance hotz?
nsielicki: what kind of performance bump were you really expecting from monte carlo?
olvroger: you mad or what
gaocaandra: ye
skooches: @gigafact thank you sir ojreevTea
AppleGrape: @georgehotz Where can I learn ML man
gaocaandra: we tried using it
gaocaandra: to route ambulances at work
nsielicki: hahahah
Mariosavitch: lol
gaocaandra: we still have it collecting dust in a bitbucket
nsielicki: it seems like it's better at discrete problems
tonyk76: yoo
nsielicki: many dissimilar states
sit_d: turn out God only runs on supercomputers
slayerdaniel: is that a futon next to you
DeeboMC: *quantum
junwohwan: Lol
Twistedbane: Twistedbane subscribed with Twitch Prime.
gaocaandra: yeah
DeeboMC: seriously tho.
gaocaandra: routing is gonna have to wait
gaocaandra: esither that
gaocaandra: or some amazing shit happens
lolzmaster99: Increase exploration noise again
nsielicki: show plot pls
l1ght5p33d: @gaocaandra ban drivers and add comma ai
gaocaandra: jajjajaaja
lolzmaster99: It's stuck near local minima
gaocaandra: thats the plan
guinness84: monte carlo was a snitch
gaocaandra: there is like 2 flors of human labour that im gonna delete
skooches: its a fucking place not a person lmfao
cod4_lightning: if anyone has no idea what the hell he is doing: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/AlphaZero
nsielicki: well we expected it to be better, I just am struggling to understand under what conditions the naive strategy would outperform it, something we're missing
DeeboMC: you dont know larry "monte carlo" jones?
Mariosavitch: we smart
FrancescoTommaso: at least you did car pool
Kawhiet: Is there a video with proof?
slayerdaniel: we bout to fake the moon landing boys?
eeXecute: Go party
mashafique: Party time PogChamp
wainemier: 'what
IaMvAzU: is that the muni?
cod4_lightning: what is this noise?
Ne0Zer0: PartyPopper
l1ght5p33d: you should also yell
skooches: dotsNeurons
cod4_lightning: goooo partyyyyy
DeeboMC: they might be giants too
Ne0Zer0: PartyTime
wainemier: PogChamp
Ne0Zer0: PartyHat
treestompztv: WOOOOOO
gaocaandra: coronaparty
l1ght5p33d: yeez
slayerdaniel: there we go
nsielicki: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wmWJ27glFQY
Lana_Lux: someone has an air horn? Lol
raisedbyphantom: POG
mashafique: PartyHat
cod4_lightning: this is some interesting content right here
skooches: zackfoSQUARE me outside geo's apartment building screaming at him
node_storm: lmfaoo. tell them we are trying to work up here. keep it down
cod4_lightning: please please please do one hackthebox today
fa_k: m
cod4_lightning: somebody still partying alone out there LOL
mangoxavier: Going to read the docs.
cod4_lightning: MaxLOL MaxLOL
slayerdaniel: SeemsGood
cod4_lightning: this part in the stream will be muted on youtube
DeeboMC: buckethead - dawn appears
skooches: you keep saying that but i don't see anything landing on anything lunar
cod4_lightning: stop violating copy rights
peter35_: heck yea learn to hoverslam that ho
routerkicker: fuck copy rights
TheKoreanZombi: Yes, I have seen lunar lander.
cod4_lightning: geo, do you like IoT?
DeeboMC: "hoverslam that ho" lmao
mik12f4: maybe it only wants to play Global Thermonuclear War?
skooches: this is we keep the gpu box onhand because we don't have 12 hours to see if our training outcome is good
katrocitus: are you trying to learn rust?
FrancescoTommaso: my cat solved car pole
cod4_lightning: https://gym.openai.com/envs/CartPole-v1/
info303: connect4 is a good one to use because it's a solved game
PrivateOrange: What about https://github.com/werner-duvaud/muzero-general ?
info303: so you can test it against a perfect strategy
xeeton: how can your naive implementation be faster than MCTS?
slayerdaniel: george, ya got any ice cream?
DeeboMC: blackkack?
Mariosavitch: he dead
DeeboMC: jack*
Jehhred: The lack of thrust is discerning
bulksquat_thrust: You ever code a stock trading bot?
nsielicki: doesn't surprise me that a paper with the word "superhuman performance" in the abstract lacks reproducibility
cod4_lightning: we've learned reactjs last time, let's learn nodejs today
slayerdaniel: liars, all of them, liars
aar0npham: could be a photoshop image =?
DeeboMC: @georgehotz Data > Spock, amirite?
cod4_lightning: "WE TYPE AND CLICK WHILE WE SHIT TALK"
axx88: What game is he coding?
searchingforlife: LUL
DeeboMC: he's isnt
Kawhiet: just throw more tpus at it
Mariosavitch: does it know it has actions to fire thrusters
nsielicki: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pudIZbCRq_c
FrancescoTommaso: brute force way
MoTeMiB: !uptime
Pr0ject414: as obi one konobi once said... "throw all the tpus at it"
TheKoreanZombi: It is going for speed and accuracy
slayerdaniel: it just doesnt feel like it
cod4_lightning: do you watch streams other than yours?
searchingforlife: its trying its best
DeeboMC: @nsielicki lol
mik12f4: delete the ground
TheKoreanZombi: If the lander flips upside down and fires its thrusters so it crashes faster I will be happy.
DeeboMC: @Pr0ject414 great man, obi wan
Mariosavitch: its learned to die quicker
janpoonthong: What is your Mac spec?
nsielicki: he's got one of those new 16" mbp
Pr0ject414: @deebomc but obi one is the better man... he is number 1
cod4_lightning: @janpoonthong 13 macbook maxed out i think
DeeboMC: i see what you did there
janpoonthong: @cod4_lightning I see
node_storm: he has the new 16 inch i think
bulksquat_thrust: this was a bad stream to hop in the middle of huh
bulksquat_thrust: my small brain doesnt know whats happening
FangSkillz: hes coding
cod4_lightning: @bulksquat_thrust EXACTLY!
FangSkillz: but trying to make his custom spaceship to fire thrusters @bulksquat_thrust
janpoonthong: He use laptop to code?
FangSkillz: yeah
FangSkillz: i guess idk LUL
nsielicki: NOT BAD AT ALL
JeanFrag: does it always respawn close to the center? then any (alteration of angle)(power of truster) will likely push it away @georgehotz
cod4_lightning: He needs that Mac Pro
node_storm: making progress
FangSkillz: !spec
FangSkillz: !pc
bulksquat_thrust: ah
birkett0011: very smrt
sit_d: he's just a baby
FangSkillz: ^
costcospizza: true
janpoonthong: What he is doing now?
JeanFrag: I think you should randomize respawn zone, not in the center @georgehotz
janpoonthong: Creating game?
FangSkillz: waiting till model starts thrusters @janpoonthong
cod4_lightning: @georgehotz make a petereon so we can get you a mac pro maxed out with 1tb ram so you make us more top notch streams
DeeboMC: @cod4_lightning you cant be serious
Lana_Lux: @janpoonthong he's using MuZero to solve a game
FangSkillz: "@georgehotz make a petereon so we can get you a mac pro maxed out with 1tb ram so you make us more top notch streams" - @cod4_lightning
StopitDonk: ^
FangSkillz: i guess he doesn't have chat open LUL
JeanFrag: rip
cod4_lightning: @deebomc yes i am, he deserve that!
ytazn: Ok I installed it
DeeboMC: he can afford it if he wants it
bulksquat_thrust: what mac is he using?
l1ght5p33d: make observation learning
32bitrobo: twitchRaid
bulksquat_thrust: seems like its breathin hard
l1ght5p33d: f$@& keras tho what does concatenate even do
FangSkillz: twitchRaid
bubblesnot: @georgehotz how well is the comma two ADAS device selling?
nsielicki: stop asking about k3yb0@rd and his computer and whether he wants a mac pro, he's happy with his setup
DeeboMC: this guy gets it
cod4_lightning: anyone here coding along with him and trying to solve the problem with him?
l1ght5p33d: jk keras is good
FangSkillz: @nsielicki are you sure since he hasn't said anything
nsielicki: it's in the description as a bannable offense.
routerkicker: give it less reward when It's vertical velocity is high
FangSkillz: but we are just trying to help him so i don't know how this would be a ban offense
bulksquat_thrust: just wondering the hardware needed to run this faster lol
FangSkillz: ^
DeeboMC: i dont think you guys are even sycophants, you're just irrationally subservient and infatuated
Loutlot: Loutlot subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months!
JeanFrag: can you randomize the spawn point? @georgehotz
cod4_lightning: do you announce that you are going to stream about a specific topic before on discord, so we can have an idea and prepare?
DeeboMC: no
DeeboMC: i dont even know that as a fact i can just infer
info303: if it randomly explores maybe it just needs a lot more episodes?
ytazn: Does it know how to fire thrusters?
eeXecute: maybe it's getting rewarded to early jk idk
pokerpete555: I vote @JeanFrag idea
l1ght5p33d: manual input,, pipe state to history buffer
pokerpete555: whatever thats worth
fychvhvjh: you can take on big semi autonomous car comps they will have vegence on u
DeeboMC: i think its a good idea
badpartyhouse: Reverse the value for the down thrust
l1ght5p33d: or switch the sign of something
badpartyhouse: make the down thrust positive
badpartyhouse: see if it learns that way
bottonresult: !uptime
fychvhvjh: are you selling car data to the asians?
rudolphdoesgames: how was the protest?
ytazn: 1900 collect a bunch of employees run a company 2020 collect a bunch of packages run a company
JeanFrag: should i even try saying it again?
badpartyhouse: it is making the down thrust has such a negative value, just make it into a positive value and see what happens then???
cod4_lightning: how can i control a robot with an iOS app? what are the steps for doing that?
ytazn: Lunar lander?
l1ght5p33d: Parse the history and reverse the sign on everything
ytazn: Or tic tac toe?
DeeboMC: step one: locate a toys'r'us..
cod4_lightning: can you talk about your pwn2own experience?
l1ght5p33d: manual input good values
JeanFrag: can you randomize spawn point? @georgehotz
ytazn: Guys I’m at training step 20 of 10k
JeanFrag: yea
fychvhvjh: can you start an all girl coding class to promote equality
gaocaandra: yeah that makes sense
ytazn: Guys this is super fucking boring
ytazn: I have to wait for 100k ganes
l1ght5p33d: what
DeeboMC: @fychvhvjh primo shit lol
JeanFrag: right now it is not worth risky using thrusters when it gets better results not doing anything because it respawns in the center @georgehotz
ytazn: The model eats 100k games
nsielicki: lol
Ne0Zer0: LUL
iIyaRPV: iIyaRPV subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months!
PiroFloydian: Bio hype
gaocaandra: bio is the future
rickoftheroot: LUL
ytazn: Lol
bubblesnot: How well is comma ai doing?
abe8k: how often are you doing covid19 bio? joined twitch for it tbh
raystriker98: well they do have unlimited resources thanks to Google
sit_d: the details of their results are lackluster
bubblesnot: Ok np
l1ght5p33d: it's just sparse reward just move things and sink into different minimum no problem
TheKoreanZombi: @abe8k He is done with bio.
DeeboMC: "bio is over.." (portlandia, anyone?)
ytazn: Bad rewards still help tho?
FrancescoTommaso: maybe solve this with good and old q-learning or sarsa
gaocaandra: do what jeafrag said
ytazn: Bad rewards say don’t do that
nsielicki: so what's happening that it's approaching a solution and then getting thrown out? we need to do more math
gaocaandra: ok
FrancescoTommaso: Ok
JeanFrag: yes!
pokerpete555: yay Jean
nsielicki: something in replay
l1ght5p33d: initial conditions are the most important thing in most complex systems
raystriker98: atleast a few Tesla v100s
Pr0ject414: "just spin up a vm and bingo bamo bobs your uncle"
DeeboMC: lol
numlox: maybe run it on colab?
AppleGrape: Integrating this into no limit texas hold em
raystriker98: colab free only gives you one single slow xeon core
gaocaandra: or some other paid service, you could sell out for compute and shove ads
raystriker98: and 2 threads
Pr0ject414: i got a 2080ti let me just give you access to all my personal files LOLOL
DeeboMC: blackjack's way more likley
l1ght5p33d: know all the other players cards
pokerpete555: I'm playing the great game right now while watching
info303: why not see what happens if it runs for longer?
pokerpete555: holdem, not blackjack
routerkicker: maybe discount it still a bit too high?
DeeboMC: blackjack is solved tho
pokerpete555: yup
pokerpete555: ez
oversum: Think it's good practice for a programmer to have both Mac and Windows?
DeeboMC: windows is spyware confrimed, so theres that.. but otherwise yea
AppleGrape: I have both
l1ght5p33d: you want to do observation on poker i would think
AppleGrape: I prefer my mac for web dev
WhispyHerc: still working on cartpole?
l1ght5p33d: manually input state of chips and who wins
Pr0ject414: bit too high meaning go down in numbers closer to zero?
oversum: I mean I'm in my junior year of college for cybersec and I'm starting to see more and more mac stuff
DeeboMC: mac for work; linux for fun... altho george does the opposite
nsielicki: lol
ytazn: @deebomc I’m flipped too but I’ll get fired soon
oversum: savage
l1ght5p33d: need WPT logs
WhispyHerc: do be wiggling fast doe 😳
katrocitus: do you kaggle?
Pr0ject414: so a marked improvement after going down .01
Pr0ject414: or just luck
DeeboMC: @ytazn you want to get fired or you just anticipate it happening soon?
pokerpete555: @l1ght5p33d better to solve cash than tourney
gaocaandra: randomize it
78DHF: !uptime
gaocaandra: lunar_lander.py
gaocaandra: is the filename
ytazn: @deebomc I anticipate it cus I’m trash and I build so slow
gaocaandra: line 56
gaocaandra: is the param i think
gaocaandra: i dunno
gaocaandra: https://github.com/openai/gym/blob/master/gym/envs/box2d/lunar_lander.py
knitler_: How is it stopping an infinite recursion through the tree?
DeeboMC: lol damn.. well with an realistic outlook like that, i think you'll do just fine
l1ght5p33d: make bin size of action and mostly use same action then smol random
nsielicki: :set paste
nsielicki: why does vim do that anyway?
DeeboMC: puts you ahead of, maybe, 80-90% people probably.. just give it time and keep perpetually improving
gaocaandra: 138
ytazn: What does Jupiter do?
swftdev: Jupiter is a notebook environment to write code in
nsielicki: the thing is the paper is about not knowing any of the rules, it shouldn't need to have this rule of the game exposed to it
l1ght5p33d: ;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;
swftdev: make code streams work again
l1ght5p33d: is spamming ascii llegal
gaocaandra: penalize it for not using thrusters
ytazn: @swftdev ty
shutchie: isn't the -100 crash?
gaocaandra: JAJAAJAAJJAJ
bulksquat_thrust: i need a programming project to save me from boredom but im not creative enough to figure one out myself
gaocaandra: join a cult
AppleGrape: There is so many possibilities.....
AppleGrape: use your brain man
be9ns: hes in the vim cult
badpartyhouse: this shit is broken
gaocaandra: how is that happening?
nsielicki: agh this is fucked
superluminal86: jupyter cult
routerkicker: maybe change discount back. idk man
gaocaandra: maybe it takes longer
FrancescoTommaso: increase punishment
JeanFrag: is there a cost to using thrusters/
Pr0ject414: -69 for not using it
gigafact: I still remember the stream when you said you did not want them to end in failure. We will ever make this work...
nsielicki: i think the strongest theory so far is that it just needs much more compute than we're throwing at it
JeanFrag: does the benefit of winning closer to the center outweigh the cost of using thrusters?
FrancescoTommaso: reduce loss of points for time to completion
gill_bates_macrosoft: @bulksquat_thrust I'm doing a few stuff here, except in rust https://github.com/rby90/Project-Based-Tutorials-in-C
be9ns: heard to talk to lex about Haskell, any projects besides a compiler?
WhispyHerc: wait so if using the thrusters is bad why do you want it to use the thrusters if it's finding ways to solve it without them
ytazn: This is like slapping the pilot when he messes up
ak0ya_: maybe mcts search?
shutchie: is the negative reward for using thrusters being overcome by a positive reward by getting closer to the surface? seems like the reward needs to be based on descent rate
swftdev: this is the existential moment where if it works or not might not matter..
info303: is the idea with muZero to discover the actions on it's own?
ytazn: Slapping the pilot seems like a great idea now
knitler_: seems like the reward would be much easier for chess/go
swftdev: sticks not carrots
Pr0ject414: im waiting for the tomcr00se music stream.
bulksquat_thrust: @gill_bates_macrosoft ive been doing stuff in c++ to get better at memory management
TheKoreanZombi: Doesn't the lander by default penalize thruster use or is the main engine different than thruster? "Firing main engine is -0.3 points each frame."
badpartyhouse: give it more reward if it keeps the time going
Iluvmf: LUL LUL LUL
node_storm: hahaha
WhispyHerc: LUL
gigafact: damn
shutchie: descent rate
badpartyhouse: ahhahaha
nsielicki: "can't lose if you can't see me, bitch"
Kawhiet: progress
rickoftheroot: LULW
FrancescoTommaso: LOL
bulksquat_thrust: "cant lose if i dont try" haha
gaocaandra: jajajaa
badpartyhouse: well the negative reward is not so bad
DeeboMC: slappa de pilot
badpartyhouse: ahhaha
Musashhhi: trying to get to earth
LiveCustoms: Geoooo
WhispyHerc: OMEGALUL
rickoftheroot: LUL
vanishingtacos: LUL LUL
Pr0ject414: give it a height restriction negative reward
shutchie: @georgehotz base the reward on the descent rate being within a specified range?
DeeboMC: lmao
ytazn: Penalize it randomly
phrixus_bro: same starting weights every time?
swftdev: where there is a determined correct outcome instead of a range of outcome
bubblesnot: Run it as admin
eljok3r: timeout
ytazn: Yeah try running it as admin
gaocaandra: penealize acceleration in the downward sense
DeeboMC: sudo work
rickoftheroot: LUL
TheKoreanZombi: Learned a barrel roll
Penguino138: Open Starfox
bubblesnot: SpaceX
Iluvmf: I dont think thats what we wanted, but I guess it kinda landed
ytazn: It learned drunk flip
l1ght5p33d: i like punish downward acceleration
gaocaandra: punish unstability
DeeboMC: i second that
Pr0ject414: after we learn muzero we do Unity ML agents
gaocaandra: measured by rotation
ytazn: Punish independent hoping and dreaming
DeeboMC: punish downward accelration
bubblesnot: What if boosters did shorter burst?
DeeboMC: lol
gaocaandra: is the penalization they used the same a s the default in gym?
ytazn: Punish being purple
iKanak_: just solve it manually and punish it for not following your actions
gaocaandra: punish it for not punishing itself
pokerpete555: just punish it
bulksquat_thrust: that learning rate tho
l1ght5p33d: you need whole run window of history
ytazn: Yeah just punish
l1ght5p33d: whole entire one
DeeboMC: punish it for accepting reward
jimmyadaro: lmao hello
gaocaandra: randomly punish it
no_g: punish it like an abusive father
nsielicki: story of my academic career right there
badpartyhouse: i volunteer as tribute
vanishingtacos: Keyword is might
Pr0ject414: this dude is doing 20,000 training rounds
FrancescoTommaso: RL usually takes forever
FrancescoTommaso: look at leela chess zero
Penguino138: I don think we should punish it? Has anyone seen Ex Machina? dotsKpog
info303: thats what Ive been sayin :D
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Is cart pole done?
nsielicki: anyone else hate how np.array([1])*4 is [4] whereas [1]*4 is [1,1,1,1]?
DeeboMC: i havent seen it but ive heard the plot
info303: i mean running it for many more episodes
l1ght5p33d: does anyone know if this was a hack https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/09/world/middleeast/iran-plane-crash-ukraine.html
superluminal86: Does Mu zero applies some kind of exploration/explotation?
nsielicki: yeah it hacks the computer to make the answer good
Pr0ject414: Can you run it in parallel?
DeeboMC: if you have to ask you arleady know it was
l1ght5p33d: incompetence
info303: i think it has to since it learns everything from scratch
Pr0ject414: Many iterations at once
l1ght5p33d: also plausible af
l1ght5p33d: need passenger list
Pr0ject414: listen to the sound of the electric toothbrush as it passes over his glistening teeth.
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Can hear the cpu fan running 4Head
l1ght5p33d: this is what happens when u give robots knives
bulksquat_thrust: kek
LiveCustoms: George you play Pokemon?
radixcov: Mac or Linux?
gaocaandra: this s the new protein fold
superluminal86: Does Mu zero applies some kind of exploration/explotation?
TheKoreanZombi: run overnight, resume tomorrow
FrancescoTommaso: the problem is that it seems to lack exploration
Pr0ject414: Is it possible to run this in parallel?
raystriker98: please stop the random n00b questions ,chat
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: Chat ask about the key board Jebaited monkaS
Pr0ject414: asynchronous actions.
routerkicker: discount on the dudes github is 0.997.
JeanFrag: it is clearly capable of learning, it learned to not use thrusters, so the problems is the incentive that makes it want to not use it @georgehotz
bubblesnot: @georgehotz what is your prediction on quantum computers?
TiPera: Hi there
0R4NG3: monkaS
l1ght5p33d: they can predict the future duh
routerkicker: lotsa thruster action i think
robonhansonem: Last time someone asked he was bearish on Quantum computers in the near term.
l1ght5p33d: obviously wave packets propogate back from the future
l1ght5p33d: everyone knows that
l1ght5p33d: its all about group velocity
robonhansonem: The Canadian QC startup D-wave was a scam.
l1ght5p33d: makes radiation in nuclear blue
l1ght5p33d: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cherenkov_radiation
eDONze: sd
be9ns: george do you play any videogames?
swftdev: are links banned??
swftdev: @georgehotz https://arxiv.org/pdf/1905.09381.pdf
mik3xx: I don't know anything about computing or coding. But it looks interesting and you've inspired me to learn. Should I take a course or learn on my own? What language should i learn?
DeeboMC: d-wave actually did nothing?
gaocaandra: learn pyhon
mik3xx: I heard python will be outdated soon?
gaocaandra: na
nsielicki: observation
gaocaandra: no such thing
swftdev: milk meme'n real hard.
nsielicki: learn c++20
nsielicki: c++20 is python but fast
iIyaRPV: Jebaited
nsielicki: i'm so excited about STL ranges and views that it's unhealthy
stale2000: 5Head
forkdb: Ok
l1ght5p33d: anyone know if you could run a game in javascript by streaming an image and hacking some input layer over it
nsielicki: https://en.cppreference.com/w/cpp/algorithm/execution_policy_tag_t is next-level stuff that AFAIK doesn't exist in any other serious language
routerkicker: @l1ght5p33d what do you mean? use html5 canvas
jwlolol: !uptime
DeeboMC: long time
l1ght5p33d: canvas is pretty good
iIyaRPV: ~3.5h @jwlolol
nsielicki: and that's on top of a few hours this morning
justenpassant: so you didn't get arrested. nice
jwlolol: nice
DeeboMC: he didnt go.... napped and watched on youtube instead
coProof: He’s not stopping!
l1ght5p33d: jail is not so bad as long as you don't fight anyone
DeeboMC: depends on duration as well
DeeboMC: it can get boring
cod4_lightning: studying OSCP 2020, any tips?
l1ght5p33d: @deebomc i suppose i meant that more as a warning
justenpassant: are you speaking from experience
DeeboMC: yes
DeeboMC: lol i see
TiPera: do u guys recommend learning python?
l1ght5p33d: spent a full year in county bro
TheKoreanZombi: @cod4_lightning Yes, try harder.
DeeboMC: yes
iIyaRPV: yes
gigafact: Over 17 hours working on this problem. Anyone blown away by George's persistence...
l1ght5p33d: girls love it
DeeboMC: damn dude. got me beat
DeeboMC: hell yea, facts
l1ght5p33d: @deebomc money is several times better
SlaterUSA: hi
socialnotsocial: Are you going to build an AR headset geohot?
SlaterUSA: what's that lil game-like thing running in the window?
l1ght5p33d: @SlaterUSA kelly?
no_g: LennyFace
DeeboMC: not sure i get that. money is better than jail? because i 100% agree... or do u mean fast money is better than slow money... cuz i disagreee in the longrun lol
SlaterUSA: @l1ght5p33d no, christian, obvs
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: pepeD
Iluvmf: @SlaterUSA Its lunarlander
l1ght5p33d: @SlaterUSA we are elite programmers
IMTotes: BBoomer
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: BBoomer pepeD
DeeboMC: "ideology sniffing raccon" lol
nsielicki: for j in range(60)
l1ght5p33d: @SlaterUSA happy to have you mr Slater
SlaterUSA: yw, now gimme 20
l1ght5p33d: lander needs some work
nsielicki: based music taste
cod4_lightning: guys it's ramadan over here! we're fasting 20 hours a day!
l1ght5p33d: just started so it's ok
DeeboMC: is that like gimme 5? but with all four limbs?
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: @deebomc RaccAttack
TheKoreanZombi: Lunar lander. Built Ford Tough!
salman2301: 20 hours? Which country is that?
SlaterUSA: @deebomc it means push-ups
biguieboss: love your taste with bob seger!!!
DeeboMC: i know dude
TiPera: !uptime
nsielicki: @deebomc laughed so hard i spilled water
TiPera: what is MCTS?
DeeboMC: haha nice
cod4_lightning: @salman2301 somewhere in europe.. try to guess
l1ght5p33d: MEDIUM CHAIN TRIGLYCERIDES
TheKoreanZombi: @TiPera Monte Carlo Tree Search
mitrocc: why are you not allowed to say the word k-eyboard?
TiPera: thank you @TheKoreanZombi
SlaterUSA: 11
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
cod4_lightning: OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOH YEAAAAAH Geo is getting ripped!
Punkfx: take shirt off
no_g: cbrahRbicep cbrahRbicep cbrahRbicep
mik12f4: arms at 45 degrees?
TiPera: ToS @Punkfx
cod4_lightning: no pain no gain bro, that was a decent workout
DeeboMC: like a rock inspired him
mitrocc: No its not ToS @TiPera
no_g: Now 50 bicycle crunches PogChamp
nsielicki: YEAH
Punkfx: its not ToS to show off those guns.
TheKoreanZombi: @mitrocc Because what difference does it make what equipment he uses?
TiPera: are people allowed to show nipples on twitch? O__O @mitrocc
gaocaandra: yeaaa boooiii
SlaterUSA: i'm too old to learn :(
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 2 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 19 in the channel!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to ak0ya_!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to vloood!
mitrocc: @TiPera People do workout streams shirtless
TiPera: i didnt know, sorry then D: @mitrocc
forkdb: Keep learning
ak0ya_: @c1tr0n75 Thanks for the gift sub!
mitrocc: @TheKoreanZombi ??? who said anything about that
biguieboss: that song means a world to me! good choice
mitrocc: @TiPera Its okay :D
justenpassant: how many iterations does this one need?
mitrocc: @TiPera D:
TiPera: but girls. = ban right D: @mitrocc
DeeboMC: need moar montage music
justenpassant: how many learning iterations does this one need?
mitrocc: @TiPera Girls cant get banned on twitch FeelsGoodMan
c1tr0n75: cheer50
TiPera: @mitrocc true, 2020 twitch Kappa
TheKoreanZombi: @mitrocc I am just explaining to you why that word is bannable. Because people ask dumb questions about it.
mitrocc: @TheKoreanZombi Doesnt make sense , but his channel his rules
cod4_lightning: bro, i don't have a GF, let's build some AI girls
nsielicki: don't you dare restart that kernel
drake_elite: hello guys any one can give a learning path i want to do something like this please?
SlaterUSA: @georgehotz what's ur rent in that humble abode
nsielicki: i think it's about to work
TheKoreanZombi: @mitrocc I support it. Dumb questions get annoying.
cod4_lightning: !time
mik12f4: does it even know its suppose to land between the flags?
cod4_lightning: !uptime
mitrocc: @TiPera Twitch have some of the best athleats, World record for cat throwing Alinity. World record for most nip slips on stream -Alinity. 3 day ban CoolStoryBob
bubblesnot: How does it sense the yellow flags?
forkdb: May be he should dedicate one whole twitch stream to answer all the questions, so that there would be no more dumb questions....
info303: it gets a big reward when it lands below a certain downward velocity I think right? if I understand correctly it has to accidentally stumble upon that scenario
Kawhiet: @forkdb theres always new viewers
cod4_lightning: how long the stream is now?
DeeboMC: cat throwing summer league
TheKoreanZombi: @forkdb No, there are too many dumb questions. They would all be asked again the next day.
bulksquat_thrust: speaking of ban worthy peripherals, im soldering one together tomorrow CoolStoryBob
mitrocc: !mouse
mitrocc: outsmarted
nsielicki: is this still the modified version of the game? are you sure you removed all the mods to the rewards you made?
forkdb: They can always go back to being sub to watch, by doing that he would make more subs as well...
mik12f4: can you narrow the flags? maybe it will learn faster
mitrocc: If i cant type the k word i can write the m word
mitrocc: ezClap
gaocaandra: he changed it
TiPera: @mitrocc nip slip when? i saw the cat thingy lmao
gaocaandra: he's using default values for penalization
mitrocc: @TiPera She slipped the nip couple days ago, and took twitch 3 days to ban her
TheKoreanZombi: No lunar lander left behind.
bulksquat_thrust: Probably only because community outrage
logi6000: yo how you doij
TiPera: @mitrocc i just checked and her channel is still up, how dafuq ? D:
mitrocc: @TiPera Because twitch staff are virgins
logi6000: whose channel
mitrocc: Alinity
Pr0ject414: it doesnt appear to be learning at all
Santiago_LHC: Are people behaving? Do we need timeouts?
Pr0ject414: just random
justenpassant: the reward maybe?
Pr0ject414: its not consistent
mitrocc: @Santiago_LHC Ive bean a bad boy, i might need a timeout ;)
TheKoreanZombi: Run overnight. Will be very smart by tomorrow. So much thrust.
Santiago_LHC: It's not fun if you enjoy it
Pr0ject414: if your plotted those out it would be jumping all over the place and not a steady decline
mitrocc: I hate it :)
logi6000: oh yeah she's done all sorts of shit and gotten away. she just dosent get banned. probably fucks the twitch staff to get free
mitrocc: Nah she has a only staff for twitch mods
mitrocc: heh
nsielicki: reduce i, increase j
TiPera: @mitrocc good point 4Head
mitrocc: onlyfans*
raystriker98: NOT OKAY
logi6000: only for allinity
liivius: all nipples not ok
rickoftheroot: fluid Kapp
IMTotes: only when breastfeeding
LiveCustoms: Only MALE Nipples
mitrocc: Only alinity nipples are okay
Musashhhi: uh oh
no_g: Cow nipples are OK
l1ght5p33d: twitch will be overrun by the horde eventually as well
l1ght5p33d: we can only hold so long
727_tf: it's trying it's hardest
TheKoreanZombi: Ran out of fuel
727_tf: it's just dumb
Pr0ject414: yes
mitrocc: If its a workout stream yes
liivius: Nopr
gigafact: no
no_g: Get the belt out George
raystriker98: don't do it
iIyaRPV: no
IMTotes: only if u r breastfeeding @georgehotz
Pr0ject414: for males
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: squadW Clap MY MAN
727_tf: no
logi6000: he wants to do it
LiveCustoms: YES
mitrocc: Yes you can
rickoftheroot: monkaS No
c1tr0n75: no
Pr0ject414: males ok
no_g: Time to discipline
risky_banana: No you're not allowed
nsielicki: VoteYea
GS540: only if you are alinity
no_g: Find out PogChamp
LiveCustoms: DO IT KappaPride
logi6000: totally
bubblesnot: I hope
mitrocc: Do it KappaPride
TheKoreanZombi: Males okay unless for prurient reasons.
nsielicki: VoteNay
tornpaperyoyos: woah what did conversation did i just get into
iIyaRPV: still no
ncanggoro: dont
rickoftheroot: LUL
c1tr0n75: too late
logi6000: no
socialnotsocial: what happened with the protein folding?
ripSquidd: Do it KappaPride
ncanggoro: why
siccbrain: nope
LiveCustoms: No only Men Nipples
babaquon: lets find out
justenpassant: that's what you should be protesting for
justenpassant: lol
rickoftheroot: only one way to find out :)
logi6000: you'd get personality raped by a twitch staff
Br4nnon: yolo?
l1ght5p33d: model isBreastfeedint{}
no_g: If you say you identify as a woman and then show your penis it's ok KappaPride
Pr0ject414: "those who present as women must also cover their nipples"
Tekrific: to few epochs
Pr0ject414: from the TOS
nsielicki: i just feel like the replay training is excessive
Br4nnon: good ole loop hole
logi6000: no will he do it. the world may never know
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: genitalia is not ok on twitch
nsielicki: 100 plays, 5000 trains
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: male of female
mitrocc: You trying to bankrupt spaceX?
DotaStar666: whats he coding
nsielicki: too many trains not enough plays
Pr0ject414: can you plot those out and see the spikes
nsielicki: increase j decrease i
nsielicki: i'm speaking out of my ass here
l1ght5p33d: @DotaStar666 nice name
logi6000: guys dont tell geo what only fans is. he'll fucking do it
mitrocc: Make a only fans KappaPride
mik12f4: deploy a parachute
zetto97: hello from Spain Geo! I have learnt a lot of things thank your content in yt and in twitch
l1ght5p33d: i only play halo 2
l1ght5p33d: on xbox original
DeeboMC: @logi6000 he already mentioned in this stream
mitrocc: Halo 2 = Bad game
logi6000: really. whatd he say
l1ght5p33d: @mitrocc maybe
bulksquat_thrust: they call it halo 2 because you get 2 guns
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d i can dig it.
DeeboMC: Halo 2 = great game
mitrocc: And you play it twice and then quit Kappa @bulksquat_thrust
fukurowlz: @zetto97 you may also improve your english
IMTotes: PogChamp BOTTOM THRUSTER!
mitrocc: If you want to improve your english, play minecraft
l1ght5p33d: wooooowwwwwwwww
DeeboMC: @logi6000 he'd send you the dotfiles if you paypal'd him 50 bucks or subscribed to his onlyfans lmao
sevaric: positive numbers PogChamp
jsnake794: i caught you live yaya
logi6000: @deebomc what dotfiles
l1ght5p33d: yes what dotfiles
l1ght5p33d: are they good?
logi6000: for what
DeeboMC: his private github shit, i think its a joke
l1ght5p33d: joking
sevaric: if you make a plot of a list that is growing, will jupyter automatically update the plot?
Pr0ject414: the appearance of randomness
l1ght5p33d: mods are asleep delete .dotfile from .gitignore
mitrocc: Wait he doesnt have a donate button? :(
Pr0ject414: i wouldnt call you a suckker. but that list looks like a lolipop
jwlolol: vim and tmux dotfiles?
logi6000: @mitrocc paypal him 50
MABunglawala: sup
logi6000: geohot at gmail
NYCyril: What are dot files ???
iKanak_: Starting to wonder if AFL would perform better than all this deep learning nonsense
MABunglawala: Are u gonna jaim
logi6000: @jwlolol I have his vim and tmux dotfiles I use them
mr_stochastic: @NYCyril Config settings
bulksquat_thrust: @NYCyril usually vim configs and bash configs
TheKoreanZombi: I am an expert at identifying randomness after reading George's book recommendation: A Million Random Digits with 100,000 Normal Deviates.
l1ght5p33d: files that start with .
mangoxavier: When it runs what is an error? the strings that start with 2?
routerkicker: @iKanak_ it's just muzero he's gotten this to work with other deep learning algos
l1ght5p33d: must do ls -al
MABunglawala: jailbreak PS5? when it comes out
NYCyril: oh ok thanks @mr_stochastic @bulksquat_thrust
jwlolol: @logi6000 yeah that's why i was wondering which dotfiles hah
logi6000: if that's it then I'll just fucking release them.
bulksquat_thrust: his zsh theme is afowler
mitrocc: George should starting doing 15 bucks for 5 minute code review
DeeboMC: yea i was just refencing which .files
MABunglawala: shit I dont understanding anything whatever he is doing. anyone else like that in here?
bulksquat_thrust: colorscheme is a jetbrains darcula clone
3ygun: How did he rate the Liberty rally?
l1ght5p33d: @DeeboMC ghidra with more tooltips
nsielicki: i think i was wrong
nsielicki: clearly
munchfumble: why do you use jupyter?
TheKoreanZombi: @munchfumble Why not?
logi6000: @georgehotz what dotfiles you talking bout
zetto97: @fukurowlz yes, im learning english, and u? how many languages you can speak?
bulksquat_thrust: @zetto97 what is your native language?
OrlinTheMage: touch me
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d holy shit dude, thats rabbit hole shit for me
zetto97: @bulksquat_thrust spanish and russian
mangoxavier: whoa
munchfumble: @TheKoreanZombi idk, I don't really know what it is other than a text editor
Pr0ject414: Throw more trains
Pr0ject414: call yourself the conductor
TheKoreanZombi: @munchfumble Ah. Gotcha. He uses it because it is quick to prototype.
DeeboMC: did they contract
mangoxavier: it was plus and then minus interesting
bulksquat_thrust: @zetto97 cool! I kinda know spanish, trying to learn to read latin rn
nsielicki: does it need to experience more things or does it need to learn more from the experiences its had
wthbro: hello
aaaakshat: Oh crap we're live again
aaaakshat: can anyone update what's happening
DeeboMC: ... contract scorpion computer services for that? lol
logi6000: @aaaakshat people want to know what the dotfiles are
bulksquat_thrust: @aaaakshat hes using an ai lib to solve a lunar lander game
aaaakshat: ooooh that's epiuc
aaaakshat: thanks
l1ght5p33d: @logi6000 that's why they want them.. no one knows
KAZERKE: Hello George moon2S
Pr0ject414: @nsielicki i would contend that it needs to learn more from what is has already experienced
cafe807: geohot is in love I guess
wthbro: lighting temperature is terrible BibleThump
logi6000: @l1ght5p33d but if its tmux and vim or anything else in his config repo
zetto97: @bulksquat_thrust very good broo
mangoxavier: yall are joking right? go google how to terminal and don't waste time
logi6000: then he scammin
nsielicki: @Pr0ject414 see i'm leaning the other way, i think it's just not trying enough new stuff
nsielicki: is 414 a reference to MIL?
l1ght5p33d: @logi6000 what config repo
DeeboMC: @zetto97 how do you get spanish and russian as your natives? interesting language combo
logi6000: @l1ght5p33d on his github
Pr0ject414: MKE
cod4_lightning: why you are yellow?
nsielicki: word, I grew up in germantown
Pr0ject414: nice.
mangoxavier: How are you keeping track of what you're learning when you're changing the numbers?
zetto97: @deebomc family :O
mangoxavier: just versioning or all in your head?
cafe807: gave up the Corona thing?
logi6000: https://github.com/geohot/configuration?files=1 this
ak0ya_: no corona
Waldoqq: give me back corona :(
DeeboMC: exotic conciousness you're running in they're breh @zetto97
DeeboMC: there*
logi6000: @waldoqq he dont care about Rona no more. he just went to a protest
Waldoqq: WTF
DeeboMC: 'rona lmao
Waldoqq: fakes news
logi6000: @waldoqq no he did
DeeboMC: he didnt go tho.
Waldoqq: George is the best law abiding citizen who never tries to insult big brother
logi6000: @deebomc oh he didnt
DeeboMC: he thought about it
l1ght5p33d: config is weak af
Waldoqq: idk who you ar etalking about @logi6000
mangoxavier: doing -150 to -400 with that last change but only a few positives, the one before had quite a few positives with lower - numbers
l1ght5p33d: my bash_rc is like 200 lines
forkdb: Is Kim dead?
l1ght5p33d: can i just dump it in chat or no
nsielicki: lol
bulksquat_thrust: Some studies are finding that the self-isolation hasnt really impacted total deaths at all
logi6000: @forkdb prob
forkdb: Ohh
logi6000: @l1ght5p33d prob not
DeeboMC: pastebin it
mangoxavier: those are way higher
mangoxavier: nice lowering
logi6000: anyone want what could possibly be the dotfiles
logi6000: https://github.com/geohot/configuration?files=1
nsielicki: we went from 50 to 10 with I and it started behaving better -- maybe we overshot. I'd try 20
DeeboMC: @zetto97 spanish via south america i presume?
mangoxavier: oohhhhh damn it's doing better after it gets a positive then fails
DeeboMC: as opposed to spain or mexico
DeeboMC: im guessing argentina
nsielicki: Does it need to learn more from what it's experienced or does it need to experience new things
mangoxavier: That's awesome
nsielicki: hell yeah
zetto97: @deebomc spanish via Spain
logi6000: remember sub only chat
mangoxavier: I think it only learns through exp? right?
eeXecute: Have a good night George
mangoxavier: hmmm
DeeboMC: ah i see. dinner at your folks house must be dank af lol
Pr0ject414: Nature vs. Nurture arguments
nizero: George how was the protest
Santiago_LHC: nature is nurturing
info303: i think lunar lander gets a big reward for landing safely rather than crashing, but it can't seem to stumble upon that scenario
l1ght5p33d: good config https://pastebin.com/Fd7bdmqL
mangoxavier: beginners luck
kniightt: hi george thumpF
logi6000: I use zsh
logi6000: with vim controls
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d noiice!
mangoxavier: It's like it rewards then is complacent and loses. But it looked like it was losing less after each success.
Pr0ject414: on the surface it doesnt appear to remember what it has learned
Kawhiet: Maybe the goal should be hover first?
nsielicki: i fucking hate zsh, i hate that catalina defaults to it. try `printf hello` in your terminal
l1ght5p33d: @DeeboMC like that ffr
l1ght5p33d: thats what you want
nsielicki: where did the output go? zsh removed it
logi6000: @nsielicki echo hello
nsielicki: right, it likes it if you give it a newline, but if it's not there it eats your output
DeeboMC: lol hell yea boi
logi6000: pretty sure george uses zsh
mangoxavier: yeah, left over how long though, and is there a way for it to improve faster and not be so random. that's the issue right?
monaliso: you should really be concerned about "printf", yep
mik12f4: there are so many more ways to fuck up i guess
Roundlay: naysay2SITREP
mangoxavier: push that to 3 lol
perfectdotexe: Geohot is my inspiration, he's the reason why I strive to be the person I can be. Knocking out what I need to do plus more.
Jehhred: If only the objective was to make the rocket fall as fast as possible
perfectdotexe: First time I caught him streaming.
Pr0ject414: The Unity ML agents has that feature i believe.
l1ght5p33d: why are there ssh in geohots config hes gonna hack me now isn't he
mangoxavier: Feels very close
nsielicki: @monaliso try python3 -c "import sys; sys.stdout.buffer.write(b'hello')" if you want a different example
DeeboMC: goin extra innings tonight. thinking of tapping out, eating tacos and finally starting DEVS
maddyakhil: !uptime
nsielicki: zsh eats malformed output which is ridiculous. It'd be one thing if they added an extra newline, it's another when they just stop showing you output of programs you run
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d wait what? you got his configs?
Pr0ject414: give it more trainings?
logi6000: @deebomc yeah https://github.com/geohot/configuration?files=1
logi6000: they been public
logi6000: loo
nsielicki: lol
logi6000: lol
neekolulbot: lol
mangoxavier: you also rose dim
info303: i remember alphazero filling up the buffer first before even beginning the training, not sure if this applies here
DOWRIGHT: 50*
perfectdotexe: $ twenty doll hairs
Santiago_LHC: @DeeboMC DEVS is good!
Pr0ject414: you would hope to see a nice curve
logi6000: I'll give the link to anybody for 25 dollar bitcoin.
perfectdotexe: @DOWRIGHT what up LUL dowrigPup
Pr0ject414: that unfortunately does not appear to be a curve
neekolulbot: what do you think about financial RL? For asset allocation among many assets?
DOWRIGHT: hi @perfectdotexe just fixing bugs. what up with you?
DeeboMC: batman@z840 ? @l1ght5p33d
logi6000: @dowright yo you Streaming tomorrow?
swagrrr: did we ever fold a protein?
CaptainRoberts: !uptime
perfectdotexe: @DOWRIGHT Wrapping up classes, just did a few tryhackme challenges.
DOWRIGHT: yes ^_^ @logi6000
logi6000: @dowright sick
mangoxavier: haha
ancientchineseelder: on adderall today george?
CaptainRoberts: how long has he been streaming, chat?
DeeboMC: @Santiago_LHC im looking forward to it
bubblesnot: What would Elon do?
nsielicki: 6 hours maybe?
wthbro: what the idea behind the program, want it to hover or land?
markydothh: Does George do adderall?
Santiago_LHC: You can do it, Mu!
logi6000: @ancientchineseelder that's a no no drugs prob gonna be a ban topic soon
PrivateOrange: Run a huge cluster and train train train
bulksquat_thrust: @DOWRIGHT sup!
DOWRIGHT: yooooooooooooo o/
perfectdotexe: Geohot is naturally on drugs, he doesn't need em
JdPaulBlart: we need a deeper net squadR
mangoxavier: It spent more time like you thought but then dicked around like before
bulksquat_thrust: @DOWRIGHT still working on the next-gen firewall?
DeeboMC: @l1ght5p33d it was in the ssh folder
Kawhiet: professional hyperparameter tuner
JdPaulBlart: new goal is to create an ai to tune ais
DOWRIGHT: yea @bulksquat_thrust just uploaded the new build to github today
logi6000: @jdpaulblart were gonna need an ai to tune that ai
bubblesnot: Can you train it to just hover consistently?
bulksquat_thrust: @DOWRIGHT sick!
JdPaulBlart: recursive ai tuning
ancientchineseelder: im new in here what is the project here?
mik12f4: maybe lunar lander is a boeing product?
info303: curious if it would quickly learn to land between the poles if you start it off in the corner
ancientchineseelder: i last tuned in during covid
logi6000: @jdpaulblart inefficient and never gets the job done
logi6000: what more do you want
perfectdotexe: I was doing a discussion in college about machine learning and decided to clip geohot from a youtube video, I almost posted him smoking weed LUL
isalhi: what’s the project tnght?
mangoxavier: dumb car
logi6000: anyone want dotfiles that wasn't here earlier
logi6000: 25 dollar eth
DeeboMC: currently scannin the .files like DBstyle
perfectdotexe: dowrigPup u take dogecoin? @logi6000
mangoxavier: yes lower random
Waldoqq: big models Kreygasm
Pr0ject414: Take everything to the extreme
Pr0ject414: max it all out
logi6000: @perfectdotexe nah bitcoin or ethereum
Santiago_LHC: 100 dollars for my wallpaper collection
mangoxavier: yes
mangoxavier: 3
peter35_: perfectdotexe ConcernDoge
DeeboMC: dude .. so i can make monies now?
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: thiccc models Kreygasm @Waldoqq
markydothh: Anyone heard about Hedera hashgraph? Any opinions?
mangoxavier: random at 1 maybe?
logi6000: @georgehotz you dont care if I quickly monetize your chat right. no. good thanks for permission
cod4_lightning: man i
logi6000: so I got a good zshrc goin for 5 dollar eth
logi6000: do I here 10 dollar
mangoxavier: 80 and 63 were positive
DeeboMC: lol it was publicly available as @l1ght5p33d said.. now its worth money ? whats goin on here lol
cod4_lightning: @georgehotz bro that dedication you have is remarkable!
mangoxavier: yeah!
SKPTCL: :)
Pr0ject414: "rev share ecosystem"
peter35_: 'can't use google' tax
SKPTCL: SKPTCL subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 1 month streak! :)
Kawhiet: just gotta train it another 3 hrs
l1ght5p33d: i write new geohot dotfile app
Pr0ject414: now that is a graph with a curve
l1ght5p33d: 8 dollars
mangoxavier: two in a row!
DeeboMC: how did i get it free?
Pr0ject414: its a little THICC but a curve none the less
l1ght5p33d: 7
manuchroma: !uptime
mangoxavier: ohh!
DeeboMC: batman@z840?????
Pr0ject414: play us some tomcr00se music
logi6000: anyone want a really nice tmux conf for 10 dollars eth. really nice even has time and date on bottom. uses ` for hotkey. best hotkey cant get a better one
raystriker98: let it run the whole night
mangoxavier: what is the reward rule for not dying?
whoishenry123: wouldn't this be easier to test if you had a more powerful GPU?
logi6000: all money goes back to gifting subs too
DeeboMC: @logi6000 ur killin me bro lol
nsielicki: can you recap what changes were made to get you here?
logi6000: so you might get your money back
jay_al97: @georgehotz has anyone gotten this to work better than this
nsielicki: k=3? replay size? iterations
nsielicki: it definitely is better
bulksquat_thrust: is this a library you can run with a gpu?
Kawhiet: barrel roll 2.0
yuvi___: just joined stream. anyone wanna explain whats going on?
logi6000: @deebomc I try my best
DeeboMC: haha
Pr0ject414: show the graph?
mangoxavier: oooh
nsielicki: nice
mangoxavier: hmmm
blizz191: activision elu different then relu?
mik12f4: yeah better
logi6000: @yuvi___ you have to send me 10 dollar eth to continue watching. he will ban otherwise. I give good tmux conf with purchase
l1ght5p33d: we only like prime numbers
l1ght5p33d: 67 > 69
bubblesnot: Does it have weight? Can you dump fuel before landing?
logi6000: monitizing
logi6000: hey where my star
l1ght5p33d: not sex wise tho
mangoxavier: hell yes
logi6000: I'm still subbed I have 2x multiplier
DeeboMC: good .xmobarrc, only 6 years old
l1ght5p33d: unless 67 is a really good move ...
Pr0ject414: add more neurons
mangoxavier: oh man two in a row then hover a long time
mangoxavier: 99, 92, then hover
nsielicki: does he live in sf or la?
bulksquat_thrust: them losses be gettin smaller
mangoxavier: 175!
logi6000: @nsielicki I'll tell you for 5 bucks eth
mik12f4: what does the first number of each line represent?
mangoxavier: hell yes! look at that 225
brofessorbob: He lives in SF
nsielicki: thanks
logi6000: @brofessorbob wrong
mangoxavier: 216
DeeboMC: @georgehotz are you batman@z840?
mangoxavier: this is a lot better
gardiyanismet: !time
brofessorbob: I live in Pacific Beach Bro. I think I'd know
DeeboMC: he lives in whales vagina
Pr0ject414: ADD MORE DENSE lolol
DeeboMC: not san fran
J3rwin: 256 Pog
Kawhiet: this honestly feels like gambling
fenharelthedreadwolf: what should I do to get selected for working in comma.ai?
logi6000: mission beach San Diego
mangoxavier: It learns a lot after it hovers
cod4_lightning: is the code on github?
Super_car_car: oh snap im in PL
mangoxavier: look at the pattern before it hovers
bulksquat_thrust: what protest?
cod4_lightning: what car do you have?
logi6000: wheres my star anyone else see its gone
mangoxavier: 1 pos then hover, then 2 pos then hover, then 3 or more pos then hover
JdPaulBlart: for the record i suggested deeper net like 30 mins so wheres my mod
routerkicker: yeah it's gone
logi6000: I'm still subbed tho.
kisspapa: trying to finish my elf infector virus for cybersec, been stuck for a day, fuck ELFs lol
Apimar: What we making today xD
cod4_lightning: what car do you have?
Pr0ject414: do even deeper net
logi6000: its gone
DeeboMC: you got a z840 at work?
mangoxavier: far bigger positives with this
JdPaulBlart: hows this DEEPER NET MR STREAMER
lebop: george what do you think about doing another hackerrank type of stream?
nsielicki: 3 consecutive positive results, don't you dare reset this shit
nsielicki: 4
logi6000: dont know what happened. I'm still subbed. twitch was afraid of my genius marketing ploys
DeeboMC: suggest it better!
info303: it learned to hever
info303: hover
mangoxavier: yess
Pr0ject414: RESET.... RESET... RESET... to the beat of the drums
mangoxavier: yesss
mangoxavier: more it hovers more success you see and higher each time
Kawhiet: learns to hover and then the randomness kicks in
DeeboMC: @logi6000 its hard out here for a pimp
logi6000: @deebomc lol
bulksquat_thrust: im trying to understand the 2D m.losses list number
nsielicki: train more on replay
nsielicki: increase i
mangoxavier: why winder rather than deeper?
Pr0ject414: hear me out... a deeper wider net
brofessorbob: Balls Deep Net
hardtarget4: lol
anasshm123: when she tells you go deeper but the programmer didn't give you enough pp
logi6000: @georgehotz guess twitch was afraid of my genius marketing ploys
cod4_lightning: imagine americans starting immigration to the middle east because of coronavirus?
DeeboMC: lmaooo
l1ght5p33d: wtf did u just do
DeeboMC: pp
mangoxavier: bignet is a type of desert in the south
fenharelthedreadwolf: can we make it mandatory that some action must be always performed ?
Waldoqq: I LOVE CORONAVIRUS I LOVE CORONAVIRUS I LOVE CORONAVIRUS I LOVE CORONAVIRUS I LOVE CORONAVIRUS I LOVE CORONAVIRUS
mangoxavier: yikes
DeeboMC: never heard of it. i want to eat bignet
nsielicki: @fenharelthedreadwolf we shouldn't have to, that's the point of munet
perfectdotexe: Does a geohot, hoot?
logi6000: twitch should give me my big dick star back
nsielicki: muzero or whatever
wthbro: When did you start programming?
anasshm123: I'm out of the loop can someone fill me on what's going on, is this Comma A.I 2.0?
mangoxavier: hmmmm
almondsnakes: yo this guy has a dishwasher he must be loaded
logi6000: twitch is just afraid of me
mangoxavier: oh shit
Waldoqq: @anasshm123 no its covid-19 2.0
cod4_lightning: how much would you sell comm ai for?
aalhendi: You still have a sustainable supply of limes in your pantry?
DeeboMC: holy shit. i didnt pronounce it right. you meant bignets like as in cafe du monde.. yea ive eaten those lmao
anasshm123: @Waldoqq thanks for the info
brofessorbob: 100 Billion Dollars
mangoxavier: oooooh
mangoxavier: that's sick
hardtarget4: we out here hovering
mangoxavier: that's awasome
brofessorbob: suck
KAZERKE: PogChamp YO
mangoxavier: FUCK YES!!!!1
JeanFrag: oohh
l1ght5p33d: OOOOOHHooo
anasshm123: clap clap clap
t0rment1337: OMG
brofessorbob: sick!
JeanFrag: Pog
nsielicki: that was fucking nuts
Roflz1lla: PogChamp
bulksquat_thrust: it was so close hahaha
Pr0ject414: THATS A WIN in my book fam
Penguino138: When does it refuel its landers?
breadhamandegg: Pog
Pr0ject414: big net for big dicks
l1ght5p33d: things so good
mangoxavier: fuck the car up the hill this motherfucker is flying
brofessorbob: Balls Deep Net
jeronm: Pog
logi6000: so I'mma just start monitizing again
DeeboMC: that just blem my mind
KAZERKE: which one
DeeboMC: how did it know?
peter35_: bignet mogs me
Waldoqq: incels OMEGALUL
anasshm123: How to know you are an Incel?
almondsnakes: that's a chad move
rahfuls: please limit facial touching in order to fade lord rona
wthbro: you know what I did today? nothing :)
anasshm123: I watched a doc on E-boys
DOWRIGHT: if you in this chat. you an incel.
brofessorbob: Pacific Beach is full of Chads
bulksquat_thrust: most incels are just simps in disguise
DOWRIGHT: oh wait....
info303: since it randomly picks from game history buffer, it might explain the instability of the value function
fenharelthedreadwolf: can we auto adjust neural networks size dynamically?
logi6000: I have a amazing screenrc best screenrc never been a better one. make you a 10x better programmer. only 10 dollars eth
mangoxavier: set random to 1
mangoxavier: real good
DeeboMC: bruh thats funny if u think that; theres just diverse ppl out here breh
mangoxavier: this is great
sk84uhlivin: PogChamp
info303: woot!
brofessorbob: lol
IMTotes: LULW
Penguino138: Geo Musk
mangoxavier: give it less gas lol
Super_car_car: this is amazing
brofessorbob: Bro landed in a crater
NYCyril: @logi6000 do you make screen great again with your screenrc ?
Penguino138: @brofessorbob You want to land in craters typically
Pr0ject414: ok hear me out again... lets do an even bigger deeper net.
cod4_lightning: imagine americans starts immigrating to the middle east because of coronavirus
brofessorbob: @Penguino138 Thanks Bro
logi6000: @nycyril yes better than tmux. best rc. best thing to ever touch your computer 10 dollars eth or if you order in the next 10 hours it's only 9.99 eth
info303: MOAR neurons!
nsielicki: @cod4_lightning nah i'm good thanks tho
Penguino138: @brofessorbob I mean its not the goal of the game, but in real life it's usually safer in craters
mik12f4: does it have to learn to shut off thrusters too?
l1ght5p33d: I saw geohot copy like three layers of neurons then it started working
brofessorbob: Is mission beach open to the public?
l1ght5p33d: this stream is blssed af
logi6000: @brofessorbob yea
mangoxavier: does it get an equal reward for thrusters off + in the flags?
fenharelthedreadwolf: sir I am a newbie and wanted to know can we dynamically adjust neural network size as we learn ?
mangoxavier: oh
brofessorbob: Trying to get pitted
logi6000: oh I dont know about now tho
DeeboMC: if i wasnt dodgin warrants id be in the trap rn... prolly watchin this on a phone with earbuds.. instead of the laptop i traded drugs for @DOWRIGHT true story; non incel here
Kawhiet: does this mean we'll get starfox?
brofessorbob: We training on CPU or GPU here?
logi6000: twitch give me my mother fucking big dick star back
DOWRIGHT: @DeeboMC airpods?
routerbomber: !uptime
DeeboMC: nah im fiscally responsibler than that. i bank my monmey
mangoxavier: ex machina shit you just did to the lander right there
logi6000: @deebomc so anyways I started snitching
DeeboMC: @logi6000 lmaooo
logi6000: lol jk
Waldoqq: @logi6000 NEVER SUBBED NEVER DONATED
LordHord: Star?
bulksquat_thrust: bulksquat_thrust subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 2 month streak! imagine not having a star
mangoxavier: ehhh
logi6000: @bulksquat_thrust twitch took my star
DOWRIGHT: isnt casting data to int > range > list > np also a huge bottleneck?
bulksquat_thrust: @logi6000 those bastards!
logi6000: I still have my 2x multiplier
Neoriginal: the biggest bottleneck is patience
logi6000: but now it just says I'm not subbed
JdPaulBlart: is this how you tuned autopilot
brofessorbob: @logi6000 contact twitch bro
JdPaulBlart: openpiliot
logi6000: @brofessorbob how
l1ght5p33d: @DOWRIGHT where does that happen
DOWRIGHT: i would assign np. random. choice to a local var np_random_choice and see if i can pull out some of those data converions.
mik12f4: what causes it to take more time on each game?
brofessorbob: @logi6000 IDK google it. Maybe twitter?
logi6000: should I just email them give me my mother fucking big dick star back on geohot channel
l1ght5p33d: lookup table? pickle?
gigafact: @logi6000 click on your username on chat. your sub just expired it looks like
nsielicki: fuck buzz aldrin
bulksquat_thrust: damn
bulksquat_thrust: lol
logi6000: j got it like two days ago
mangoxavier: everyone sub
chetdonovan: koilD
pwnbase: did you see the vid where buzz punched that guy
KAZERKE: would the AI knows about the 5G towers and corona ? 🤔
DOWRIGHT: @l1ght5p33d it might not be part of the code executing tbh. but the look with counter is doing similar, just not as extreme
l1ght5p33d: lookup table of every possible frame the game can be in to speed type conversion
DOWRIGHT: loop*
gaocaandra: what did i miss
gaocaandra: did it work?
DeeboMC: It did
gaocaandra: nice
mangoxavier: I don't see a pattern but hope the graph is good
DOWRIGHT: having to loop up a method ever iter is gunna add overhead.
gaocaandra: what was the problem
l1ght5p33d: rewrite game in assembly
DOWRIGHT: look
brofessorbob: Any module or tool to help benchmark python code to identify potential bottlenecks?
DeeboMC: What da prolem is
nsielicki: so... is that album art actually just captain crunch having sex with a crossdressing koolaid man?
DeeboMC: 😂
mhmd0: !live
DeeboMC: Made me cough up Newport smoke
nsielicki: hahah guess we're even
bulksquat_thrust: im just trying to figure out what the picture on the wall is a reference of
mik12f4: this one not as good
mangoxavier: one eye dude got cucked
fenharelthedreadwolf: does adding negative rewards any useful ?
DeeboMC: 😂 there we go @nsielicki
wthbro: what ⌨️ are you using?
mangoxavier: there are some hovers prett close
bulksquat_thrust: @wthbro you've done it now
wthbro: Kappa
mangoxavier: but not great positives
fenharelthedreadwolf: for example if it doesn't do anything for a certain time , you start reducing the rewards
DeeboMC: Emoji’s gettin slick @wthbro
Kawhiet: participation trophy
mangoxavier: graph doesn't look good
bulksquat_thrust: this ai is a summary of my self education in CS
bulksquat_thrust: "wants to learn but gives up"
logi6000: still letting me sub like it didnt yesterday.
bulksquat_thrust: haha
logi6000: just keeps saying something went wrong and shows me an ugly ass animated girl
LordHord: @logi6000 your card got declined homie
logi6000: no when I go into the menu to sub
DeeboMC: so what’s this deal with this ghidra shit @l1ght5p33d
치킨워커: are you hiring
l1ght5p33d: @DeeboMC assembly lookup table
l1ght5p33d: with tooltips
DeeboMC: The nsa just released it to the public tho?
scullionw: scullionw subscribed with Twitch Prime.
l1ght5p33d: @DeeboMC version 1 theyre probably on like at least 100 by now
mik12f4: does the first number represent how long its in the air?
DeeboMC: Ahh I see.. just taunting us n shit I guess.
JdPaulBlart: good night @georgehotz youre welcome for suggesting deeper net btw
luggy_b0i: @logi6000 If you're in the US make sure you pay with paypal. Xsolla might be triggering something with whoever your service provider is.
Faceless_Bard: good morning everyone o/
mangoxavier: watching this helps u figure it out
purpaleslushiii: @georgehotz what is the most important math to be a good coder?
mangoxavier: that graph is looking rather good
itsChopsticks: anyone else functionally retarded and doesnt understand it
itsChopsticks: just me? sick
nsielicki: this stuff is just very difficult, don't say that about yourself
luggy_b0i: @logi6000 And you might have to call them now if they blocked your card. I wont lie, it happened to me once.
DeeboMC: Nah bro, just need more prerequisites in place
mangoxavier: yes ever changing landscape and needing to learn.
calcmath: been gone a while, what is he doing now?
itsChopsticks: i'll just stick to writing really bad scripts in ps and python, compsci people just too big brain for me
brofessorbob: Is perl a dead language?
mik12f4: first numbers are all small
nsielicki: learn perl if you want to make money
nsielicki: dead languages pay more
Creamy_Goodness_: A strange game. The only winning move is not to play.
brofessorbob: I heard Cobal can make you loot
itsChopsticks: if you feel like supporting dead systems, sure
stone43_: Perl is easy to learn though if you know Ruby or Python
itsChopsticks: COBOL sucks ass
mangoxavier: yeah
mangoxavier: looks random
mangoxavier: your random is set to .02 not .05
FangSkillz: he doesn't read chat LUL
brofessorbob: Python popped my cherry and trying to figure a next language.
mangoxavier: yeah
DOWRIGHT: big disk club!
brofessorbob: 0.5
DeeboMC: Depends on if you want a really specific job at place that’s probably irrelevance; otherwise yeah don’t waste your time
nsielicki: your mcts was slow but you should work that back in real quick and see if it makes a difference
mik12f4: looks way worse?
Super_car_car: your discount is .98 instead of .998?
Super_car_car: ah my bad
tangobeer: !uptime
l1ght5p33d: discount is bad terminology
l1ght5p33d: going into the future does not mean good or bad, it should be a "reducing" or "avoiding" type of language
mik12f4: seems like it only learns when it takes its time
calcmath: whichhe playing iwht now? envirnment is
calcmath: still cartpole?
brofessorbob: Aite Bros. This Bro needs to sleep. Good luck with landing the lunar lander Geo-bro.
Waldoqq: anyone want to watch me stream Svelte?
calcmath: oops got mangled
Kawhiet: It's not learning to hover tho
DeeboMC: I wonder what carrot top’s up to right now. Prolly re-reading Knuth, working on the replacement for python
mangoxavier: nah
nsielicki: I had never heard of value prediction network, thought it might be related to value prediction in computer architecture but I guess it's not
nsielicki: I did a (failed) research project on microarchitecture VP
mangoxavier: yeah, before big net
Waldoqq: BibleThump
l1ght5p33d: typescript > python
Pr0ject414: whoever suggested the even bigger deep net is an asshole
Waldoqq: Typescript > English
Pr0ject414: lupoCREEP lupoCREEP
Faceless_Bard: a serious/not serious question chat : do you think tools like muzero will make speedrunning much harder , if the game devs build around it ?
calcmath: wider nets are more stable than deeper nets
routerkicker: branch prediction in modern cpu architectures is done by neural nets as well @nsielicki
mangoxavier: tighten net, confirm, raise random, confirm, adjust
mik12f4: what can you change to get first number above 500?
pogu: @routerkicker that's pretty insane. Is NN inference THAT cheap now
routerkicker: yeah it's right on the chip though
nsielicki: @routerkicker value prediction is not the same as branch prediction
l1ght5p33d: @Faceless_Bard Isn't speed running already hard why would it matter if the difficulty is changed
mangoxavier: self.epsilon = self.epsilon * self.decay
Faceless_Bard: l1ght5p33d probably making the games unbuggable ? one way
nsielicki: @routerkicker see https://www.cs.cmu.edu/afs/cs/academic/class/15740-f03/www/lectures/ValuePredictionDisc.htm
routerkicker: thanks
bulksquat_thrust: 5 hundred thousand
mangoxavier: Ɛ = Ɛ * decay :⇔ Ɛ = Ɛ * decay ^ X
mangoxavier: self.epsilon = self.epsilon * self.decay
nsielicki: @routerkicker if you're interested in trying the problem yourself, https://www.microarch.org/cvp1/
mangoxavier: got to go to bed, later
nsielicki: ut-austin just beat André Seznec by quite a bit which is a big deal
DeeboMC: @faceless_bard I was just about to say sorry no one address that because I thought it was interesting but I didn’t even know how to articulate why I felt like it wouldn’t have an effect but I guess that’s a theory, although “unbuggable” seems a little more optimistic than I’d be willing to bank on
tripcloth: whatch making geoh
Faceless_Bard: DeeboMC SeemsGood i think i could have asked that better . But yeah perhaps very optimistic , but maybe 'bugfree' enough so that its impossible to speedrun. It might be a tool publishers like , since put time limits that are always never enough for a game to be polished properly :thinking:
Faceless_Bard: since they*
DeeboMC: I could see that but *jeff goldblum voice* “life.. uh uh uh.. finds a way” 😆
Faceless_Bard: :P
gigafact: it's this what they do at TeslaAI
DeeboMC: with much less shit talking im sure
nsielicki: discount definitely was involved when we were winning that
stone43_: This is what ML engineers do all day
Faceless_Bard: with probably better hardware :o
Pr0ject414: we had 3 nets
nsielicki: i think it was really low like 96
Pr0ject414: when it was working
Pr0ject414: it wasnt wider than original
info303: tesla self driving neural net architechture is pretty nutty
DeeboMC: you have an article?
stone43_: ixnay on the eslaTay talk
Nicholai518: Hey @georgehotz showing you some LOVE from NY
DeeboMC: ok but i wanna know about thier neural net architechture and why its so nutty
DeeboMC: alktay*
Pr0ject414: we were at like 200k for the model
Fr0zenOfficial: good morning :)
Pr0ject414: what is it at now?
SparksCx: !uptime
Pr0ject414: when it worked*
raystriker98: congrats your model is a teenager
DeeboMC: "my cpu is a neural net processor, a learning compyootuh... ahhhehh"
nsielicki: models
mik12f4: better numbers an hour ago
SparksCx: lol
gigafact: haha
nsielicki: lmfao when it came in sideways
Faceless_Bard: LUL
Keboburrito: lol
t0rment1337: lmaoo
Faceless_Bard: need a compilation of those clips
Santiago_LHC: Did we land yet?
DeeboMC: its gettin funky
SparksCx: atleast is firing all it's rockets
DeeboMC: a few good ones
gigafact: this is amazing
routerkicker: once we touched the ground at 0 speed and then took off again
suav12: What are the plots?
DeeboMC: thats what i beeen thinkin... this mfker is forgetful
nsielicki: time on x axis, rewards is top graph, bottom graph is losses
bulksquat_thrust: ive decided im going to make an aimbot for bannerlord as my programming project
stone43_: I joined late. No MCTS?
Fr0zenOfficial: I just joined what we doin here? :D
Pr0ject414: didnt they have like 500000
nsielicki: MCTS was slow and didn't make a difference
electro_y0: !uptime
Pr0ject414: in the replay buffer
routerkicker: YES weigh samples by reward sounds good
l1ttlemtman: good morning
DeeboMC: yea because it needs some specificity
toxyviper: He make a game?
l1ttlemtman: a reinforcement learning environment
nsielicki: no he teach a computer to win game
DeeboMC: the game is just there to test his heuristic
info303: wonder if they will use this type of solution for real lunar landers one day :D
bulksquat_thrust: @info303 oh god i hope not
NoLimitFitness: !uptime
webuser011: george, are you a robot?
stone43_: at least not this model
info303: @bulksquat_thrust haha well, I mean if you fast forward into the future
routerkicker: nah they got lasers and analytical algorithms that work better. ML is used for realtime obstacle avoidance on landing though.
bulksquat_thrust: @info303 going to be some enders game shit where bots are learning on real landers hahaha
nsielicki: is that actually how the spacex landing works? lidar?
info303: well the output from the lazers would be the input into RL algorithm, and the analytical algorithms replaced with a neural net
nsielicki: I would think that the exhaust of the rocket would make that impossible
DeeboMC: are we at like 5 hours now?
opheimer: !uptime
nsielicki: it's way past 5 hours, closer to 7 or 8
routerkicker: idk about spacex maybe we can get george to break nda LUL
opheimer: no Nightbot?
l1ttlemtman: nda
maddyakhil: !uptime
Pr0ject414: LIKE A ROCK
DeeboMC: thanks mod lol
stone43_: if Chevrolet built a lunar lander
tytos01: how was the protest @georgehotz ?
bulksquat_thrust: muda muda muda
DeeboMC: he ended up staying home
Santiago_LHC: Motivation!
JoeMountMount: just joined, what's he doin?
l1ttlemtman: you should have bought the expensive macbook
bulksquat_thrust: when you install visual studio and it just starts poppin up cmds all over the screen
l1ttlemtman: get a mac pro
nsielicki: get one of those usb-c gpus maybe
nsielicki: enclosure
JoeMountMount: what happened to solving COVID Kappa
SciTwi: Hi George! How are you doing with all the stuff that's going on?
l1ttlemtman: do you speak chinese ?
mik12f4: what does the number before the reward represent?
entangledbeing: How much u make on twitch lol
nsielicki: you ever work with FPGAs? You think this sort of turnaround on validation is long, try waiting 12 hours for synthesis
IaMvAzU: r u planning on becoming a twitch partner?
bulksquat_thrust: ive got the beefiest pc you can build and visual studio still runs like a snail hobbHands
nsielicki: @mik12f4 number of steps before game dies
info303: @mik12f4 timesteps
JakeLes: Visual studio runs well wat
mik12f4: thanks
l1ttlemtman: make a carla reinforcement agent
DeeboMC: bro when this thing gets cooin is when you need to put on stranglehold by nugent and come in guns blazin
l1ght5p33d: @JoeMountMount send comma ai a mass spectrometer
l1ght5p33d: an*
l1ght5p33d: a
DeeboMC: Cookin*
JoeMountMount: @l1ght5p33d why would you need a mass spec lol
TasosTheLord: HeyGuys
l1ght5p33d: an ai mass spectrometer
JoeMountMount: yeah why
l1ttlemtman: muzero on go thinks 12 steps ahead
nsielicki: i believe this problem will be solved tonight
tytos01: can you do some GridSearchCV on this ?
l1ght5p33d: @JoeMountMount because its too expensive for you
DeeboMC: https://music.youtube.com/watch?v=MRj5KT3742o&feature=share
JoeMountMount: like why would ai help mass spectometry
l1ttlemtman: yes that was for the paper version
l1ttlemtman: they ran another version for 2 weeks or so
l1ght5p33d: @JoeMountMount now you're asking the right questions
JakeLes: So this is the guy they base all the hackers on in movies
mik12f4: wouldnt there have to be a minimum number of timesteps in order for it not to crash?
JoeMountMount: @l1ght5p33d LUL but what was he planning to do w it?
l1ght5p33d: also sammy kamkar
l1ght5p33d: samy
PFY1: hey guys, how do i get started with python and ML?
stone43_: read
JoeMountMount: take a class
JoeMountMount: or watch some free lectures
info303: tons of cheap online courses
l1ttlemtman: make a carla agent
knitler_: chess wouldnt the reward value matter less?
l1ttlemtman: that would be cool with muzero
l1ght5p33d: @PFY1 read all this at least 3 times https://machinelearningmastery.com/start-here/
l1ght5p33d: then look for code to copy and paste
smurfd0: now it had those "feelers" for a bit (i guess they are thrusters)
l1ttlemtman: wow thats good advice lol
PFY1: @l1ght5p33d thanks lol
stone43_: That's a good site
Santiago_LHC: I have another motivational song: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VjEq-r2agqc
kerastan11: Hey George, have you done any more talks related to your talk on your simulation "religion"?
JoeMountMount: does george actually read anything hes just been skimming random articles for the past 15 minutes
DeeboMC: @Santiago_LHC nice but maybe a little TOO on the nose.. jus imo lol
fElixb: Good morning from Germany!
tripcloth: here i go again on my own - whitesnake
c9_will_get_out_of_groups: What are you working on today?
ResonatorGames: so cheesy
l1ght5p33d: state-action-reward-state-action
saeveritt: chill beats to quarantine to?
DeeboMC: second for whitesnake @tripcloth
Jehhred: I disappear for 30 minutes and this is what I come back to
nsielicki: emo song request: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=whPh_PasI58
Pr0ject414: is the problem that we need to reset the whole mode
ResonatorGames: sledgehammer isn't inspirational. It's about sex.
l1ght5p33d: always remember q <- q + a(r + dqs1 - qs))
l1ght5p33d: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/State%E2%80%93action%E2%80%93reward%E2%80%93state%E2%80%93action
DeeboMC: @georgehotz take @tripcloth 's requesst
l1ght5p33d: always
birkett0011: BibleThump
routerkicker: hackerman curling the youtube title
l1ttlemtman: did you watch the alphago movie already now ?
nsielicki: >adams song on recommended ;_;
DannyB_VG: camping in alaska is a amazing band
mashafique: Documentary about incels LUL ?
poseidondunaja: !uptime
Penguino138: Penguino138 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 2 month streak! Ayyy
DeeboMC: lunar lander is gonna come in moody now
eimis1337: !uptime
socialnotsocial: what happened with protein folding?
hoebamaa: Yeah what is that? Sounds real nice Geo
Depoise: !uptime
l1ght5p33d: @socialnotsocial we're benchmarking faster algorithm . We'll come back to that
JoeMountMount: yeah I wanna know what happened to the COVID stuff too
Jeptah88: What is it learning?
l1ttlemtman: lunar landing
Jeptah88: Oh, coll I see
DeeboMC: fuck it, when in doubt, crank up some bucket
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: he does not want to know
l1ttlemtman: please play the atari game
Penguino138: @georgehotz how often are you a late night coder?
l1ttlemtman: its easier to see how it performs there
nsielicki: are you using the actual gym version of the game still? this isn't just like a fucked up reward function right?
DeeboMC: minusthebear
routerkicker: yeah it's the original
Jeptah88: Are we seeing a sample game or is it really learning 1 game at a time?
l1ght5p33d: it was better before
Jeptah88: LUL
Penguino138: Is there a certain time of day you prefer programming or does it just depend?
DeeboMC: reminds me of myexitunfair
nitrixen: @Penguino138 Ideally while I'm awake.
Penguino138: I mean it for geo :p
nsielicki: asking that gets you banned, stop asking
TasosTheLord: or subscribe and you can ask Kappa
aykevy: hammer Pog
hoebamaa: asking what?
DeeboMC: are these people meming or are they serious about it
mashafique: I think at this point people are just memeing.
gigafact: never give up, never surrender
l1ght5p33d: copy paste more keras layers i saw you do that and it worked earlier
l1ttlemtman: run the atari game
petxe: Good morning! ^^
Jeptah88: GG
DeeboMC: lol ok. *faith in humanity stabilzes*
Jehhred: Who would have thought balancing a stick is easier than landing a space shuttle
DeeboMC: dude i lunar lander was where its at
Captain_Cavo: snake
info303: start it from the upright position!
l1ght5p33d: snek
Captain_Cavo: nokia style
nsielicki: just needs a fresh look on a new day
DeeboMC: i cant get jiggy with this shit
DeeboMC: hell yea boiii
DeeboMC: brute force, no finesse
lord_alpaca_666: this is what happened to the european mars rover
DeeboMC: thing is just flinging spaghetti at the wall
WillGreen98: How long has George been streaming?
Jehhred: 3 days
P0LY: !uptime
Jeptah88: !uptime
DeeboMC: 8 or 9 hours
forkdb: !uptime
P0LY: :o
DeeboMC: im guessing
forkdb: Ohok
Crocodile_Dendi_: 5 hrs 54
Jeptah88: I see 5:54
DeeboMC: oh shit.. way off
lord_alpaca_666: i like jupyter lab because it has dark mode
nsielicki: !uptime
7pius: george hotz is so sick, he might have been infected
DeeboMC: i like that
DeeboMC: bro you got a deep bench.. yung phil jackson over here
nsielicki: yeah, increase j
raystriker98: leave it open
Jeptah88: Do it
KAZERKE: do it
bloopsterr: go for it
mashafique: Farming channel points overnight PogChamp
bobsmash: yess :)
DeeboMC: muzero shows some promise
raystriker98: I support
okeeeeeee: me
DeeboMC: muzero seems worth it... let it learn regardless tho
raystriker98: maybe we'll clip the video of a successful landing for you
guinness84: it solves both CartPole and CartPole PogChamp
routerkicker: are there other algos wich give you a dynamics model?
DeeboMC: they way it does it tho seeems more intelligent when it does get it right. it just doesnt seem to learn from its past very effieciently
l1ttlemtman: how many searches does it do on muzero compared to ppo ?
Jeptah88: The landing spot is in the same place, it should be really easy
Penguino138: beautiful
DeeboMC: it was just chillin
erlsek: noobzero
DeeboMC: burnn
WEEEEEEEELL_ITS_KNOCC_OUT: LUL
Jeptah88: DeepMind will crash your lunar lander
l1ttlemtman: how many searches does it do on muzero compared to ppo ?
DeeboMC: deepmind is tenacious tho
Jeptah88: Like butter
l1ttlemtman: but still that way muzero has a lot more potential
KAZERKE: Wowee
sakshambhutani2001: nice
JjohnConstantine: what's the end goal?
birkett0011: Are there more complex simulations to test on? How many variable can these realistically handle?
nsielicki: any explanation for why the losses do that on the tail?
l1ttlemtman: go is 10^170 position
l1ttlemtman: s
l1ttlemtman: @birkett0011
DeeboMC: openai sure takes its goddamn time tho.. deepmind just continually hucks it til failure lol
Leo__dog: @georgehotz if i gave you my ip, could you be able to hack me
guinness84: are u rendering 1 to 1 with deepminds code
DeeboMC: finesse tho
jsnake794: hey i caught one of your streams
nsielicki: pybind11
DeeboMC: whats deepmind's strategy
DeeboMC: fall?
petxe: @georgehotz You think Java is a good programming language to start cooding?
l1ttlemtman: still deepmind > openai
birkett0011: are there more complex gyms available?
l1ttlemtman: yes carla
DeeboMC: 10 billion iterations til succes?
Jeptah88: DM trying to do barrelrolls
mik12f4: why does the landscape change?
info303: deepmind was working on starcraft2 bot, how far have they come? I think they had it working like a year ago
mars4real: PogChamp
ppnn123w: !uptime
l1ght5p33d: how much change makes it not muzero anymore?
l1ttlemtman: they beat a professional player
DeeboMC: openai sits there and reflects lol
info303: i think they had an unveil on twitch like a year ago
hardtarget4: openai too good
DeeboMC: meanwhile, DM's like....
info303: and I think they trained it for 200 real-time years in 2 weeks or something like that
l1ttlemtman: they beat lee sedol in go and some liquid guy in starcraft
DeeboMC: lol
Snooker_snooker_snooker: it finally discovered theres a y-axis force
l1ght5p33d: how did u get MuModel from the psuedocode?
info303: google money haha
l1ttlemtman: google buys you gpu
Pr0ject414: wasnt that paper able to do it 600 runs?
castavs: @petxe I think he hates java. lol
nsielicki: thanks for the stream, frustrating but hey this shit is always frustrating
nsielicki: if it was easy everyone would do it
ofaas: gg
mik12f4: thanks for the entertainment, goodnight
DeeboMC: you gonna keep your muzero model learin' overnight after stream ends?
castavs: This is Thor's hammer in an ice lake
sakshambhutani2001: You can write some sorta sdk of bot detection for website and make people label commaai's data
Joselinis: Goodmorming
nsielicki: ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)
l1ttlemtman: they do already
l1ttlemtman: comma pencil
DeeboMC: do you have cable?
Gamer_nohope: !uptime
nsielicki: post notebook to github when
sakshambhutani2001: no that is for people but like you can give it to all website like Not a bot stuff
Jeptah88: GGs
NatePh_07: it was a good night
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: GG
l1ght5p33d: extend keras layer = new-muzero = newzero
mik12f4: Forgot, any daytraders, VSTM 8 est, goodnight again
Penguino138: Hope to see you soon geo
fedexkinkos: teach me how to dougie
gigafact: thanks for all the streams
DeeboMC: do you have cable?
NatePh_07: what should we try next
ErmBison: whats next?
tangobeer: are you streaming tomorrow?
K0enich: comma.space soon?
l1ttlemtman: please write a better monte carlo search
Keboburrito: lesson learned, openai > muzero for space. Thanks for the streams
birkett0011: You think these can be practically applied to more complex models like in https://cloud.anylogic.com/
castavs: How comma will solve the problem of different models with same name in different countries?
wthbro: will you do a series for newbies, this is too complicated to grasp
l1ttlemtman: or run muzero with carla
routerkicker: thanks for the stream. byebye!
info303: more AI streams! SeemsGood
nsielicki: peace and good night
baconslices13: i just joined after finishing hw lmao
wthbro: rip
pwnbase: Goodnight, God bless you, God bless these United States.
calcmath: goodnight
Waldoqq: goodnight man I enjoyed the stream
lebop: george what do you think about doing another hackerrank type of stream? please
wthbro: a viewer :(
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: BlessRNG BlessRNG
tangobeer: are you going to be streaming tomorrow?
smurfd0: one step for cartpol one tiny step for lunar
l1ttlemtman: there is a straight up gym env for carla
l1ttlemtman: just change and run
l1ght5p33d: @pwnbase hmmm....
fedexkinkos: can u do a steam where u personally teach me how to solve hacker rank
l1ttlemtman: ssh into gpuslave
axiosz: what was the artist you were listening the past days on stream?
t0mmv: which gpu are you using?
NatePh_07: see ya George
solyyd: whats your next big project